<ar>
16.5:
يركز أحدث إصدار من تطبيق WooCommerce على تحسينات الثبات! إضافة إلى ذلك، يمكن لمستخدمي WooPayments الآن الاستمتاع بالتبديل بسلاسة بين العملات في عرض ملخص الودائع. قم بالترقية الآن للحصول على تجربة WooCommerce أكثر سلاسة!
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.5:
In der neuesten Version der WooCommerce-App stehen Stabilitätsverbesserungen im Vordergrund! Außerdem können WooPayments-Benutzer in der Zusammenfassung für Auszahlungen ab sofort nahtlos zwischen Währungen hin- und herwechseln. Führe jetzt ein Upgrade durch und profitiere von einem reibungsloseren WooCommerce-Erlebnis!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
16.5:
La versión más reciente de la aplicación WooCommerce se centra en mejoras en la estabilidad. Además, ahora los usuarios de WooPayments pueden cambiar fácilmente entre divisas en la vista Resumen de depósitos. Actualiza ahora para disfrutar de una mejor experiencia con WooCommerce.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
16.5 :
La dernière version de l’application WooCommerce se concentre sur l’amélioration de la stabilité ! En outre, les utilisateurs de WooPayments peuvent dorénavant changer de devise en toute fluidité sur l’aperçu Récapitulatif des dépôts. Mettez à niveau WooCommerce dès maintenant pour profiter d’une expérience plus fluide !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.5:
המהדורה האחרונה של אפליקציית WooCommerce ממוקדת בשיפורי יציבות! ועוד: מעכשיו, משתמשי WooPayments ייהנו ממעבר נוח בין מטבעות בתצוגת 'סיכום הפקדות'. משדרגים עכשיו ונהנים מחוויית WooCommerce חלקה יותר!
</iw-IL>
<id>
16.5:
Aplikasi WooCommerce versi terbaru mengutamakan perbaikan stabilitas! Selain itu, pengguna WooPayments kini dapat mengganti mata uang dengan mudah pada tampilan Ringkasan Deposit. Upgrade sekarang untuk menikmati pengalaman WooCommerce yang lebih lancar!
</id>
<it-IT>
16.5:
L'ultima versione dell'app WooCommerce si concentra sui miglioramenti in termini di stabilità. Inoltre, gli utenti WooPayments ora possono passare facilmente da una valuta all'altra nella visualizzazione di riepilogo degli acconti. Effettua subito l'aggiornamento per vivere un'esperienza WooCommerce più fluida.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.5:
WooCommerce アプリの最新バージョンは安定性の向上に重点を置いています。 さらに、WooPayments ユーザーはデポジット概要ビューで通貨間をシームレスに切り替えられるようになりました。 今すぐアップグレードして、WooCommerce エクスペリエンスをさらにスムーズにしましょう !
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.5:
최신 우커머스 앱 버전에서는 안정성 향상에 중점을 두고 있습니다. 아울러 WooPayments 사용자는 이제 예치금 요약 보기의 통화 사이를 원활하게 전환할 수 있습니다. 더 원활한 우커머스 환경을 위해 지금 업그레이드하세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.5:
De nieuwste versie van de WooCommerce-app richt zich op verbeteringen van de stabiliteit! Daarnaast kunnen gebruikers van WooPayments nu genieten van naadloos schakelen tussen valuta's in de weergave Overzicht van stortingen. Upgrade nu voor een vloeiendere WooCommerce-ervaring!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.5:
A versão mais recente do app do WooCommerce é voltada para melhorias na estabilidade. Usuários do WooPayments agora podem trocar tranquilamente de moeda na visualização Resumo de depósitos. Faça upgrade agora mesmo para ter uma experiência melhor no WooCommerce!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.5:
Последняя версия приложения WooCommerce нацелена на повышение стабильности! Кроме того, пользователи WooPayments теперь могут без проблем переключаться между валютами в представлении «Сводка по платежам». Обновите приложение WooCommerce и работайте с удовольствием!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.5:
Den senaste versionen av WooCommerce-appen fokuserar på stabilitetsförbättringar. Dessutom kan WooPayments-användare nu smidigt växla mellan valutor i vyn Insättningsöversikt. Uppgradera nu för en smidigare WooCommerce-upplevelse.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.5:
En son WooCommerce uygulaması sürümü istikrar iyileştirmelerine odaklanıyor. Ayrıca WooPayments kullanıcıları artık Depozito Özeti görünümünde para birimleri arasında sorunsuzca geçiş yapabilir. Daha sorunsuz bir WooCommerce deneyimi için hemen yükseltin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.5：
最新版 WooCommerce 应用程序重点提升了稳定性！ 此外，WooPayments 用户现在可以在“存款摘要”视图中无缝切换货币。 立即升级，享受更顺畅的 WooCommerce 体验！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.5:
最新版本的 WooCommerce 應用程式加強提升穩定性！ 此外，WooPayments 使用者現在可輕鬆在「存款摘要」畫面中切換不同貨幣。 立即升級，享受更順暢的 WooCommerce 體驗！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
16.5:
The latest WooCommerce app version focuses on stability improvements! Additionally, WooPayments users can now seamlessly switch between currencies on the Deposits Summary view. Upgrade now for a smoother WooCommerce experience!
</en-US>
