<ar>
3.0:
* يدعم التطبيق الآن عمليات استرداد الأموال حسب المبلغ. يتوافر على شاشة تفاصيل الطلب، ويتيح لك إصدار استرداد أموال جزئي أو كامل يدويًا لطلب مدفوع.
* تُظهر المنتجات ذات الصور المتعددة جميع الصور الآن في المعرض.
* إصلاح الخطأ: نادرًا ما يؤدي الحفظ أثناء الوجود على شاشة "إضافة ملحوظة الطلب" إلى حدوث عطل. أما الآن، فكلمة "نادرًا" أصبحت "أبدًا".
* يتضمن عرض تفاصيل الطلب الآن طريقة شحن الطلب.
</ar>
<de-DE>
3.0:
* Die App unterstützt jetzt Rückerstattung nach Betrag. Diese Option findest du auf dem Bildschirm der Bestelldetails, und du kannst manuell eine teilweise oder vollständige Rückerstattung für einen bezahlten Auftrag gewähren.
* Bei Produkten mit mehreren Bildern werden jetzt alle Bilder in einer Galerie angezeigt.
* Fehlerkorrektur: Selten führte der Speichervorgang auf dem Bildschirm zum Hinzufügen einer Notiz zum Auftrag zu einem Absturz. Jetzt wurde aus „selten“ nie.
* Die Ansicht mit den Auftragsdetails beinhaltet jetzt die Versandmethode für den Auftrag.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
3.0:
* Ahora la aplicación admite reembolsos por importe. Está disponible en la pantalla de detalles del pedido y te permite emitir manualmente un reembolso parcial o total en un pedido pagado.
* Los productos con varias imágenes ahora las muestran todas en una galería.
* Corrección de errores: En raras ocasiones, el guardado en la pantalla "Añadir nota de pedido" provocaba un error. Ahora, "en raras ocasiones" es "nunca".
* La vista de detalles del pedido ahora incluye el método de envío.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
3.0 :
* L'application prend désormais en charge les remboursements par montant. Cette fonctionnalité est disponible sur l'écran des détails de la commande et vous permet d'exécuter manuellement un remboursement partiel ou complet d'une commande payée.
* Lorsque des produits possèdent plusieurs images, elles sont désormais toutes présentées dans une galerie.
* Résolution de bug : il arrivait dans de rares cas un échec de l'enregistrement à partir de l'écran « Ajouter une note à la commande ». Désormais, il n'y a plus aucun échec de l'enregistrement.
* La vue présentant les détails de la commande mentionne désormais le mode de livraison de la commande.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
3.0:
* כעת האפליקציה תומכת בהחזרים כספיים לפי סכום. אפשרות זו זמינה במסך הפרטים של ההזמנה. ניתן לבצע ידנית החזר חלקי או מלא עבור הזמנה ששולמה.
* מוצרים עם תמונות מרובות יוצגו מעכשיו עם כל התמונות בגלריה.
* תיקוני באגים: לעתים נדירות, שמירה במסך 'הוספת פתק להזמנה' הייתה גורמת לקריסה. עכשיו, זה כבר לא קורה.
* בתצוגה של פירוט ההזמנה אפשר עכשיו לראות את שיטת המשלוח שנבחרה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
3.0:
* Aplikasi kini mendukung pengembalian dana menurut jumlah. Tersedia di layar detail pesanan, dan memungkinkan Anda mengeluarkan pengembalian dana sebagian atau penuh secara manual untuk pesanan yang telah dibayar.
* Produk dengan beberapa gambar kini menampilkan semua gambar di galeri.
* Perbaikan bug: Jarang, penyimpanan saat di layar “Add Order Note” menyebabkan crash. Kini, “jarang” menjadi “tidak pernah”.
* Tampilan detail pesanan kini mencakup metode pengiriman pesanan.
</id>
<it-IT>
3.0:
* L'app ora supporta i rimborsi per importo. È disponibile sulla schermata di dettaglio dell'ordine e ti consente di emettere un rimborso parziale o completo per un ordine pagato.
* I prodotti con immagini multiple ora le mostrano tutte in una galleria.
* Correzione di bug: raramente, il salvataggio sulla schermata per aggiungere una nota dell'ordine causava un arresto anomalo. Ora non accade mai.
* La vista dei dettagli dell'ordine ora comprende il metodo di spedizione dell'ordine.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
3.0:
* アプリで、金額による払い戻しがサポートされるようになりました。注文詳細の画面で、支払い済みの注文の一部または全額を手動で払い戻すことができます。
* 画像が複数ある製品で、すべての画像がギャラリーに表示されるようになりました。
* バグ修正 :まれに「Add Order Note」画面での保存中にクラッシュする問題がありましたが、解決しました。
* 注文詳細ビューに、注文の配送方法が表示されるようになりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
3.0:
* 앱에서 이제 금액별 환불을 지원합니다. 이 기능은 주문 상세 정보 화면에서 사용할 수 있으며 유료 주문에 대해 부분 또는 전액 환불을 수동으로 발행할 수 있습니다.
* 여러 이미지가 있는 제품은 이제 모든 이미지를 갤러리에 표시합니다.
* 버그 수정: "주문 메모 추가" 화면에서 저장할 때 충돌이 거의 발생하지 않습니다. 이제 “거의”가 아닌 “전혀” 발생하지 않게 되었습니다.
* 주문 상세 정보 보기에 이제 주문의 배송 방법이 포함됩니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
3.0:
* De app ondersteunt nu terugbetalingen per bedrag. Deze functie is beschikbaar via het bestelgegevensscherm en hiermee kun je handmatig een gedeeltelijke of volledige terugbetaling voor een betaalde bestelling uitvoeren.
* Bij producten met meerdere afbeeldingen worden alle afbeeldingen nu in één galerij weergegeven.
* Bugfix: Opslaan wanneer het scherm 'Bestelopmerking toevoegen' was geopend, leidde heel af en toe tot een crash. 'Heel af en toe' is nu vervangen door 'Nooit'.
* Het overzicht van bestelgegevens bevat nu ook de verzendmethode.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
3.0:
* Agora o aplicativo oferece reembolsos por valor. Com essa opção, disponível na tela “Detalhes do pedido”, você emite manualmente reembolsos parciais ou totais para pedidos pagos.
* Agora produtos com várias imagens as exibem em uma galeria.
* Correção de bug raro: a tela “Adicionar observação ao pedido” travava durante o salvamento. Não mais.
* Agora a visualização “Detalhes do pedido” inclui o método de envio.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
3.0:
* Приложение теперь поддерживает возврат средств с учетом суммы. Функция доступна на экране с описанием заказа, и она позволяет вручную выполнить частичный или полный возврат средств по оплаченному заказу.
* Все изображения продукта теперь показаны в галерее.
* Исправлена ошибка: в редких случаях сохранение заказа на экране «Добавление примечания к заказу» могло приводить к сбою. Больше этого не случится.
* Экран с описанием заказа теперь включает информацию о способе доставки.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
3.0:
* Appen stöder nu återbetalningar efter belopp. Det finns på din beställningsinformationsskärm och låter dig manuellt utfärda en partiell eller fullständig återbetalning för en betald beställning.
* Produkter med flera bilder visar nu alla bilder i ett galleri.
* Buggkorrigering: Sällan kunde en spara-åtgärd från skärmen Lägg till beställningsanteckning leda till en krasch. Nu har sällan blivit aldrig.
* Beställningsinformationsvyn inkluderar nu beställningens fraktmetod.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
3.0:
* Uygulama artık tutara göre iade yapılmasını destekliyor. Bu özellik, ayrıntı ekranında bulunur ve ödemesi yapılmış bir sipariş için elle kısmi veya tam iade yapmanıza imkan verir.
* Artık birden fazla resme sahip ürünlerin tüm resimleri galeride görüntüleniyor.
* Hata düzeltmesi: “Sipariş Notu Ekle” ekranında yapılan kaydetme işlemi nadiren bir çökmeye yol açıyordu. Bu sorun giderildi.
* Sipariş ayrıntıları görünümünde artık siparişin sevkiyat yöntemi görüntüleniyor.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
3.0：
* 此应用程序现已支持按金额退款。此功能在“订单详细信息”屏幕中可用，可以让您针对已付款的订单手动发起部分或全额退款。
* 带有多张图片的产品现已在图库中显示所有图片。
* 错误修复：在极少数情况下，在“添加订单备注”屏幕上保存内容会导致崩溃。现在，这种情况已不会再发生。
* 订单详细信息视图现已包括订单配送方式。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
3.0：
* 應用程式現在支援依金額退款。你可在訂單詳細資訊畫面使用此功能，並手動為已付款訂單核發部分或全額退款。
* 包含多張圖片的產品現在會以圖庫的方式顯示所有圖片。
* 錯誤修正：儘管極為少見，但過去在「新增訂單備註」畫面進行儲存時有可能導致當機。現在這種情況絕對不會再發生了。
* 訂單詳細資訊檢視畫面現在會顯示訂單運送方式。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
3.0:
* The app now supports refunds by amount. It’s available on the order detail screen, and lets you manually issue a partial or full refund for a paid order.
* Products with multiple images now show all images in a gallery.
* Bug fix: Rarely, the saving while on the “Add Order Note” screen would lead to a crash. Now, “rarely” is “never.”
* The order detail view now includes the order’s shipping method.
</en-US>
