<ar>
7.7:
يمكن للتجار الذين يستخدمون مدفوعات WooCommerce في الولايات المتحدة قبول مدفوعات بطاقات الائتمان الشخصية لسداد مدفوعات عملائك عند التسليم أو طلبات الاستلام. يتضمن هذا الإصدار أيضًا بعض التحسينات الطفيفة استنادًا إلى ملاحظاتك. شكرًا لمساعدتنا على إنشاء تطبيق أفضل للجميع.
</ar>
<de-DE>
7.7:
Händler, die WooCommerce Payments in den USA nutzen, können persönliche Kreditkartenzahlungen für die Zahlungen deiner Kunden bei Zustellung oder Abholung von Bestellungen akzeptieren. Außerdem sind einige kleine, auf deinem Feedback basierenden Verbesserungen in dieser neuen Version enthalten. Vielen Dank, dass du uns dabei hilfst, eine bessere App für alle zu entwickeln.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
7.7:
Los vendedores que utilicen WooCommerce Payments en EE. UU. pueden aceptar pagos en persona mediante tarjeta de crédito para que tus clientes paguen en la entrega o recogida de los pedidos. En esta versión, también se incluyen algunas mejoras pequeñas basadas en tus comentarios. Gracias por ayudarnos a hacer una aplicación mejor para todos.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
7.7 :
Les commerçants qui utilisent WooCommerce Payments aux États-Unis peuvent accepter les paiements en personne par carte de crédit pour les commandes de leurs clients avec paiement à la livraison ou au moment du retrait. Cette version inclut également quelques améliorations mineures basées sur vos commentaires. Merci de nous aider à améliorer l’application pour tout le monde.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
7.7:
סוחרים שמשתמשים ב-WooCommerce Payments בארה"ב יכולים לקבל תשלום באמצעות כרטיסי אשראי באופן אישי מלקוחות שמשלמים במהלך המסירה או האיסוף של ההזמנה. בגרסה הזאת כללנו גם כמה שיפורים קטנים לפי המשוב שקיבלנו מהמשתמשים. תודה שעזרתם לנו לשפר את האפליקציה עבור כולם.
</iw-IL>
<id>
7.7:
Penjual di AS yang menggunakan WooCommerce Payments dapat menerima pembayaran kartu kredit langsung untuk dari pelanggan setelah pengiriman atau penerimaan pesanan. Dalam rilis ini juga disertakan beberapa perbaikan kecil sesuai feedback Anda. Terima kasih telah membantu kami menyempurnakan aplikasi untuk semua orang
</id>
<it-IT>
7.7:
I venditori che usano WooCommerce Payments negli Stati Uniti possono accettare pagamenti con carta di credito di persona per il pagamento alla consegna dei clienti o per gli ordini di ritiro. In questo rilascio sono inclusi anche alcuni miglioramenti minori basati sul tuo feedback. Grazie per averci aiutato a creare un'app migliore per tutti.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
7.7: 
米国で WooCommerce Payments をご利用のマーチャントは、注文品の配送または集荷の際に対面のクレジットカード決済で顧客の支払いを受領できます。 今回のリリースには皆さまからのフィードバックに基づく細かな改善もいくつか含まれています。 アプリの改善にご協力いただきありがとうございます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
7.7:
미국에서 우커머스 결제를 사용하는 판매자는 고객의 주문 배송 또는 수령 시 결제에 대해 대면 신용카드 결제를 수락할 수 있습니다. 피드백에 따라 몇 가지 사소한 부분도 이 릴리스에서 개선했습니다. 모든 사람을 위한 더 좋은 앱을 만들 수 있도록 도와주셔서 감사합니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
7.7:
Verkopers in de VS die gebruikmaken van WooCommerce Payments kunnen fysieke creditcardbetalingen aannemen voor de betalingen van je klanten bij levering of ophaalbestellingen. In deze versie zijn tevens een aantal kleine verbeteringen doorgevoerd, op basis van jullie feedback. Bedankt voor de hulp, zo kunnen we voor iedereen een betere app maken.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
7.7:
Comerciantes que usam o WooCommerce Payments nos EUA podem aceitar pagamentos com cartão de crédito presenciais na entrega ou retirada de pedidos. Esta versão também inclui algumas pequenas melhorias com base no seu feedback. Obrigado por nos ajudar a criar um aplicativo melhor para todos.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
7.7:
Продавцы из США, использующие WooCommerce Payments, могут принимать платежи с кредитных карт в момент, когда клиент получает заказанный товар. Реализованы небольшие улучшения с учётом отзывов пользователей. Благодарим за то, что помогаете совершенствовать приложение.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
7.7:
Handlare som använder WooCommerce Payments i USA kan ta emot personliga betalningar via kreditkort för kundbetalningar vid leverans eller upphämtning. I den här versionen ingår dessutom ett antal mindre förbättringar som är baserade på er feedback. Tack för att ni hjälper oss att skapa en bättre app för alla.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
7.7:
WooCommerce Payments'ı ABD'de kullanan satıcılar, müşterilerinin teslimatta veya siparişleri alırken şahsen kredi kartıyla yapacakları ödemeleri kabul edebilirler. Ayrıca bu sürümde, sizden gelen geri bildirimlere göre gerçekleştirilmiş birkaç küçük iyileştirme de yer almaktadır. Herkes için daha iyi bir uygulama oluşturmamıza yardımcı olduğunuz için teşekkür ederiz.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
7.7：
在美国使用 WooCommerce Payments 的商家可以接受客户在送货或取货时使用信用卡现场付款。 此版本还根据您的反馈进行了几处微小改进。 感谢您为呈现更加出色的应用程序做出的贡献。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
7.7：
在美國使用 WooCommerce Payments 的商家，可以接受客戶在宅配到府或自行取貨時親自刷卡付款。 此版本也改善了一些使用者指出的小問題。 感謝你協助我們打造更完善的應用程式。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
7.7:
Merchants using WooCommerce Payments in the USA can accept in-person credit card payments for your customers’ payment upon delivery or pickup orders. Also included in this release are a few minor improvements based on your feedback. Thanks for helping us make a better app for everyone.
</en-US>
