<ar>
18.2:
في آخر تحديث لدينا، نقوم بتحسين تجربة WooCommerce الخاصة بك! سننتقل من المدفوعات البسيطة إلى تدفق إنشاء الطلبات الأكثر تخصيصًا، ما يتيح لك تعيين المبلغ المطلوب بكل سهولة. إضافة إلى ذلك، يُقدِّم مركز التحليلات المحسَّن لدينا الآن رؤى داخل حزم المنتجات وبطاقات الهدايا، ما يوفر طريقة عرض أكثر شمولاً لإحصاءات أعمالك، نظرًا إلى أن تلك الامتدادات نشطة. استمتع بالترقية!
</ar>
<de-DE>
18.2:
Im Rahmen unseres letzten Updates wird dein WooCommerce-Erlebnis verbessert! Wir wechseln vom einfachen Bezahlen zu einer besser anpassbaren Bestellerstellung und geben dir somit die Möglichkeit, ganz einfach den gewünschten Betrag festzulegen.  In unserem verbesserten Analyse-Hub findest du nun Einsichten zu Produktpaketen und Geschenkkarten. Wenn du diese Erweiterungen aktivierst, profitierst du von einer umfassenderen Übersicht über deine Unternehmensstatistiken. Viel Spaß mit dem Upgrade!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
18.2:
Con nuestra última actualización, mejoramos tu experiencia en WooCommerce. Pasamos de los pagos simples a un flujo de creación de pedidos más personalizado para que puedas establecer fácilmente las cantidades deseadas. Además, la mejora de nuestro Analytics Hub permite ahora ofrecer detalles de los paquetes de productos y tarjetas regalo, ofreciendo una visión más completa de las estadísticas de tu negocio, siempre y cuando tengas activadas estas extensiones. ¡Disfruta de las novedades!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
18.2 :
Avec notre dernière mise à jour, nous améliorons votre expérience WooCommerce ! Nous passons de paiements simplifiés à un flux de création de commande plus personnalisable, vous permettant de définir aisément le montant désiré. Par ailleurs, notre espace statistique fournit désormais des tendances concernant Product Bundles et Gift Cards, ce qui offre un aperçu plus complet de vos statistiques commerciales si ces extensions sont actives. Profitez de cette mise à niveau !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
18.2:
בעדכון האחרון שפורסם, אנחנו משפרים את חוויית השימוש ב-WooCommerce! אנחנו עוברים מ'תשלומים פשוטים' לתהליך יצירה של הזמנות עם אפשרויות נוספות להתאמה אישית כדי לאפשר לך לקבוע את הסכום הרצוי בקלות. בנוסף, אנחנו משפרים את 'מרכז הניתוח הסטטיסטי' כדי לספק תובנות ל-Product Bundles ולשוברי מתנה ולהציע סקירה מקיפה יותר על הנתונים הסטטיסטיים של העסק, אם ההרחבות האלו פעילות. שדרוג נעים שיהיה!
</iw-IL>
<id>
18.2:
Pembaruan terkini kami akan menyempurnakan pengalaman WooCommerce Anda. Kami sedang mengalihkan pembayaran simpel menjadi alur pembuatan pesanan yang lebih mudah disesuaikan agar Anda dapat menetapkan jumlah yang diinginkan tanpa repot. Selain itu, Hub Analitik kami kini menyajikan wawasan seputar Bundel Produk dan Kartu Hadiah sehingga Anda memiliki gambaran yang lebih utuh terkait statistik bisnis Anda, selama ekstensi tersebut aktif. Nikmati upgrade ini!
</id>
<it-IT>
18.2:
Nel nostro ultimo aggiornamento, stiamo migliorando l'esperienza WooCommerce. Stiamo passando dai pagamenti facili a un flusso di creazione degli ordini più personalizzabile, consentendoti di impostare l'importo desiderato in modo semplice. Inoltre, il nostro Analytics Hub aggiornato ora fornisce una panoramica su Product Bundles e Gift Card, offrendo una visione più completa delle statistiche della tua attività, dato che queste estensioni sono attive. Goditi l'aggiornamento.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
18.2:
最新のアップデートでは、WooCommerce の操作環境を強化しています。 シンプルペイメントから、より柔軟にカスタマイズできる注文作成フローに移行しており、希望する金額を簡単に設定できるようになります。 さらに、改良された Analytics Hub では商品パッケージとギフトカードに関する統計概要を確認できるようになりました。これらの拡張機能を有効にすると、より包括的な視点からビジネス統計を見ることができます。 アップデートをぜひご利用ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
18.2:
최신 업데이트에서 우커머스 환경을 강화하고 있습니다! 원하는 금액을 쉽게 설정할 수 있도록 간편한 결제에서 더욱더 사용자 정의 가능한 주문 생성 절차로 전환하고 있습니다. 또는 이제는 개선된 분석 허브에서 상품 번들과 상품권에 대한 인사이트가 제공되므로 해당 확장 기능을 활성화하면 더 포괄적으로 비즈니스 통계를 볼 수 있습니다. 업그레이드를 만끽하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
18.2:
Met onze laatste update verbeteren we je WooCommerce-ervaring! We stappen over van eenvoudige betalingen naar een meer aanpasbare flow voor het aanmaken van bestellingen, waardoor je gemakkelijk het gewenste bedrag kan instellen. Bovendien geeft onze verbeterde Analytics Hub nu inzicht in productbundels en cadeaubonnen, waardoor je een uitgebreider overzicht krijgt van je bedrijfsstatistieken, op voorwaarde dat die extensies actief zijn. Geniet van de upgrade!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
18.2:
Em nossa última atualização, aprimoramos sua experiência no WooCommerce. Estamos trocando os pagamentos simples por um fluxo de criação de pedido mais personalizável para você poder definir facilmente o valor desejado. Além disso, a central de análises agora inclui insights sobre pacotes de produtos e vales-presentes. Assim, você tem uma visão mais abrangente das estatísticas do seu negócio caso essas extensões estejam ativas. Aproveite o upgrade!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
18.2:
Наше очередное обновление позволяет улучшить вашу работу с WooCommerce! Мы переходим от простых платежей к настраиваемому процессу создания заказа, чтобы вам было проще указывать необходимую сумму. Кроме того, теперь вы сможете найти в улучшенном Аналитическом центре данные по комплектам товаров и подарочным картам, активировав эти разрешения. Это даст вам более полное представление о том, как идут дела. Надеемся, вам понравится обновление!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
18.2:
I vår senaste uppdatering har vi förbättrat din WooCommerce-upplevelse. Vi går över från enkla betalningar till ett mer anpassningsbart flöde för beställningsskapande, vilket gör att du enkelt kan ange önskat belopp. Dessutom tillhandahåller vår förbättrade analyshubb nu insikter om produktpaket och presentkort, vilket ger en mer heltäckande bild av din företagsstatistik, förutsatt att dessa utökningar är aktiva. Njut av uppgraderingen.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
18.2:
En yeni güncellememizde WooCommerce deneyiminizi geliştiriyoruz! Basit ödemelerden daha özelleştirilebilir bir sipariş oluşturma akışına geçiş yaparak dilediğiniz tutarı kolaylıkla belirlemenizi sağlıyoruz. Ayrıca iyileştirilmiş Analytics Hub'ımız artık Ürün Paketlerine ve Hediye Kartlarına dair bilgiler sağlayarak bu uzantıların etkin olması halinde işletme istatistikleriniz hakkında daha kapsayıcı bir görünüm sunar. Yükseltmenin keyfini çıkarın!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
18.2：
在最新更新中，我们将进一步完善您的 WooCommerce 使用体验！ 我们正在从简单的付款过渡到可定制化程度更高的订单创建流程，让您可以轻松设置所需的金额。 此外，我们改进后的“分析中心”现在可以提供关于产品捆绑和礼品卡的数据分析，在激活相关扩展程序的情况下，您可更全面地了解您的业务统计信息。 敬请享受本次升级！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
18.2:
我們在最新的更新中，強化你的 WooCommerce 體驗！ 我們正從輕鬆付款功能轉換為可自訂的訂單建立流程，讓你能輕鬆設定所需金額。 此外，我們經強化的 Analytics Hub 現可提供商品搭售方案和禮物卡的洞察報告，只要將相關擴充功能保持啟用，你就能全面檢視企業統計資料。 盡情享受升級功能吧！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
18.2:
In our latest update, we're enhancing your WooCommerce experience! We're transitioning from simple payments to a more customizable order creation flow, enabling you to set the desired amount with ease. Plus, our improved Analytics Hub now provides insights into Product Bundles and Gift Cards, offering a more comprehensive view of your business stats, given those extensions are active. Enjoy the upgrade!
</en-US>
