<ar>
9.0:
تُعد التواريخ بالغة الأهمية عندما تدير نشاطًا تجاريًا! أصلحنا خللاً عند تعيين "تاريخ البيع" على أحد المنتجات – في بعض الأحيان، لم يكن ذلك التاريخ في نهاية المطاف هو ما حدَّدته. ملاحظات المجتمع لنكون الأفضل!
</ar>
<de-DE>
9.0:
Daten sind für Unternehmer enorm wichtig! Wir haben eine Störung beim Festlegen eines „Verkaufsdatums“ bei Produkten behoben – manchmal entsprach das Datum am Ende nicht dem zuvor ausgewählten Datum. Danke für das Feedback der Community!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
9.0:
Las fechas son fundamentales cuando diriges un negocio Hemos solucionado un problema que se producía al establecer la "fecha de venta" en un producto. A veces, la fecha no era la que se había seleccionado. ¡Comentarios de la comunidad para ir a por la victoria!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
9.0 €
Dates are crucial when you’re running a business! We fixed a glitch when setting a “sale date” on a product – sometimes, that date didn’t end up being what you selected. Community feedback for the win!
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
9.0:
כשיש לך עסק, תאריכים זה דבר חשוב! תיקנו בעיה בהגדרה של 'תאריך המבצע' במוצר – לפעמים התאריך שם לא הופיע בהתאם לבחירה שלך. משוב מהקהילה הוא כלי מנצח!
</iw-IL>
<id>
9.0:
Dalam menjalankan usaha, urusan waktu sangatlah penting! Kami sudah memperbaiki gangguan dalam penentuan "tanggal obral" produk. Terkadang, tanggalnya tidak sesuai dengan yang dipilih. Untung ada masukan dari anggota komunitas!
</id>
<it-IT>
9.0:
Le date sono cruciali quando stai gestendo un'attività. Abbiamo risolto uno errore tecnico durante l'impostazione di una "data di vendita" su un prodotto: a volte, quella data non è stata quella selezionata. Il feedback della community per vincere.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
9.0:
ビジネスを営む上で日付はとても重要です。 商品の「販売日」を設定する際に、選択した日付にならないことがある不具合を修正しました。 コミュニティの声はビジネスの成功につながります。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
$9.0
비즈니스를 운영할 때 날짜는 매우 중요합니다. 제품의 “세일 날짜”를 설정할 때 문제가 해결되었습니다. 선택한 날짜와 다를 수 있습니다. 성공을 위한 커뮤니티 피드백!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
9.0:
Datums zijn enorm belangrijk voor het runnen van een bedrijf. We hebben een fout verholpen waarbij bij het instellen van een 'verkoopdatum' op een product soms die datum afweek van de datum die je had gekozen. Bedankt voor jullie feedback!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
9.0:
Datas são essenciais ao gerenciar uma empresa. Por isso, corrigimos uma falha na seleção da data da venda de um produto que fazia com que, às vezes, a data exibida não fosse a selecionada. Ponto para o feedback da comunidade!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
9.0:
При ведении бизнеса важно придерживаться определённых дат. Мы исправили сбой, в результате которого иногда при задании даты продажи товара выбиралась другая дата. Отзывы участников сообщества решают всё!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
9.0:
Datum är viktiga när du driver ett företag. Vi har åtgärdat ett fel som uppstod vid inställningen av ett "säljdatum" för en produkt – ibland stämde datumet som användes inte överens med datumet som valdes. Feedback från vår community är guld värd.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
9.0 dolar
Ticaret yapıyorsanız tarihler çok önemlidir! Bir üründe "indirim tarihi" ayarlarken oluşan bir hatayı düzelttik (bazen seçtiğiniz tarihten başka bir tarih görüntüleniyordu). Kazanmak için topluluk geri bildirimi!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
9.0：
对于公司经营来说，数据至关重要！ 我们修复了设置产品的“销售日期”时出现的一个小问题：该日期有时并不是您所选择的日期。 社区反馈助力我们取得胜利！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
9.0：
營運時，日期是十分關鍵的資訊！ 我們修正了設定產品「銷售日期」時，系統有時最後不會顯示你所選日期的錯誤。 社群意見回饋太有幫助了！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
9.0:
Dates are crucial when you’re running a business! We fixed a glitch when setting a “sale date” on a product – sometimes, that date didn’t end up being what you selected. Community feedback for the win!
</en-US>
