<ar>
7.0:
يُعد إنشاء ملصقات شحن دولية أمرًا سهلاً! يمكن الآن للتجار في الولايات المتحدة الأمريكية الذين يستخدمون شحن وضرائب WooCommerce في مخزنهم إنشاء ملصقات شحن ونماذج مخصصة لجهات الوصول الدولية. مستمرون في إنشاء هذه الميزة – يمكنك تجربتها وأخبرنا كيف تسير الأمور!
</ar>
<de-DE>
7.0:
Das Erstellen internationaler Versandetiketten ist ein Kinderspiel! Verkäufer in den USA, die WooCommerce Shipping & Tax in ihrem Store verwenden, können nun Versandetiketten und Zollformulare für internationale Empfänger erstellen. Wir werden diese Funktion weiter ausbauen – Probiere sie aus und teile uns mit, was du davon hältst!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
7.0:
Crear etiquetas para envíos internacionales es muy fácil. En Estados Unidos, los vendedores que utilizan WooCommerce Shipping & Tax en su tienda ya pueden generar etiquetas de envío y formularios de aduanas para destinos internacionales. Seguimos desarrollando esta función, así que pruébala y cuéntanos que te parece.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
7.0 :
Créer des étiquettes d’expédition internationales est un jeu d’enfant ! Les marchands aux États-Unis qui utilisent WooCommerce Shipping & Tax dans leur boutique peuvent désormais générer des étiquettes d’expédition et des formulaires douaniers pour les destinations internationales. Nous continuons de développer cette fonctionnalité, alors testez-la et donnez-nous votre avis !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
7.0:
יצירת תוויות משלוח בינלאומי היא פעולה קלה ביותר! סוחרים בארה"ב שמשתמשים במשלוחים ובמיסים של WooCommerce בחנות שלהם יכולים כעת לאחסן תוויות משלוח וטופסי מכס ליעדים בינלאומיים. אנחנו ממשיכים לבנות את הכלי הזה - נסו אותו וספרו לנו על ההתנסות שלכם!
</iw-IL>
<id>
7.0:
Membuat label pengiriman internasional kini menjadi mudah! Penjual di Amerika Serikat yang menggunakan WooCommerce Shipping & Tax di tokonya sekarang bisa membuat label pengiriman dan formulir bea cukai untuk tujuan pengiriman internasional. Kami terus mengembangkan fitur ini, jadi silakan dicoba dan sampaikan pengalaman Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
7.0:
Creare etichette di spedizione internazionale è un gioco da ragazzi! I commercianti che utilizzano WooCommerce Shipping & Tax nel proprio negozio negli Stati Uniti possono ora generare etichette di spedizione e moduli doganali per destinazioni internazionali. Stiamo continuando a migliorare questa funzionalità: provala e facci sapere come va.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
7.0:
海外向けの配送ラベルを簡単に作成できます。 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax をストアで使用している米国のマーチャントは、海外向けの配送ラベルや税関申告書を作成できるようになりました。 こちらは現在開発中の機能ですので、お試しいただき、ご意見をいただけますと幸いです。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
7.0:
국제 배송 레이블을 간편하게 만드세요! 스토어에서 WooCommerce 배송 및 세금을 사용하는 미국의 판매자는 이제 해외 목적지에 대한 배송 레이블과 세관 양식을 생성할 수 있습니다. 이 기능을 계속 구축하고 있습니다. 사용해 보고 소감을 말씀해 주세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
7.0:
Het aanmaken van internationale verzendlabels is een fluitje van een cent! Verkopers in de VS die WooCommerce Shipping en Tax voor hun winkel gebruiken, kunnen nu verzendlabels en aangepaste formulieren voor internationale bestemmingen genereren. We zullen deze functionaliteit blijven doorontwikkelen, maar probeer 'm eens uit en laat ons dan weten of alles werkte!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
7.0:
Criar etiquetas de envio internacional é muito simples! Agora comerciantes nos EUA usando o WooCommerce Shipping & Tax em suas lojas podem gerar etiquetas de envio e declarações aduaneiras para destinos internacionais. Ainda estamos aperfeiçoando essa funcionalidade, então experimente-a e diga-nos o que achou!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
7.0:
Моментальное создание международных транспортных этикеток! Продавцы из США, использующие в своих магазинах WooCommerce Shipping & Tax, теперь могут создавать транспортные этикетки и настраиваемые формы для международной пересылки. Мы продолжим работу над этой функцией, а пока можете попробовать ее и оставить отзыв.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
7.0:
Det är enkelt att skapa internationella fraktetiketter! Handlare i USA som använder WooCommerce Shipping & Tax i sin butik kan nu generera fraktetiketter och tullformulär för internationella destinationer. Vi fortsätter att utveckla den här funktionen – prova den och berätta vad du tycker!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
7.0:
Uluslararası kargo etiketleri oluşturmak çok kolay! ABD'deki satıcılar, mağazalarında WooCommerce Shipping & Tax'i kullanarak artık uluslararası destinasyonlar için kargo etiketleri ve gümrük formları oluşturabilir. Bu özelliği geliştirmeye devam ediyoruz. Deneyin ve nasıl çalıştığını bize bildirin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
7.0：
制作国际配送标签简直不费吹灰之力！ 现在，在商店中使用 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 的美国商家可以为国际目的地生成配送标签和报关单。 我们会继续开发这个功能 – 试试吧，看看怎么样！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
7.0：
輕鬆建立國際郵寄標籤！ 在商店中使用 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 的美國商家現在可為國際貨件產生郵寄標籤和海關表格。 我們正在持續改善此功能，歡迎試用並與我們分享心得！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
7.0:
Creating international shipping labels is a breeze! Merchants in the USA using WooCommerce Shipping & Tax in their store can now generate shipping labels and customs forms for international destinations. We’re continuing to build this feature – give it a whirl and let us know how it goes!
</en-US>
