<ar>
17.5:
يسعدنا طرح تحديث جديد رائع يمثِّل قفزتنا الأولى نحو تحسين إدارة الطلبات على الأجهزة اللوحية! يقدِّم هذا التحديث واجهة أكثر أناقة، ما يجعل مهمة إدارة الطلبات أمرًا سهلاً على جهازك اللوحي. انتبه جيدًا لمزيد من التحسينات بينما نواصل العمل لجعل تجربتك أكثر روعة!
</ar>
<de-DE>
17.5:
Wir freuen uns, ein nagelneues Update einführen zu können, das den ersten Schritt zur Verbesserung der Bestellverwaltung auf Tablets einleitet! Dieses Update sorgt für eine übersichtlichere Benutzeroberfläche, mit der die Verwaltung von Bestellungen auf deinem Tablet zum Kinderspiel wird. Halte Ausschau nach weiteren Verbesserungen, denn wir arbeiten ständig daran, dein Erlebnis noch besser zu machen!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
17.5:
Nos emociona lanzar una nueva y resplandeciente actualización que dinamiza nuestro objetivo de mejorar la gestión de pedidos en las tabletas. Esta actualización incluye una interfaz de estilo más profesional, para que gestiones los pedidos en tu tableta antes de contar hasta 3. Mantén los ojos bien abiertos, porque seguiremos trabajando en más mejoras para que tu experiencia sea siempre lo más de lo más.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
17.5 :
Nous sommes ravis de déployer une nouvelle mise à jour qui marque notre premier bond vers la modernisation de la gestion des commandes sur tablette ! Cette mise à jour fluidifie l’interface, faisant de la gestion des commandes sur votre tablette un jeu d’enfant. Gardez les yeux grand ouverts pour découvrir de nouvelles améliorations pendant que nous nous efforçons de rendre votre expérience encore plus cool !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
17.5:
אנחנו שמחים להשיק עדכון חדש ונוצץ שיהיה השלב הראשון בשדרוג חוויית הניהול של הזמנות בטאבלטים! בעדכון הזה הוספנו ממשק חלק יותר, כך שאפשר לנהל הזמנות בקלות רבה דרך הטאבלט. אנחנו עדיין עובדים על שיפורים נוספים כדי ליצור חוויה מגניבה עוד יותר, יש למה לחכות!
</iw-IL>
<id>
17.5:
Inilah pembaruan terkini yang luar biasa untuk memberi sentuhan berbeda pada pengelolaan pesanan Anda di tablet! Pembaruan ini menghadirkan antarmuka yang lebih fungsional agar mengelola pesanan di tablet Anda makin mudah. Jangan lewatkan peningkatan lainnya karena kami terus berupaya menyempurnakan pengalaman Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
17.5
:Siamo entusiasti di presentare un nuovo aggiornamento che rappresenta il nostro primo passo verso una migliore gestione degli ordini su tablet! Con l'aggiornamento arriva un'interfaccia più semplice, che rende la gestione degli ordini su tablet un gioco da ragazzi. Tieni gli occhi aperti in attesa di ulteriori miglioramenti: continuiamo a lavorare per rendere la tua esperienza ancora migliore!
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
17.5:
タブレット端末での注文管理を快適にする試みの第一歩として、すばらしい最新アップデートを公開することをお知らせいたします。 今回のアップデートでは、さらに洗練されたインターフェースを採用し、タブレットで注文を簡単に管理できるようになりました。 今後もますます快適にご利用いただけるよう、機能強化に努めてまいりますので、どうぞご期待ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
17.5:
태블릿의 주문 관리를 더 매력적으로 만드는 첫 번째 도약을 의미하는 빛나는 새 업데이트를 드디어 공개합니다. 이 업데이트를 통해 인터페이스가 깔끔해져 태블릿의 주문 관리 작업이 아주 쉬워집니다. 더 멋진 환경을 위해 계속 노력하고 있으니 더 많은 개선 사항을 지켜봐 주세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
17.5:
We hebben vol trots een schitterende nieuwe update uitgebracht die onze eerste stap markeert naar een nieuw, verfrissend orderbeheermogelijkheid op tablets! Deze update heeft een strakkere interface waardoor het beheer van bestellingen een makkie wordt op je tablet. Houd onze site in de gaten voor meer verbeteringen terwijl we eraan blijven werken om jouw ervaring nog cooler te maken!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
17.5:
Temos o prazer de anunciar esta atualização, que representa nossa primeira iniciativa de otimização de gerenciamento de pedidos em tablets. Ela apresenta uma interface mais elegante, simplificando a tarefa de gerenciamento de pedidos no seu tablet. Fique de olho nas próximas melhorias enquanto continuamos trabalhando para tornar sua experiência ainda mais incrível!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
17.5:
Мы счастливы представить вам новейшее обновление, которое станет первым шагом к тому, чтобы сделать приятным и увлекательным управление заказами с планшетов! В этом обновлении вы найдёте симпатичный интерфейс, который значительно упростит управление заказами с планшета. Следите за появлением новых функций, а мы будем и дальше делать всё для того, чтобы вам было приятно работать с нами.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
17.5:
Vi är glada att kunna presentera en helt ny uppdatering, i vilken vi gör vår första ansats att piffa upp beställningshanteringen på surfplattor. Den här uppdateringen ger ett snyggare gränssnitt, vilket gör uppgiften att hantera beställningar till en barnlek på din surfplatta. Vi fortsätter arbetet med att göra din upplevelse ännu häftigare, så håll ögonen öppna efter fler förbättringar.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
17.5:
Tabletlerde sipariş yönetimini canlandırmaya dair ilk adımımızı gösteren göz alıcı yeni güncellememizi sunmaktan heyecan duyuyoruz! Bu güncelleme, daha çok göze hitap eden bir arayüz getirerek tabletinizde siparişleri yönetme görevini çok kolay hale getirir. Deneyiminizi daha da iyi bir hale getirmeye çalışırken daha fazla geliştirme için gözlerinizi dört açın!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
17.5：
我们很高兴推出一项闪亮的新更新，这标志着我们在不断完善平板电脑上的订单管理功能方面实现了第一次飞跃！ 本次更新带来了更流畅的界面，让您可以在平板电脑上轻松完成订单管理任务。 我们将继续努力为您提供更炫酷的体验，敬请期待更多增强功能！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
17.5:
我們很高興推出全新酷炫更新，首次在平板電腦上推出訂單管理功能！ 此次更新帶來更靈巧的介面，在平板上管理訂單變得輕而易舉。 密切注意更多改善功能，我們會持續為你帶來更酷炫的體驗！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
17.5:
We're thrilled to roll out a shiny new update that marks our first leap towards jazzing up order management on tablets! This update brings a slicker interface, turning the task of managing orders into a breeze on your tablet. Keep your eyes peeled for more enhancements as we keep working to make your experience even cooler!
</en-US>
