<ar>
4.1:
* أضفنا لمسة جديدة من الألوان على التطبيق — استمتع بالألوان الجديدة!
* يتوافر الآن الوضع الداكن لأي شخص يُفضِّل استخدام الشاشات ذات درجات السطوع الأقل.
* أزلنا قسم الشحن من عرض تفاصيل المنتجات الافتراضية (لأنَّك لا تشحنها).
* إذا كانت لديك قائمة منتجات أصغر، فإن العناصر ستختفي منها أحيانًا، ولكن ليس بعد الآن لأنَّنا أصلحنا ذلك الخطأ.
* ستؤدي محاولة عرض تفاصيل أحد المنتجات إلى تعطُّل التطبيق، وذلك في حالات نادرة جدًا. أصلحنا ذلك الخطأ كذلك.
</ar>
<de-DE>
4.1:
* Unsere App hat einen neuen Look bekommen – wir hoffen, dir gefallen die Farben!
* Der dunkle Modus ist jetzt für alle verfügbar, die einen dunkleren Bildschirm bevorzugen.
* Wir haben bei der Detailansicht deiner virtuellen Produkte den Abschnitt zum Versand entfernt, da du diese ja nicht per Post verschickst.
* Auf kleineren Produktlisten sind manchmal Artikel verschwunden – diesen Fehler haben wir behoben.
* Manchmal ist beim Anklicken der Detailansicht die App abgestürzt – auch diesen Fehler haben wir behoben.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
4.1:
* Le hemos dado una mano de pintura a la app. ¡Disfrútalo!
* El modo Oscuro ya está aquí para los que prefieren pantallas menos brillantes.
* Hemos eliminado la sección Envío de la vista de detalles de los productos virtuales (básicamente, porque no se envían)
* Si tenías una lista de productos pequeña, a veces los artículos desaparecían. Ya no, lo hemos solucionado.
* En muy raras ocasiones, al intentar ver los detalles de un producto la aplicación se bloqueaba. También lo hemos solucionado.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
4.1 :
* De nouvelles couleurs apportent du peps à l'application !
* Tous les utilisateurs préférant un écran moins lumineux peuvent désormais utiliser le mode sombre.
* Nous avons supprimé la section Expédition de la vue détaillée des produits virtuels (étant donné que vous n'en expédiez pas).
* Dans les listes de produits plus petites, certains articles disparaissaient parfois. Cela n'arrivera plus, ce bug ayant été résolu.
* La tentative d'affichage des détails d'un produit entraînait l'arrêt de l'application en de très rares occasions. Nous avons également résolu ce bug.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
4.1:
* צבענו מחדש את האפליקציה – מקווים שהצבעים החדשים ימצאו חן בעיניך!
* המצב הכהה כעת זמין לכל המשתמשים שמעדיפים מסכים בהירים פחות.
* הסרנו את המקטע 'משלוח' מתצוגת הפרטים במוצרים וירטואלים (כי לא באמת שולחים אותם).
* אם רשימת המוצרים שלך קצרה יחסית, לפעמים נעלמו ממנה פריטים אבל אל חשש – תיקנו את הבאג.
* במקרים נדירים מאוד, האפליקציה הייתה קורסת כאשר ניסו להציג את הפריטים של המוצר. תיקנו גם את הבאג הזה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
4.1:
* Kami baru saja memberikan lapisan cat yang baru untuk aplikasi — nikmati warna barunya!
* Mode gelap kini tersedia bagi yang lebih menyukai layar redup.
* Kami menghilangkan bagian Pengiriman dari tampilan detail produk virtual (karena, ya, memang Anda tidak mengirimnya).
* Jika Anda memiliki daftar produk yang lebih kecil, terkadang item menghilang dari daftar, tetapi sekarang tidak akan lagi — kami telah memperbaiki bug tersebut.
* Di saat-saat tertentu, mencoba menampilkan detail produk dapat menyebabkan crash pada aplikasi. Kami juga telah memperbaiki bug tersebut.
</id>
<it-IT>
4.1:
*Abbiamo appena rinfrescato all'app. Goditi i nuovi colori!
*Dark mode è ora disponibile per chi preferisce schermi meno luminosi.
*Rimossa la sezione Spedizione dalla visualizzazione dei dettagli dei prodotti virtuali (perché, beh, non li spedisci).
*In un elenco di prodotti ridotto, gli articoli a volte scomparivano da esso, ora non più: bug risolto.
*In rare occasioni, il tentativo di visualizzare i dettagli di un prodotto provocava l'arresto anomalo dell'app. Abbiamo risolto anche quel bug.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
4.1:
* アプリの外観が新しくなりました — 新しい色をお楽しみください !
* 明るくない画面を好む人はダークモードを利用できるようになりました。
* バーチャル商品の詳細ビューから「配送」セクションを削除しました (配送の必要がないため)。
* 商品リストが小さい場合、項目がリストに表示されないことがありましたが、表示されるようになりました。このバグを修正しました。
* ごくまれに、商品の詳細を表示しようとすると、アプリがクラッシュすることがありました。このバグも修正しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
4.1:
* 새로운 색상으로 앱 분위기를 바꾸었습니다. 지금 확인해 보세요!
* 이제 많이 밝지 않은 화면을 선호하는 사람 누구나 어둡게 모드를 이용할 수 있습니다.
* 해당 제품을 배송하지 않기 때문에 가상 제품의 세부정보 보기에서 배송 섹션을 제거했습니다.
* 제품 목록이 상대적으로 작은 경우 경우에 따라 아이템이 사라지는 경우가 있었으나 버그를 수정하여 더 이상 해당 문제가 발생하지 않습니다.
* 매우 드물지만 제품의 세부정보를 보려고 하면 앱이 중단되는 현상이 발생했습니다. 이 버그도 수정했습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
4.1:
* We hebben de kleuren van de app vernieuwd: geniet ervan!
* De nachtmodus is nu beschikbaar voor iedereen die behoefte heeft aan een minder fel scherm.
* We hebben het gedeelte Verzending verwijderd uit het detail-overzicht van virtuele producten (omdat je ze natuurlijk niet verzendt).
* Als je een kleinere productlijst hebt, werden sommige artikelen er soms uit verwijderd, maar nu niet meer, want die bug is opgelost.
* Heel af en toe vond er een crash van de app plaats wanneer de details van een product werden bekeken. Die bug hebben we ook opgelost.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
4.1:
* Acabamos de dar uma nova cara ao app. Aproveite as novas cores!
* Para quem prefere telas mais escuras, disponibilizamos o modo noturno.
* Removemos a seção Envio da visualização de detalhes dos produtos virtuais (porque não precisam ser enviados, né).
* Os produtos às vezes desapareciam das listas menores, mas agora já resolvemos esse problema.
* Em algumas ocasiões, tentar ver os detalhes de um produto travava o aplicativo. Consertamos esse problema também.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
4.1:
* Мы освежили цветовую гамму — оцените новые цвета!
* Темная тема оформления теперь доступна для тех, кто предпочитает умеренную яркость.
* Мы убрали раздел «Отгрузки» для виртуальных продуктов (потому что они не «отгружаются»).
* В небольших списках продукты могли иногда пропадать, но больше этого происходить не будет — ошибка исправлена.
* В очень редких случаях просмотр деталей товара приводил к сбою приложения. Эта ошибка тоже исправлена.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
4.1:
* Vi har just gett appen ett nytt lager färg — njut av de nya färgerna!
* Mörkt läge är nu tillgängligt för alla som föredrar mindre ljusa skärmar.
* Vi har tagit bort avsnittet Frakt från detaljvyn för virtuella produkter (eftersom de inte skickas).
* Om du hade en mindre produktlista kunde det ibland försvinna objekt från den, men så är inte längre fallet — vi har åtgärdat det felet.
* I mycket sällsynta fall kraschade appen om man försökte visa den detaljerade informationen för en produkt. Vi har åtgärdat det felet också.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
4.1:
* Uygulamaya yepyeni renkler kazandırdık - yeni renklerin keyfini çıkarın.
* Artık daha az parlak ekranları tercih eden herkes Karanlık modu kullanılabilir.
* Sanal ürünlerin ayrıntı görünümünden Gönderim bölümünü kaldırdık (çünkü onlar gönderilmez).
* Daha küçük bir ürün listeniz olduğunda öğeler bazen listeden kaybolurdu, ancak artık değil. Bu hata düzeltildi.
* Çok nadir durumlarda, bir ürünün ayrıntılarını görüntülemeye çalışmak uygulamanın çökmesine neden olurdu. Bu hata da düzeltildi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
4.1：
* 我们刚刚为应用程序添加了新颜色，快来体验新颜色！
* 现已面向偏爱弱光屏幕的用户推出夜间模式。
* 我们已从虚拟产品的详细信息视图中删除了“配送”部分（因为虚拟产品无需配送）。
* 如果您的产品列表较小，某些商品有时会从列表中消失，那么现在不会了，我们修复了该错误。
* 在极少数情况下，尝试查看产品详细信息会导致应用程序崩溃，我们也修复了该错误。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
4.1：
* 我們為應用程式加入全新配色，盡情享受全新色彩設計！
* 深色模式現已推出，適合偏好將螢幕調暗的使用者選用。
* 我們從虛擬產品的詳細資訊檢視畫面中移除了「送貨」區段 (因為虛擬產品不需要送貨選項)。
* 產品清單較小時，有時某些項目會消失不見；我們現已修復此錯誤，不會再有這個問題了。
* 在極少數情況下，嘗試查看產品的詳細資訊會導致應用程式當機。這個錯誤也已修正。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
4.1:
* We just gave the app a fresh coat of paint — enjoy the new colors!
* Dark mode is now available for anyone who prefers less-bright screens.
* We removed the Shipping section from virtual products’ detail view (because, well, you don’t ship them).
* If you have a smaller product list, items would sometimes disappear from it, but not anymore — we fixed that bug.
* On very rare occasions, attempting to view the details of a product would crash the app. We fixed that bug, too.
</en-US>
