<ar>
4.0:
* متحمسون لتقديم علامة تبويب المنتجات!
* لدى المستخدمين الآن إمكانات تحرير محدودة للمنتجات البسيطة كذلك، انتظروا المزيد في المستقبل.
</ar>
<de-DE>
4.0:
* Wir freuen uns, den Tab „Produkte“ vorzustellen!
* Zusätzlich haben Benutzer jetzt begrenzte Bearbeitungsfunktionen für einfache Produkte, mehr Funktionen in Kürze.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
4.0:
* Te presentamos la nueva pestaña Productos.
* Ahora, los usuarios también tienen funciones de edición limitadas en productos sencillos, y se irán añadiendo más.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
4.0 :
* Nous sommes heureux de vous présenter l’onglet Produits !
* Les utilisateurs ont aussi pour l’instant des fonctions d’édition limitées pour les produits simples. Des fonctions supplémentaires seront bientôt ajoutées.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
4.0:
* אנחנו שמחים להציג לכם את הלשונית החדשה 'מוצרים'!
* למשתמשים יש כעת גם יכולות עריכה מוגבלות במוצרים פשוטים, אפשרויות נוספות יפורסמו בעתיד.
</iw-IL>
<id>
4.0:
* Dengan senang hati kami memperkenalkan tab Produk!
* Sekarang pengguna juga memiliki kemampuan penyuntingan terbatas untuk Produk Sederhana, dengan lebih banyak fitur di pembaruan mendatang.
</id>
<it-IT>
4.0:
*Siamo entusiasti di introdurre la scheda Prodotti.
*Gli utenti hanno ora opzioni di modifica limitate per i prodotti semplici, con altre in arrivo.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
4.0:
* 「商品」タブが導入されました !
* シンプルな商品に制限付きの編集機能が加わりました。今後も追加される予定です。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
4.0:
* 제품 탭을 소개하게 되어 기쁩니다!
* 이제 사용자는 간편 제품에 대한 편집 기능이 제한되어 있으며, 앞으로 더 많은 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
4.0:
* We kondigen met trots een Producten-tabblad aan!
* Gebruikers kunnen nu ook beperkte bewerkingsfuncties voor eenvoudige producten gebruiken en later zullen er meer volgen.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
4.0:
* Estamos felizes em apresentar a guia Produtos!
* Agora os usuários têm recursos de edição limitados para produtos simples, e tem muito mais a caminho.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
4.0:
* Представляем вкладку "Продукты"!
* Теперь пользователям доступны некоторые возможности редактирования обычных продуктов, а скоро они будут расширены.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
4.0:
* Vi är glada att kunna introducera en Produkter-flik!
* Användare har nu även begränsade redigeringsmöjligheter för Enkla produkter. Mer kommer.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
4.0:
* Ürünler sekmesini tanıtmaktan memnuniyet duyuyoruz!
* Kullanıcılar artık Basit Ürünler için sınırlı düzenleme yetkilerine sahip olacak, zamanla daha fazlası da gelecek.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
4.0：
* 隆重推出“产品”选项卡！
* 此外，用户现在对简单产品已有有限的编辑能力，未来还会有更多。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
4.0：
* 我們很高興推出「產品」分頁！
* 使用者現在也能對「簡易產品」使用有限編輯功能，之後會推出更多功能。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
4.0:
* We’re excited to introduce a Products tab!
* Users also now have limited editing capabilities for Simple Products, with more to come.
* We fixed a date-conversion bug that was hiding some orders and grouping others incorrectly.
</en-US>
