<ar>
12.6:
هل كنت على دراية بأنه يمكنك إنشاء طلب من التطبيق؟ أجرينا بعض التحسينات على إنشاء الطلبات لجعل تجربتك أكثر سلاسة. يرجى الاستمرار في إرسال ملاحظاتك! حيث إننا نقرأها كلها!
</ar>
<de-DE>
12.6:
Hast du gewusst, dass du über die App Bestellungen erstellen kannst? Wir haben bei der Erstellung von Bestellungen ein paar Verbesserungen am Gesamterlebnis vorgenommen. Sende uns bitte weiterhin dein Feedback! Wir lesen alle Einsendungen.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
12.6:
¿Sabías que puedes crear un pedido desde la aplicación? Hemos corregido algunos errores y realizado varias mejoras para que tu experiencia sea más fluida. Sigue enviándonos tus comentarios. Los leemos todos.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
12.6 :
Saviez-vous que vous pouviez créer une commande dans l’application ? Nous avons apporté quelques améliorations à la création de commandes pour optimiser votre expérience. Continuez de nous donner votre avis ! Nous les lisons tous !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
12.6:
Did you know you can create an order from the app? תיקנו כמה באגים והוספנו כמה שיפורים כדי לאפשר חוויית שימוש טובה יותר. נשמח להמשיך לקבל משוב! אנחנו קוראים כל משוב שאנחנו מקבלים!
</iw-IL>
<id>
12.6:
Sudah tahu kalau pesanan bisa dibuat dari aplikasi? Untuk itu, kami menghadirkan sejumlah penyempurnaan agar proses pembuatan pesanan jadi lebih lancar. Terus kirimkan feedback Anda! Kami membaca semuanya!
</id>
<it-IT>
12.6:
Sapevi che puoi creare un ordine dall'app? Abbiamo apportato alcuni miglioramenti alla creazione degli ordini per rendere la tua esperienza più fluida. Continua a inviarci il tuo feedback. Li leggiamo uno a uno.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
12.6:
アプリから注文を作成できることをご存知でしたか ? 体験がスムーズになるよう注文作成機能への改善をいくつか行いました。 引き続き皆さまのご意見をお待ちしております。 よろしくお願いいたします。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
12.6:
앱에서 주문을 생성할 수 있다는 것을 알고 계셨나요? 더 원활하게 경험할 수 있도록 몇 가지 개선 사항을 주문 생성에 적용했습니다. 피드백을 계속 보내주세요! 하나하나 읽어보고 있습니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
12.6:
Wist je al dat je direct vanuit de app een bestelling kan aanmaken? We hebben wat bugs verholpen en verschillende verbeteringen aangebracht om je ervaring nog soepeler te maken. Blijf ons voorzien van feedback! We lezen alles!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
12.6:
Sabia que você pode criar um pedido pelo aplicativo? Fizemos algumas melhorias na criação de pedidos para melhorar sua experiência. Continue enviando seu feedback. Lemos cada um deles!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
12.6:
Вы знали, что заказ можно создать прямо в приложении? Мы усовершенствовали процесс создания заказа, чтобы повысить удобство работы. Продолжайте отправлять нам отзывы! Мы всё читаем.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
12.6:
Visste du att du kan skapa en beställning från appen? Vi har gjort några förbättringar av beställningsskapandet för att göra din upplevelse smidigare. Fortsätt att skicka feedback. Vi läser allt.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
12.6:
Uygulamadan sipariş oluşturabileceğinizi biliyor muydunuz? Deneyiminizi daha sorunsuz hale getirmek için sipariş oluşturmayla ilgili birkaç iyileştirme yaptık. Lütfen geri bildirimlerinizi göndermeye devam edin! Her birini okuyoruz!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
12.6：
您知道吗？您可以通过应用程序创建订单。 我们对订单创建进行了一些改进，致力于让您的体验更加流畅。 请继续发送您的反馈意见！ 我们会阅读每一条反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
12.6：
你知道嗎？你可以從應用程式建立訂單。 我們改善了建立訂單的幾個問題，讓你的體驗更流暢。 請持續提供意見回饋給我們！ 我們會讀過每一則留言！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
12.6:
Did you know you can create an order from the app? We made a few improvements to order creation to make your experience smoother. Please keep sending your feedback! We read every one of them!
</en-US>
