<ar>
4.3:
يمكنك تصفية المنتجات وفرزها من علامة تبويب "المنتجات".
* يظهر تعقب الشحنة على شاشة تفاصيل الطلب. تظهر الطلبات ذات التواريخ اللاحقة على علامة تبويب "كل الطلبات".
* وظائفنا الجديدة لتحرير المنتجات قيد التجريب. جرّبه!
* تم إصلاح العديد من الأعطال ولون النص في تذاكر الدعم في الوضع الداكن.
</ar>
<de-DE>
4.3:
* Im Produkte-Tab kannst du Produkte filtern und sortieren.
* Die Sendungsverfolgung wird auf dem Bildschirm mit den Auftragsdetails angezeigt. Bestellungen mit einem Datum in der Zukunft werden im Tab „Alle Bestellungen“ angezeigt.
* Unsere neue Produktbearbeitungsfunktion ist als Betaversion verfügbar. Probiere sie aus!
* Wir haben mehrere Gründe für Abstürze und die Textfarbe auf den Support-Tickets im dunklen Modus behoben.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
4.3:
* Filtra y ordena productos desde la pestaña Productos.
* El seguimiento de envío se muestran en la pantalla de detalles del pedido. Los pedidos con fecha posterior a la actual se muestran en la pestaña Todos los pedidos.
* La funcionalidad de edición de productos está disponible en versión beta. ¡Pruébala!
* Hemos corregido muchos problemas, así como el color del texto de las incidencias en modo oscuro.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
4.3 :
* Filtrez et triez les produits à partir de l'onglet Produits.
* Le suivi de l'expédition apparaît sur l'écran des détails de la commande. Les commandes à venir apparaissent dans l'onglet Toutes les commandes.
* Notre nouvelle fonctionnalité de modification des produits est en phase bêta. Essayez-la !
* Résolution de plusieurs défaillances et d'un problème lié à la couleur du texte sur les billets d'assistance en mode sombre.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
4.3:
* ניתן לסנן ולמיין מוצרים מהלשונית 'מוצרים'.
* מעקב המשלוח מופיע במסך של פרטי ההזמנה. הזמנות עם תאריך עתידי יופיעו בלשונית 'כל ההזמנות'.
* אפשרות העריכה החדשה שלנו למוצרים נמצאת בגרסת הביתא. ניתן לנסות אותה כעת!
* תיקנו מספר קריסות ואת צבע הטקסט בכרטיסי תמיכה במצב הכהה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
4.3:
* Menyaring dan mengurutkan Produk dari tab Produk.
* Pelacakan pengiriman muncul di layar detail pesanan. Pesanan di tanggal yang akan datang muncul di tab Semua pesanan.
* Fungsionalitas penyuntingan produk baru kami sedang dalam tahap beta. Cobalah!
* Memperbaiki beberapa error yang menimbulkan crash dan warna teks di tiket dukungan pada mode gelap.
</id>
<it-IT>
4.3:
*Filtro e ordine per prodotto dalla scheda Prodotti.
*La tracciabilità della spedizione viene visualizzata sulla schermata dei dettagli dell'ordine. Gli ordini con data futura vengono visualizzati nella scheda Tutti gli ordini.
*La nuova funzionalità di modifica del prodotto è in fase beta. Provala!
*Risolti più arresti anomali e il colore del testo sui ticket di supporto in Dark Mode.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
4.3:
* 「商品」タブから商品を絞り込んで並べ替えます。
* 配送状況の追跡は注文詳細の画面に表示されます。将来の日付に設定した注文はすべての注文タブに表示されます。
* 新商品の編集機能はベータ版です。お試しください !
* 複数のクラッシュと、ダークモードでのサポートチケットのテキストカラーを修正しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
4.3:
* 제품 탭에서 제품을 필터링하고 정렬합니다.
* 주문 세부정보 화면에 선적 추적 정보가 나타납니다. 향후 주문은 모든 주문 탭에 나타납니다.
* 새로운 제품 편집 기능은 베타 버전입니다. 사용해 보세요!
* 어두운 모드에서 지원 티켓의 여러 가지 충돌 문제 및 텍스트 색상이 수정되었습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
4.3:
* Filter en sorteer producten vanuit het Producten-tabblad.
* Verzending bijhouden wordt weergegeven op het scherm met bestelgegevens. Bestellingen met een toekomstige datum worden weergegeven op het tabblad Alle bestellingen.
* Onze nieuwe productbewerkingsfunctie heeft de bèta-fase bereikt. Probeer hem nu zelf!
* Verschillende problemen met crashes opgelost en de tekstkleur op support-tickets in de nachtmodus.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
4.3:
* Opções de filtro e classificação na guia Produtos.
* Monitoramento de envio exibido na tela Detalhes do pedido. Pedidos futuros exibidos na guia Todos os pedidos.
* Experimente a versão Beta da nova funcionalidade de edição de produtos.
* Correção de várias falhas e da cor de texto em tíquetes de suporte no modo escuro.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Версия 4.3:
* Возможности фильтрования и сортировки продуктов на вкладке "Товары".
* Отслеживание посылки доступно на экране сведений о заказе. Заказы на будущие даты можно посмотреть на вкладке “Все заказы”.
* Новая функция редактирования товаров находится в стадии бета-тестирования. Попробуйте ее!
* Исправлено несколько ошибок, приводящих к сбою приложения, а также цвет текста запросов в службу поддержки в тёмном режиме.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
4.3:
* Filtrera och sortera produkter från fliken Produkter.
* Leveransspårning visas på orderinformationsskärmen. Framtidsdaterade order visas på fliken Alla order.
* Vår nya funktion för produktredigering är en betaversion. Testa den!
* Fixade flera krascher och textfärgen på supportärenden i mörkt läge.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
4.3:
* Ürünler sekmesinden Ürünleri filtreleyin ve sıralayın.
* Sipariş ayrıntıları ekranında gönderim takibi görünüyor. Gelecek tarihli siparişler Tüm siparişler sekmesinde görünüyor.
* Yeni ürün düzenleme işlevimiz beta sürümünde. Bir deneyin!
* Karanlık modda destek biletleriyle ilgili birden çok kilitlenme hatası ve metin rengi düzeltildi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
4.3：
* 从“产品”选项卡中对产品进行过滤和排序。
* 订单详情屏幕上显示发货跟踪。“所有订单”选项卡上显示日期在未来的订单。
* 我们的新产品编辑功能目前为测试版。不妨试试吧！
* 修复了多个崩溃问题，以及深色模式下的支持申请单文本颜色问题。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
4.3：
* 從產品分頁篩選和排序產品。
* 訂單詳細資訊畫面會顯示送貨追蹤功能。「所有訂單」分頁會顯示未來日期的訂單。
* 我們推出測試版產品編輯功能。立即試用！
* 修復多個當機問題，並修正深色模式中支援聯絡單的文字顏色。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
4.3:
* Filter and sort Products from the Products tab.
* Shipment tracking appears on the order detail screen. Future-dated orders appear on the All orders tab.
* Our new product editing functionality is in beta. Try it!
* Fixed multiple crashes and the text color on support tickets in dark mode.
</en-US>
