<ar>
4.8:
* تم تحديث قسم "إضافة تعقُّب الشحنة" لعرضه فقط في حالة توافر إضافة تعقُّب الشحنة
* تم إصلاح عطل كان يحدث عند النقر المزدوج على عنصر التنقل، وعطل آخر (نادر) ناتج عن محاولة إخفاء العرض غير النشط.

</ar>
<de-DE>
4.8:
* Bereich „Sendungsverfolgung hinzufügen“ aktualisiert, sodass er nur noch angezeigt wird, wenn das Sendungsverfolgungs-Plugin vorhanden ist.
* Absturz beim Doppeltippen auf ein Navigationselement und ein weiterer (seltener) Absturz beim Verbergen einer nicht aktiven Anzeige behoben.

</de-DE>
<es-ES>
4.8:
* Se ha actualizado la sección "Add shipment tracking" (Añadir seguimiento de envío) a la sección para que se muestre únicamente si está disponible el plugin Shipment Tracking (Seguimiento de envío).
* Se ha solucionado un fallo que se producía al tocar dos veces un elemento de navegación y otro (en raras ocasiones) que se producía al intentar ocultar una vista no activa.

</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
4.8 :
* Mise à jour de la section « Ajouter le suivi de l’expédition » pour qu’elle ne s’affiche que si l’extension Suivi de l’expédition est disponible.
* Résolution d’un problème en effectuant un double-clic sur un élément de navigation et d’un autre (rare) problème causé par la tentative de masquer une vue non active.

</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
4.8:
* עדכנו את המקטע 'להוסיף מעקב אחר משלוח' כדי שיוצג רק כאשר התוסף של מעקב המשלוח זמין.
* תיקנו קריסה שהתרחשה בהקשה כפולה על אלמנט ניווט ועוד קריסה (נדירה) שנגרמה בניסיון להסתיר תצוגה לא פעילה.

</iw-IL>
<id>
4.8:
* Bagian “Tambah pelacakan pengiriman” diperbarui sehingga hanya tampil jika plugin Pelacakan Pengiriman tersedia.
* Crash saat mengetuk dua kali elemen navigasi dan crash lainnya akibat menyembunyikan tampilan non-aktif (jarang terjadi) diperbaiki.

</id>
<it-IT>
4.8:
* Sezione per aggiungere la tracciabilità della spedizione aggiornata per essere mostrata solo se il plugin Tracciabilità della spedizione è disponibile.
* Risolto un arresto anomalo che si verificava toccando due volte un elemento di navigazione e un altro (raro) arresto anomalo causato dal tentativo di nascondere una vista non attiva.

</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
4.8:
* 配送追跡プラグインが利用できる場合のみ「配送追跡を追加」セクションが表示されるように変更。
* ナビゲーション要素をダブルタップした際に発生するクラッシュ、およびアクティブになっていないビューを非表示にしようとすると (稀に) 発生するクラッシュを修正。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
4.8:
"배송 추적 추가" 섹션이 배송 추적 플러그인을 사용하는 경우에만 표시되도록 업데이트했습니다.
* 탐색 요소를 두 번 누를 때 발생하는 충돌과 활성화되지 않은 화면을 숨기려고 할 때 발생하는 (드문) 충돌을 해결했습니다.

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
4.8:
* Het gedeelte 'Verzending bijhouden toevoegen' is bijgewerkt om alleen de Shipment Tracking-plugin te laten zien als deze beschikbaar is.
* Een crash na het dubbeltikken op een navigatie-element en nog een (zeldzame) crash veroorzaakt door het proberen verbergen van een non-actief overzicht zijn opgelost.

</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
4.8:
* Seção "Adicionar rastreamento de envio" atualizada para ser exibida somente se o plugin Shipment Tracking estiver disponível.
* Correção de falha causada ao dar dois cliques em um elemento de navegação, e de uma falha (rara) causada ao tentar ocultar uma visualização não ativa.

</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
4.8:
* Обновлен раздел «Добавить отслеживание заказов», который теперь отображается, только если доступен плагин отслеживания.
* Исправлена ошибка, из-за которой возникал сбой при двойном нажатии на элементы навигации, а также еще одна (редкая) ошибка, происходившая при попытке скрыть неактивные представления.

</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
4.8:
* Avsnittet "Lägg till leveransspårning" uppdaterades så att det endast visas om tillägget Leveransspårning är tillgängligt.
* En krasch som uppstod vid dubbeltryck på ett navigationselement och en annan (sällsynt) krasch som uppstod vid försök att dölja en icke-aktiv vy åtgärdades.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
4,8:
* "Gönderi takibi ekle" bölümü yalnızca Gönderi Takibi eklentisi mevcutsa görüntülenecek şekilde güncellendi.
* Bir gezinme öğesine çift dokunulduğunda yaşanan kilitlenme ile, etkin olmayan bir görünümü gizlemeye çalışırken oluşan başka bir (nadir) kilitlenme sorunu düzeltildi.

</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
4.8:
* 更新了“添加配送跟踪”部分，以仅在 Shipment Tracking 插件可用时显示。
* 修复了双击导航元素时出现的崩溃问题，以及因尝试隐藏非活动视图导致的另一个（极少出现）崩溃问题。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
4.8：
* 更新「新增貨件追蹤」區段，只有安裝「貨件追蹤」外掛程式時才會顯示此區段。
* 修復按兩下導覽元素時發生的當機問題，以及嘗試隱藏非使用中檢視畫面而導致的其他 (少見) 當機情況 。

</zh-TW>
<en-US>
4.8:
* Updated the “Add shipment tracking” section to display only if the Shipment Tracking plugin is available.
* Fixed a crash when double-tapping a navigation element, and another (rare) crash caused by trying to hide a non-active view.
 
</en-US>
