<ar>
11.8: يمكنك الآن الرّدّ على مراجعات المنتج مباشرة من التطبيق! يتضمن هذا التحديث أيضًا العديد من التحسينات على متغيرات المنتج وميزة التحليلات. يرجى مشاركة ملاحظاتك - وسنقرأ كل المشاركات واحدة واحدة.
</ar>
<de-DE>
11.8:
Du kannst jetzt direkt in der App auf Produktrezensionen antworten! Dieses Update beinhaltet außerdem einige Verbesserungen bei Produktvariationen und der Analysefunktion. Bitte teile dein Feedback mit uns – wir lesen jeden einzelnen Kommentar.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
11.8:
¡Ahora puedes responder a las reseñas de los productos directamente desde la aplicación! Esta actualización incluye también varias mejoras en las variaciones de los productos y en las estadísticas. No dudes en compartir tus opiniones, leemos todas y cada una de ellas.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
11.8 :
Vous pouvez désormais répondre aux avis des produit directement depuis l'application ! Cette mise à jour comprend également plusieurs améliorations des variantes de produits et de la fonction d'analyse. Partagez vos commentaires, nous les lisons tous !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
11.8: מעכשיו אפשר לענות לביקורות על מוצרים ישירות מהאפליקציה! עדכון זה כולל גם מספר שיפורים לווריאציות של מוצרים ותכונת הניתוח. אנא שתפו משוב - אנו קוראים כל אחד מהם.
</iw-IL>
<id>
11.8:
Sekarang Anda dapat membalas ulasan produk langsung dari aplikasi! Pembaruan ini juga mencakup beberapa peningkatan pada variasi produk dan fitur analitik. Silakan bagikan feedback Anda – kami membaca semuanya.
</id>
<it-IT>
Adesso puoi rispondere alle recensioni dei prodotti direttamente dall'app! Questo aggiornamento include anche vari miglioramenti alle funzionalità di variazione del prodotto ed analisi. Continua a inviarci il tuo feedback; ci aiuta a capire su cosa lavorare in futuro.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
11.8:
商品レビューに対して、アプリから直接返信できるようになりました。このアップデートでは、製品のバリエーションと分析機能にも改良を加えました。ぜひフィードバックをお寄せください。頂いたご意見にはすべて目を通しています。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
11.8:
이제 바로 앱에서 제품 리뷰에 답변할 수 있습니다! 이번 업데이트에는 여러 제품과 분석 기능에 대한 몇 가지 개선도 포함됩니다. 피드백을 공유해주세요 – 모두 꼼꼼히 읽어보겠습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
11.8: Je kan nu rechtstreeks vanuit de app reageren op productrecensies! Deze update bevat ook verschillende verbeteringen aan de productvariaties en de analysefunctie. Deel je feedback - we lezen ze allemaal.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
11.8:
Agora você pode responder a avaliações de produtos diretamente no app! Esta atualização também inclui várias melhorias nas variações do produto e no recurso de análise. Compartilhe seu feedback, nós lemos cada um deles.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
11.8:
Вы можете отвечать на обзоры товара прямо через приложение! Это обновление также включает в себя несколько улучшений функций вариативности товаров и аналитики. Пожалуйста, поделитесь вашим отзывом — мы читаем все поступившие сообщения.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
11.8:
Du kan nu svara på produktrecensioner direkt från appen! Denna uppdatering innehåller också flera förbättringar av produktvarianter och analysfunktionen. Dela gärna feedback – vi läser var och en av dem.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
11.8:
Artık ürün yorumlarına doğrudan uygulamadan yanıt verebilirsiniz! Bu güncellemede ayrıca ürün çeşitlerinde ve istatistiklerde pek çok iyileştirmeye gittik. Lütfen geri bildirimlerinizi bizimle paylaşın, hepsini okuyoruz.↵
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
11.8:
您现在可以在此应用程序上直接对产品评价进行回复！此次应用程序更新也加强了产品变体和分析的功能。请分享您的反馈，我们对每项反馈都关注。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
11.8：
即日起，你可以直接在 App 中回答產品評價！這次更新也包括產品變化與分析功能的多項改進 。請提供你的回饋，每則回饋我們都會閱讀。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
11.8:
You can now reply to product reviews directly from the app! This update also includes several enhancements to the product variations and the analytics feature. Please share feedback – we read every one of them.
</en-US>
