<ar>
16.6:
أخبار رائعة، للجميع! يعزز آخر تحديث من تجربة WooCommerce الخاصة بك بطرق متعددة. استمتع بتحديثات سريعة للمخزون عن طريق مسح الرموز الشريطية ضوئيًا بسهولة من صفحة المنتجات بشكل مباشر - يمكنك تخيُّل الراحة! تقدِّم واجهة المستخدم المتجددة الآن مبالغَ مخصصة حسب النسبة المئوية للحصول على مزيد من المرونة. ابدأ رحلة إنشاء منتجك بسلاسة من خلال دمج الصور من التطبيقات الأخرى. تضمن التحسينات الداخلية أداءً أكثر سرعة، ما يَعد باستكشاف مبهج وأكثر سهولة في الاستخدام. تعمق الآن واستكشف هذه التحسينات الرائعة!
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.6:
Tolle Neuigkeiten! Die neusten Updates optimieren dein WooCommerce-Erlebnis in vielfacher Hinsicht. Scanne Barcodes direkt auf der Produktseite, um den Lagerbestand bequem und schnell zu aktualisieren! In der überarbeiteten Benutzeroberfläche kannst du individuelle prozentuale Beträge eingeben. Bei der Produkterstellung kannst du jetzt Bilder aus anderen Apps nahtlos einfügen. Interne Optimierungen ermöglichen eine benutzerfreundlichere Suche. Sieh dir diese tollen Verbesserungen an!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
16,6:
¡Increíbles noticias para todos! La última actualización mejora tu experiencia de WooCommerce de varias formas. Disfruta de actualizaciones del inventario escaneando códigos de barras sencilla y directamente desde la página Productos, ¡muy práctico! Nuestra nueva IU ahora presenta cantidades personalizadas según porcentajes para mayor flexibilidad. Comienza el proceso de crear productos fácilmente incorporando imágenes desde otras aplicaciones. Las optimizaciones internas garantizan un rendimiento más ágil, dando como resultado una exploración más emocionante y sencilla para el usuario. ¡Entra ahora y explora estas fantásticas mejoras!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
16.6 :
Bonne nouvelle ! Cette mise à jour améliore votre expérience WooCommerce de bien des façons. Mise à jour fluide de l’inventaire en scannant les codes-barres directement depuis la page Produits. Pratique ! Flexibilité accrue grâce aux montants personnalisés basés sur des pourcentages de notre UI repensée. Création de produits fluide avec l’intégration d’images d’autres applications. Optimisations internes pour de meilleures performances, vous offrant une navigation conviviale et vivifiante. Plongez-vous dedans et explorez ces améliorations fantastiques !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.6:
יש לנו חדשות מרגשות! בעדכון האחרון שפורסם, שיפרנו את חוויית השימוש ב-WooCommerce בכמה דרכים. ניתן לעדכן את המלאי בקלי קלות באמצעות סריקה מהירה של ברקוד ישירות מהעמוד 'מוצרים' – כמה פשוט, ככה נוח! ממשק המשתמש המחודש שלנו כולל כעת סכומים ששניתן להתאים אישית לפי אחוזים כדי לאפשר גמישות רבה יותר. אפשר להתחיל את תהליך יצירת המוצר ביעילות על ידי שילוב של תמונות מאפליקציות אחרות. שיפורים פנימיים מבטיחים ביצועים מהירים יותר כדי לוודא שהשיטוט ברחבי האתר נעים וידידותי יותר למשתמש. אפשר לקפוץ לאתר כבר עכשיו כדי להתרשם מכל השיפורים הנהדרים האלה!
</iw-IL>
<id>
16.6:
Kabar gembira! Pembaruan terakhir akan memperkaya pengalaman WooCommerce Anda dalam banyak hal. Nikmati pembaruan inventaris yang cepat dengan memindai barcode langsung dari halaman Produk. Betapa mudahnya! UI telah dirancang ulang dan kini menyertakan fitur jumlah kustom berdasarkan persentase demi meningkatkan fleksibilitas. Mulailah pembuatan produk tanpa repot dengan memasukkan gambar dari aplikasi lain. Optimisasi internal memastikan performa yang lebih cepat, sehingga menjanjikan pengalaman yang menyenangkan dan lebih ramah pengguna. COba sekarang dan nikmati keunggulan terbaru yang fantastis ini!
</id>
<it-IT>
16,6:
Ottime notizie, gente! L'ultimo aggiornamento migliora la vostra esperienza WooCommerce in diversi modi. Ottieni rapidi aggiornamenti sull'inventario semplicemente scansionando i codici a barre dalla tua pagina Prodotti: immagina la praticità! La nostra interfaccia utente rinnovata ora introduce importi personalizzati basati sulla percentuale per una maggiore flessibilità. Inizia il percorso per la creazione del tuo prodotto in modo semplice incorporando immagini da altre app. Le ottimizzazioni interne garantiscono una prestazione migliore, promettendo un'esplorazione entusiasmante e più intuitiva. Scoprile ora ed esplora questi fantastici miglioramenti!
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.6:
皆さまに楽しいお知らせがあります。 最新のアップデートにより、WooCommerce エクスペリエンスがさまざまな方法で強化されます。 商品ページから直接バーコードを簡単にスキャンして在庫をすぐに更新できます。この便利さをぜひご堪能ください。 刷新された UI ではパーセンテージベースのカスタム金額が導入され、柔軟性が向上しました。 他のアプリから画像を組み込むことで、商品作成のプロセスをシームレスに開始できます。 内部の最適化により、確実にパフォーマンスがすばやくなり、快適でより利便性の高い環境でご利用いただけます。 ぜひ今すぐ以上の素晴らしい強化された機能をご確認ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.6:
신나는 소식입니다! 최신 업데이트로 우커머스 환경이 다방면에서 개선됐습니다. 이제 상품 페이지에서 바코드를 직접 스캔하여 재고를 쉽고 빠르게 업데이트하세요. 정말 편리합니다! 개선된 UI에 유연성을 더하기 위해 백분율 기반 사용자 정의 금액이 도입되었습니다. 다른 앱의 이미지를 통합하여 상품 생성 여정을 원활하게 시작하세요. 내부 최적화를 통해 성능을 더 높여서 보다 즐겁고 사용자 친화적인 탐색을 제공합니다. 지금 바로 시작하여 이 멋진 개선 사항을 경험해 보세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.6:
Spannend nieuws iedereen! Deze recentste update zal je WooCommerce-ervaring op vele manieren verbeteren. Werk je voorraad moeiteloos en snel bij door de streepjescode direct vanuit de productpagina te scannen. Zo eenvoudig kan het zijn. Onze verbeterde UI is nu nog veelzijdiger en beschikt nu over aangepaste bedragen op basis van percentages. Begin eenvoudig met het aanmaken van producten door afbeeldingen uit andere apps toe te voegen. De interne verbeteringen zorgen voor strakkere prestaties, voor een fantastische en gebruiksvriendelijke ervaring. Neem een kijkje en ontdek deze geweldige verbeteringen!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.6:
Boas notícias, pessoal! A atualização mais recente do WooCommerce melhora sua experiência de várias formas. Aproveite atualizações rápidas de inventário ao ler códigos de barras com facilidade diretamente da página Produtos. Pense na praticidade! Nossa IU repaginada traz valores personalizados com base na porcentagem para aumentar a flexibilidade. Incorpore imagens de outros aplicativos para começar a criar seu produto sem problemas. As otimizações internas garantem um desempenho melhor, proporcionando uma experiência emocionante e mais intuitiva. Mergulhe de cabeça nessas melhorias fantásticas para conhecê-las!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.6:
У нас отличные новости! Наше последнее обновление улучшает WooCommerce сразу по нескольким параметрам. Теперь вы можете моментально обновлять запас, легко сканируя штрихкоды прямо на странице «Товары». Только представьте себе, как удобно! В обновлённом пользовательском интерфейсе появился расчёт индивидуальных сумм в процентах — больше гибкости! Начните создание товара, просто интегрировав изображения из других приложений. Внутренняя оптимизация обеспечивает повышение производительности — поиск товара станет проще и увлекательнее. Надеемся, вы будете в восторге от этих потрясающих обновлений!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.6:
Spännande nyheter, allihopa! Den senaste uppdateringen förbättrar din WooCommerce-upplevelse på flera olika sätt. Få snabba lageruppdateringar genom att enkelt skanna streckkoder direkt från sidan Produkter – föreställ dig bekvämligheten! Vårt förnyade användargränssnitt introducerar nu procentbaserade anpassade belopp för ökad flexibilitet. Inled din produktskaparresa sömlöst genom att införliva bilder från andra appar. Interna optimeringar garanterar en snabbare prestanda och utlovar en spännande och mer användarvänlig utforskning. Dyk in nu och utforska dessa fantastiska förbättringar!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.6:
Size heyecan verici haberlerimiz var! En son güncelleme WooCommerce deneyiminizi birçok yönden geliştiriyor. Barkodları doğrudan Ürünler sayfasında zahmetsizce tarayarak envanter güncellemelerini hızlıca yapabilirsiniz. İşinizin ne kadar kolaylaşacağını bir düşünün! Yenilenen kullanıcı arayüzümüzde artık daha fazla esneklik sağlamak için yüzde tabanlı özel miktarlar kullanılabiliyor. Diğer uygulamalardan görseller ekleyerek ürün oluşturma yolculuğunuza sorunsuzca başlayın. Dahili optimizasyonlar daha hızlı bir deneyim sunar, böylece daha heyecan verici ve kullanıcı dostu bir keşif süreci sağlar. Hemen göz atarak bu harika gelişmeleri keşfedin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.6：
各位，激动人心的消息！ 最新更新以多种方式增强了您的 WooCommerce 体验。 直接从“产品”页面扫描条形码即可轻松享受快速的库存更新 — 方便程度可想而知！ 我们改进后的用户界面现在引入了基于百分比的自定义金额功能，提高了灵活性。 您可以将其他应用程序中的图片整合到您的产品中，无缝开始您的产品创建之旅。 通过内部优化确保更快的运行速度，以便为用户带来令人兴奋且更人性化的探索体验。 立即了解，探索这些精彩的增强功能！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.6:
我們有令人雀躍的消息要跟大家分享！ 最新的更新內容會從多方面強化你的 WooCommerce 體驗。 輕鬆直接從「產品」頁面掃描條碼，即可快速更新庫存，這該有多方便啊！ 我們的 UI 經過重新設計，現在也推出以百分比為基準的自訂金額，提高使用靈活度。 從其他應用程式納入圖片，即可輕鬆建立產品。 內部最佳化設計保證效能更流暢，提供更讓人興奮、也更方便使用者的探索體驗。 立即深入探索這些超讚的強化功能！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
16.6:
Exciting news, everyone! The latest update enhances your WooCommerce experience in multiple ways. Enjoy swift inventory updates by effortlessly scanning barcodes directly from the Products page—imagine the convenience! Our revamped UI now introduces percentage-based custom amounts for added flexibility. Begin your product creation journey seamlessly by incorporating images from other apps. Internal optimizations guarantee a snappier performance, promising an exhilarating and more user-friendly exploration. Dive in now and explore these fantastic enhancements!
</en-US>
