<ar>
16.3:
في هذا التحديث، جعلنا إدارة متجر WooCommerce الخاص بك أسهل! يمكنك الآن عرض أرصدتك وودائعك مباشرة على شاشة المدفوعات إذا كنت من مستخدمي WooCommerce Payments. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أضفنا إمكانية إنشاء منتجات الاشتراك أو تحريرها. ولجعل عملية إنشاء الطلب أكثر سلاسة، ندعم الآن منتجات الحزمة. استمتع بالوظائف المحسَّنة واستمر في تلقي تعليقاتك!
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.3:
Durch dieses Update wird die Verwaltung deines WooCommerce-Shops noch einfacher! Als Benutzer von WooCommerce Payments kannst du deine Guthaben und Auszahlungen ab sofort direkt auf dem Bildschirm für Zahlungen anzeigen. Außerdem hast du nun die Möglichkeit, Abonnementprodukte zu erstellen und zu bearbeiten. Und damit die Bestellerstellung noch reibungsloser funktioniert, unterstützen wir ab sofort Produktpakete. Genieße die verbesserten Funktionen und sende uns weiterhin Feedback!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
16,3:
En esta actualización, hemos facilitado aún más la gestión de tu tienda de WooCommerce. Ahora puedes ver tus saldos y depósitos directamente en la pantalla Pagos si eres usuario de WooCommerce Payments. Además, hemos añadido la posibilidad de crear o editar productos de suscripción. Y, para facilitar la creación de pedidos, ahora admitimos productos agrupados. Disfruta de la funcionalidad mejorada y sigue enviando tus comentarios.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
16.3 :
Avec cette mise à jour, nous simplifions encore plus la gestion de votre boutique WooCommerce ! Vous pouvez désormais voir votre solde et vos dépôts directement sur l’écran Paiements si vous utilisez WooCommerce Payments. En outre, nous pouvez maintenant créer ou modifier des produits d’abonnement. Et pour fluidifier la création de commandes, nous prenons désormais en charge les produits groupés. Profitez de cette fonctionnalité améliorée et faites-nous parvenir vos commentaires !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.3:
עדכון זה יעזור לך לנהל את החנות שלך ב-Woocommerce עוד יותר בקלות! מעכשיו, משתמשי WooCommerce Payments יוכלו לראות יתרות והפקדות ישירות במסך 'תשלומים'. הוספנו גם אפשרות ליצירה או עריכה של סוגי מינויים. וכדי להקל עליך עוד יותר ליצור הזמנות, מעכשיו אנו תומכים בחבילות. מאחלים לך הנאה מהפונקציונליות המשופרת ונשמח להמשיך לקבל משוב!
</iw-IL>
<id>
16.3:
Dalam pembaruan ini, pengelolaan toko WooCommerce Anda kini makin mudah! Saldo dan deposit kini dapat langsung dilihat di layar Pembayaran jika Anda adalah pengguna WooCommerce Payments. Selain itu, kami menambahkan kemampuan untuk membuat atau mengedit produk langganan. Untuk memperlancar pembuatan pesanan, sekarang kami juga mendukung produk bundel.  Nikmati peningkatan fungsionalitas dan kirimkan terus feedback Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
16.3:
In questo aggiornamento, abbiamo reso la gestione del negozio WooCommerce ancora più semplice. Sei sei utente di WooCommerce Payments, ora puoi visualizzare i saldi e gli acconti direttamente nella schermata Pagamenti. Inoltre, abbiamo aggiunto la possibilità di creare o modificare i prodotti in abbonamento. E per rendere la creazione degli ordini ancora più fluida, ora supportiamo i prodotti in pacchetto. Goditi la funzionalità migliorata e continua a mandarci il tuo feedback.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.3:
今回のアップデートでは、WooCommerce ストアの管理がさらに簡単になりました。 WooCommerce Payments ユーザーの方は、残高と入金を「支払い」画面で直接確認できるようになりました。 さらに、定期購入商品を作成または編集する機能も追加されました。 また、注文作成をスムーズにするために、パッケージ商品もサポートされるようになりました。 改善された機能をぜひご利用ください。フィードバックをお待ちしております。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.3:
이 업데이트에서는 우커머스 스토어 관리를 더욱더 쉽게 만들었습니다. 이제는 우커머스 결제 사용자라면 결제 화면에서 바로 잔액과 예치금을 볼 수 있습니다. 구독 상품을 생성하거나 편집하는 기능도 추가했습니다. 그리고 주문이 더 원활하게 생성되도록 이제는 번들 상품도 지원됩니다. 개선된 기능을 만끽하고 피드백을 계속 보내주세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.3:
Met deze update maken we het beheren van je WooCommerce-winkel nog makkelijker! Als je WooCommerce Payments gebruikt, kan je nu je saldo's en betalingen direct op het scherm van Payments zien. Ook heb je nu de optie om abonnementproducten te maken of te bewerken. Verder is het aanmaken van bestellingen makkelijker en ondersteunen we nu gebundelde producten. Geniet van de verbeterde functionaliteit en blijf ons vooral je feedback sturen!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.3:
Nesta atualização, simplificamos ainda mais o gerenciamento da sua loja do WooCommerce. Agora você pode ver seus saldos e depósitos diretamente na tela Pagamentos se for usuário do WooCommerce Payments. Além disso, adicionamos a capacidade de criar ou editar produtos de assinatura. E para tornar a criação de pedidos mais tranquila, agora aceitamos produtos agrupados. Aproveite as melhorias de funcionalidade e continue mandando feedback!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.3:
С этим обновлением управлять магазином WooCommerce стало ещё проще! Теперь вы можете просматривать свои балансы и счета прямо на экране «Платежи», если вы являетесь пользователем WooCommerce Payments. Кроме того, мы добавили возможность создавать или редактировать товары по подписке. А ещё теперь поддерживаются пакеты товаров, чтобы упростить создание заказов. Надеемся, вам понравятся новые функции, с нетерпением ждём ваших отзывов!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.3:
Med den här uppdateringen har vi gjort det ännu enklare att hantera din WooCommerce-butik! Nu kan du se dina saldon och insättningar direkt på skärmen Betalningar om du använder WooCommerce-betalningar. Dessutom har vi lagt till möjligheten att skapa eller redigera prenumerationsprodukter. Och för att göra det smidigare att skapa ordrar stöder vi nu paketprodukter. Mycket nöje med de förbättrade funktionerna och ge oss gärna feedback!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.3:
Bu güncellemede WooCommerce mağazanızı yönetmeyi daha da kolaylaştırdık! Artık WooCommerce Payments kullanıcıysanız bakiyenizi ve depozitolarınızı doğrudan Ödemeler ekranından görüntüleyebilirsiniz. Ayrıca abonelik ürünlerini oluşturma veya düzenleme özelliği de ekledik. Sipariş oluşturmayı kolaylaştırmak için artık paket ürünleri de destekliyoruz. İyileştirilmiş işlevlerin keyfini çıkarın ve geri bildirimlerinizi bizimle paylaşın!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.3：
在本次更新中，我们进一步降低了 WooCommerce 商店的管理难度！ WooCommerce Payments 用户现在可以直接在“付款”界面上查看余额和存款。 此外，我们还新增了创建或编辑订阅产品的功能。 并且，为了提高订单创建操作的流畅性，我们现在支持捆绑产品。 请尽情享受改进后的功能，并持续提供反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.3:
經過本次更新，你可以更輕鬆地管理 WooCommerce 商店！ 如果你是 WooCommerce Payments 使用者，現在可以直接在「付款」畫面檢視餘額和存款。 此外，我們還新增了建立或編輯訂閱產品的功能。 為了讓訂單建立流程更加順暢，我們也開始支援搭售產品。 敬請享受更強大的功能，也歡迎分享你的寶貴意見！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
16.3:
In this update, we've made managing your WooCommerce store even easier! You can now view your balances and deposits directly on the Payments screen if you're a WooCommerce Payments user. Additionally, we've added the ability to create or edit subscription products. And, to make order creation smoother, we now support bundle products. Enjoy the improved functionality and keep your feedback coming!
</en-US>
