<ar>
9.2:
تُعد الكثير من المعلومات الخاصة بطلب ما من عميل مهمة! لقد سمعنا أنك ترغب في نسخ بعض هذه التفاصيل ولصقها خارج التطبيق. يمكنك الآن الضغط مطولاً على معظم الحقول لنسخها إلى الحافظة. انسخها بعيدًا في رسالة نصية أو رسالة بريد إلكتروني أو ملحوظة!

لقد عالجنا كذلك أخطاء عديدة بشأن المدفوعات الشخصية وإنشاء الطلب. نشكرك على ملاحظاتك!
</ar>
<de-DE>
9.2:
Viele der Informationen auf einer Bestellung eines Kunden sind wichtig! Wir haben gehört, dass du einige dieser Details gerne außerhalb der App kopieren würdest. Ab sofort kannst du die meisten Felder durch längeres Drücken in die Zwischenablage kopieren. Also worauf wartest du noch – versuche es mit Textnachrichten, E-Mails oder Notizen!

Außerdem haben wir mehrere Fehler in Bezug auf persönliche Zahlungen und die Erstellung von Bestellungen behoben. Vielen Dank für dein Feedback!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
9.2:
Gran parte de la información del pedido de un cliente es importante. Sabemos que te sería útil copiar y pegar algunos de esos datos fuera de la aplicación. Por eso, ahora si mantienes pulsados la mayoría de los campos se copian en el portapapeles. Pega esta información en un mensaje de texto, correo electrónico o nota.

También hemos solucionado varios errores relacionados con los pagos en persona y la creación de pedidos. ¡Gracias por tus comentarios!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
9.2:
La plupart des informations figurant sur la commande d’un client sont importantes ! Nous savons que vous aimeriez pouvoir copier et coller certains de ces renseignements en dehors de l’application. C’est désormais possible en appuyant longtemps sur la plupart des champs pour les copier dans le presse-papiers. Collez-les dans un SMS, un e-mail ou une note !

Nous avons également corrigé plusieurs bogues concernant les paiements en personne et la création de commandes. Merci pour votre commentaire !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
9.2:
רוב המידע שמתקבל בהזמנה מלקוח חשוב ביותר! הבנו שצריך לפעמים להעתיק כמה מהפרטים האלה ולהדבקים אותם מחוץ לאפליקציה. כעת, אפשר ללחוץ לחיצה ארוכה על רוב השדות כדי להעתיק אותם ללוח. ואז להדביק את המידע בהודעת טקסט, באימייל או בפתק!

גם טיפלנו בכמה באגים ב'תשלומים באופן אישי' וביצירת ההזמנה. תודה על את המשוב!
</iw-IL>
<id>
9.2:
Sebagian besar informasi tentang pesanan dari pelanggan sangatlah penting! Kami dengar Anda sering menyalin-tempel beberapa detail tersebut di luar aplikasi. Sekarang Anda dapat menekan lama sebagian besar kolom untuk menyalinnya ke clipboard. Silakan menempelnya ke dalam pesan teks, email, atau catatan!

Kami juga mengatasi beberapa bug terkait pembayaran langsung di tempat dan pembuatan pesanan. Terima kasih atas masukan Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
9.2:
Molte delle informazioni su un ordine di un cliente sono importanti. Abbiamo sentito che vorresti copiare e incollare alcuni di questi dettagli al di fuori dell'app. Ora puoi premere in modo prolungato sulla maggior parte dei campi per copiarli negli appunti. Incolla in un messaggio di testo, e-mail o nota.

Abbiamo anche risolto diversi bug relativi ai pagamenti di persona e alla creazione degli ordini. Grazie per il feedback!
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
9.2:
お客様からの注文情報の多くには重要な情報が含まれます。 そのような詳細情報をコピーして、アプリ外に貼り付けたいという声に応え、ほとんどのフィールドは長押しすれば、クリップボードにコピーできるようにしました。 テキストメッセージ、メール、メモに貼り付けられます。

また、オフラインでの支払いと注文の作成に関するいくつかのバグにも対応しました。 フィードバックをいただきありがとうございます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
9.2:
고객의 주문에 대한 정보는 많을수록 좋습니다! 해당 상세 정보를 복사하여 앱 외부에 붙여 넣으면 좋겠다는 의견을 들었습니다. 이제 대부분 필드는 길게 눌러 클립보드로 복사하실 수 있습니다. 문자 메시지, 이메일 또는 메모에 붙여 넣으세요!

직접 결제 및 주문 생성과 관련한 여러 가지 버그도 해결했습니다. 피드백을 보내주셔서 감사합니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
9.2:
Veel van de informatie over een order van een klant is belangrijk! We hebben gehoord dat jullie deze details ook buiten de app willen kunnen kopiëren en plakken. Nu kun je de meeste velden kopiëren naar het klembord door erop te klikken en ingedrukt te houden. Plak dit in een tekstbericht, e-mail of bestandje.

We hebben ook verschillende bugs voor fysieke betalingen en het aanmaken van bestellingen opgelost. Bedankt voor je feedback!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
9.2:
Muitas das informações de um cliente no pedido são importantes. Ficamos sabendo que vocês gostam de copiar alguns desses dados para colar fora do aplicativo. Agora basta tocar e manter pressionado na maioria dos campos para copiá-los para a área de transferência. Copie e cole uma mensagem de texto, e-mail ou anotação!

Também corrigimos vários bugs de pagamentos presenciais e criação de pedidos. Obrigado pelo feedback!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
9.2:
Большая часть сведений по заказу, полученных от клиента, очень важны! Мы узнали, что вы бы хотели копировать и вставлять некоторые из этих данных вне приложения. Теперь их можно копировать в буфер обмена долгим нажатием на большинстве полей. Вставляйте данные в текстовые сообщения, письма электронной почты или примечания.

Кроме того, мы устранили некоторые ошибки, возникавшие при совершении очных платежей и создании заказов. Спасибо за ваш отзыв!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
9.2
En kundbeställning innehåller en mängd viktig information. Vi har förstått att ni vill kunna kopiera och klistra in vissa av dessa detaljer utanför appen. De flesta fält går därför nu att kopiera till urklipp med hjälp av en lång tryckning. Informationen kan klistras in i textmeddelanden, e-postmeddelanden och anteckningar.

Vi har också åtgärdat en rad olika fel som rörde personliga betalningar och beställningsskapande. Tack för din feedback!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
9.2:
Bir müşteriden gelen siparişle ilgili bilgilerin çoğu önemlidir! Bu ayrıntılardan bazılarını uygulamanın dışına kopyalayıp yapıştırmak istediğinizi duyduk. Artık çoğu alan uzun basarak panoya kopyalayabilirsiniz. Bir metin mesajına, e-postaya veya nota yapıştırın!

Ayrıca şahsen ödemeler ve sipariş oluşturma ile ilgili birkaç hatayı da düzelttik. Geri bildiriminiz için teşekkürler!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
9.2:
客户订单中的大多数信息都很重要！ 我们听说您想在应用程序外复制并粘贴一些详细信息。现在您可以长按多数字段将其复制到剪贴板。 在文本信息、电子邮件或通知中粘贴！

我们也解决了现场付款和订单创建中的几处问题。 感谢您的反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
9.2：
顧客訂單上的許多資訊都很重要！ 我們瞭解你想要複製一些詳細資料並貼到應用程式以外的地方。現在你可以在大多數欄位上長按，即可將資料複製到剪貼簿。 你可以貼到簡訊、電子郵件或是筆記中！

我們也修正了幾個有關親自收款和建立訂單的錯誤。 感謝你的意見回饋！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
9.2:
Much of the information on an order from a customer is important! We’ve heard you’d like to copy and paste some of those details outside the app. Now you can long-press on most fields to copy them to the clipboard. Paste away in a text message, e-mail, or note!

We’ve also addressed several bugs around in-person payments and order creation. Thank you for your feedback!
</en-US>
