<ar>
15.6:
يسعدنا الإعلان عن آخر تحديث لدينا! والآن، يمكن للتجار، الذين يجرون عمليات البيع في مواقع مختلفة، الاستمتاع بسهولة إعدادات معدلات الضرائب التلقائية. أصلحنا أيضًا مشكلة كانت تمنع تسجيل الدخول عندما استخدمت المواقع دليلاً مخصصًا لتثبيت ووردبريس. بالإضافة إلى أننا عززنا إنشاء المنتجات باستخدام إمكانات الذكاء الاصطناعي والمتاجر المستضافة ذاتيًا باستخدام إضافة Jetpack AI. استمتع بسلاسة العمليات وتعزيز الإنتاجية بفضل هذه التحسينات الجديدة. عمليات بيع سعيدة!
</ar>
<de-DE>
15.6:
Gestatten? Unser neues Update! Händler, die an verschiedenen Orte verkaufen, profitieren von automatischen Einstellungen für Steuersätze. Das Problem, das das Anmelden verhindert hat, wenn Websites ein individuelles Verzeichnis für die WordPress-Installation verwendet haben, ist behoben. Die Produkterstellung wurde mit AI-Rechten für WPCOM und selbst gehostete Stores, die das Plugin Jetpack AI nutzen, versehen. So genießt du einen reibungsloseren Betrieb und bessere Produktivität. Viel Erfolg!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
15,6:
Estamos encantados de anunciar nuestra última actualización. Ahora, los vendedores que venden en diferentes lugares pueden disfrutar de la comodidad de la configuración automática de las tasas de impuestos. También hemos solucionado un problema que impedía el inicio de sesión cuando los sitios utilizaban un directorio personalizado para la instalación de WordPress. Además, hemos potenciado la creación de productos con funciones de IA para WPCOM y tiendas autoalojadas mediante el plugin Jetpack AI. Disfruta de un funcionamiento más fluido y de una mayor productividad con estas nuevas mejoras. ¡Felices ventas!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
15.6:
Nous sommes ravis d’annoncer notre dernière mise à jour ! Désormais, les commerçants qui vendent dans plusieurs régions peuvent bénéficier d’un réglage automatique des taux de taxe. Nous avons également corrigé un problème qui empêchait la connexion lorsque les sites utilisaient un répertoire personnalisé pour l’installation de WordPress. De plus, nous avons optimisé la création de produits avec des fonctionnalités d’IA pour WPCOM et les boutiques auto-hébergées utilisant l’extension Jetpack AI. Grâce à ces nouvelles améliorations, bénéficiez de plus de fluidité et d’une productivité accrue. Bonnes ventes !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
15.6:
אנחנו שמחים להכריז על העדכון אחרון! כעת, סוחרים שמוכרים סחורה במיקומים שונים יכולים ליהנות מהגדרות נוחות של חישוב אוטומטי לשיעור המס. בנוסף, תיקנו בעיה שמנעה כניסה לחשבון כאשר אתרים השתמשו בספרייה מותאמת אישית להתקנה של WordPress. גם העצמנו את תהליך יצירת המוצר עם יכולות של בינה מלאכותית בחנויות של WPCOM ובחנויות באחסון עצמי שמשתמשות בתוסף Jetpack AI. השיפורים האלה מאפשרים לכולם ליהנות מביצועים חלקים יותר ומעבודה פרודוקטיבית יותר. שתהיה מכירה מהנה!
</iw-IL>
<id>
15.6:
Dengan gembira kami umumkan pembaruan terkini kami! Kini, penjual yang berjualan di berbagai lokasi dapat menikmati kemudahan dalam mengatur tarif pajak otomatis. Kami juga sudah memperbaiki masalah yang menghambat login ketika situs menggunakan direktori khusus untuk menginstal WordPress. Selain itu, kami memaksimalkan pembuatan produk berkat kemampuan AI untuk WPCOM dan toko yang dihosting sendiri menggunakan plugin Jetpack AI. Nikmati pengoperasian yang makin lancar dan produktivitas yang makin tinggi berkat semua penyempurnaan terbaru ini. Selamat berjualan!
</id>
<it-IT>
15.6:
Siamo felici di annunciare il nostro ultimo aggiornamento. Ora chi vende in diversi Paesi può godere della comodità delle impostazioni automatiche dell'aliquota d'imposta. Abbiamo inoltre risolto un problema che impediva l'accesso quando i siti utilizzavano una directory personalizzata per l'installazione di WordPress. In più, abbiamo potenziato la creazione di prodotti con le funzionalità di IA per WPCOM e di negozi ospitati personalmente utilizzando il plugin Jetpack AI. Goditi operazioni più fluide e una maggiore produttività con questi nuovi miglioramenti. Ti auguriamo di vendere con successo.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
15.6:
最新のアップデートについてお知らせします。 さまざまな場所で販売するマーチャントが税率を自動で設定できるようになり、利便性が向上しました。 また、サイトが WordPress インストールのカスタムディレクトリを使用しているときにログインできなくなる問題を修正しました。 さらに、Jetpack AI プラグインを利用しているインストール型のストアや WPCOM での商品の作成を、AI 機能によりパワーアップしました。 これらの新たな機能強化によるスムーズな操作と生産性の向上を実感してください。 販売をお楽しみください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
15.6:
최신 업데이트를 발표합니다. 이제는 다양한 위치에서 판매하는 판매자가 자동 세율 설정을 편리하게 이용할 수 있습니다. 워드프레스를 설치할 사용자 정의 디렉터리를 사이트에서 사용하면 로그인되지 않던 문제도 해결했습니다. 젯팩 AI 플러그인을 사용하는 AI 기능으로 WPCOM과 독립 호스트 스토어의 상품 생성을 강화했습니다. 이러한 새로운 개선 사항을 통해 더 원활한 운영과 향상된 생산성을 만끽하세요. 즐겁게 판매하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
15.6:
Hier is onze nieuwste update! Verkopers in verschillende locaties kunnen genieten van het gemak van het instellen van geautomatiseerde belastingtariefen. We hebben ook een probleem verholpen waarbij inloggen niet mogelijk was wanneer sites een aangepaste directory gebruikten voor WordPress-installatie. Daarbij hebben we het aanmaken van producten een boost gegeven met AI-mogelijkheden voor WPCOM en zelfgehoste winkels met de Jetpack AI-plugin. Geniet van soepelere handelingen en verbeterde productiviteit met deze nieuwe verbeteringen. Veel verkoopplezier!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
15.6:
Temos o prazer de anunciar a atualização mais recente! Agora, comerciantes que vendem em locais diferentes aproveitam configurações automáticas de impostos. Também corrigimos um problema que impedia o login quando sites usavam um diretório personalizado para instalação do WordPress. Além disso, turbinamos a criação de produtos com recursos de IA para WPCOM e lojas auto-hospedadas que usam o plugin de IA do Jetpack. Aproveite operações simplificadas e maior produtividade com essas novas melhorias. Boas vendas!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
15.6:
Мы рады представить вам очередное обновление. Отныне продавцы, торгующие в нескольких регионах, могут воспользоваться удобной функцией автоматической настройки налоговых ставок. Кроме того, была исправлена ошибка, из-за которой невозможно было выполнить вход, если сайт использовал собственную директорию для установки WordPress. А ещё мы значительно расширили возможности создания товаров для WPCOM и автономных магазинов с помощью искусственного интеллекта, подключив Jetpack AI plugin. Благодаря новым улучшениям вам будет проще и приятнее работать, а производительность значительно возрастёт. Надеемся, что вам понравится! Удачных продаж!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
15.6:
Vi är glada att kunna presentera vår senaste uppdatering. Nu kan handlare som säljer på olika platser använda sig av bekväma inställningar för automatiska momssatser. Vi har också åtgärdat ett problem som förhindrade inloggning när webbplatser använde en anpassad katalog för WordPress-installation. Dessutom har vi förbättrat produktskapandet med AI-funktioner för WPCOM och butiker som drivs på egen server med hjälp av Jetpacks AI-tillägg. Dessa nya förbättringar ger smidigare hantering och förbättrad produktivitet. Lycka till med försäljningen.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
15.6:
En yeni güncellemelerimizi duyurmaktan büyük heyecan duyuyoruz! Artık farklı lokasyonlarda satış yapan satıcılar, otomatik vergi oranı ayarlarının rahatlığından yararlanabilirler. Siteler WordPress kurulumu için özel bir dizin kullandığında oturum açmayı engelleyen bir sorunu da giderdik. Ayrıca, Jetpack Yapay Zeka eklentisini kullanan WPCOM ve kullanıcı tarafından barındırılan mağazalar için yapay zeka özellikleriyle ürün oluşturmayı güçlendirdik. Bu yeni iyileştirmelerle daha sorunsuz işlemlerin ve gelişmiş üretkenliğin keyfini çıkarın. İyi satışlar!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
15.6：
很高兴发布我们的最新更新！ 现在，在不同地点进行销售的商家可以享受自动税率设置功能所带来的便利。 我们还修复了站点使用自定义 WordPress 安装目录时无法登录的问题。 此外，我们还借助 AI 功能，增强了 WPCOM 和使用 Jetpack AI 插件的自托管商店的产品创建能力。 这些改进能提高您的操作顺畅性和效率。 祝您销售顺利！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
15.6：
很高興能宣布最新更新版本資訊！ 現在起，不同國家/地區的商家都能享受自動稅率設定帶來的便利。 我們也修復了於 WordPress 安裝中使用自訂目錄時，發生的網站登入失敗問題。 此外，我們也運用 Jetpack AI 外掛程式新增了 AI 功能，可用於建立 WPCOM 和自助託管商店中的商品。 享受更順暢的營運流程，並利用這些新功能提升生產力。 祝銷售愉快！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
15.6:
We're thrilled to announce our latest update! Now, merchants selling in different locations can enjoy the convenience of automatic tax rate settings. We've also fixed an issue that was preventing login when sites used a custom directory for WordPress installation. Plus, we've supercharged product creation with AI capabilities for WPCOM and self-hosted stores using the Jetpack AI plugin. Enjoy smoother operations and enhanced productivity with these new improvements. Happy selling!
</en-US>
