<ar>
17.3:
قمنا بتحسين تدفق إنشاء ملصق الشحن لضمان تجربة أكثر سلاسة وسهولة. يهدف ذلك التحسين إلى تبسيط عملية تنفيذ طلبك، ما يجعلها أسرع وأكثر كفاءة. ترجى مواصلة إرسال الملاحظات إلينا – فكلنا آذان مصغية!
</ar>
<de-DE>
17.3:
Wir haben den Prozess zum Erstellen von Versandetiketten verbessert, um dir ein reibungsloseres und intuitiveres Erlebnis zu ermöglichen. Mit dieser Verbesserung soll deine Auftragsausführung optimiert sowie schneller und effizienter gestaltet werden. Sende uns bitte weiter Feedback – wir freuen uns darauf!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
17.3:
Hemos mejorado el proceso de creación de etiquetas de envío para que la experiencia resulte más sencilla y fluida. Con esta mejora también se pretende optimizar tu proceso de tramitación de pedidos, de modo que todo sea más rápido y eficiente. Sigue enviándonos tus comentarios: ¡te escuchamos!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
17.3 :
Nous avons amélioré le flux de création d’étiquettes d’expédition pour assurer une expérience plus fluide et plus intuitive. Cette amélioration vise à rationaliser le processus de traitement des commandes, afin de le rendre plus rapide et plus efficace. Continuez à nous envoyer vos commentaires. Votre avis nous intéresse !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
17.3:
שיפרנו את תהליך היצירה של תוויות משלוח כדי לוודא חוויית שימוש יעילה ואינטואיטיבית יותר. השיפור נועד ליצור תהליך חלק יותר למילוי הזמנות על ידי שיפור הזריזות והיעילות שלו. נשמח לקבל עוד משוב – אנחנו תמיד כאן כדי להקשיב!
</iw-IL>
<id>
17.3:
Kami menyempurnakan alur pembuatan label pengiriman agar pengalaman Anda lebih mulus dan intuitif. Peningkatan ini bertujuan untuk menyederhanakan proses pemenuhan pesanan sehingga menjadi lebih cepat dan efisien. Mohon terus berikan feedback – kami siap mendengarkan!
</id>
<it-IT>
17.3:
Abbiamo migliorato il flusso di creazione delle etichette di spedizione per garantire un'esperienza più fluida e intuitiva. Questo miglioramento mira a snellire il processo di evasione degli ordini, rendendolo più veloce ed efficiente. Continua a inviarci feedback: siamo lieti di ascoltarli.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
17.3:
配送ラベルの作成フローが強化され、よりスムーズで直感的に操作できるようになりました。 この改善は、注文のフルフィルメント処理を合理化し、より迅速で効率的にすることを目的としています。 引き続き、フィードバックをお寄せください。ぜひ参考にさせていただきます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
17.3:
더 원활하고 더 직관적인 경험이 확보되도록 배송 레이블 생성 절차를 개선했습니다. 더 빠르고 더 효율적으로 진행되도록 주문 처리 프로세스를 간소화하는 것이 이 개선의 목표입니다. 계속 피드백을 보내주세요. 경청하겠습니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
17.3:
We've enhanced the shipping label creation flow to ensure a smoother and more intuitive experience. This improvement aims to streamline your order fulfillment process, making it faster and more efficient. Blijf ons feedback sturen – wij luisteren!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
17.3:
Melhoramos o fluxo de criação de etiquetas de envio para garantir uma experiência mais intuitiva e tranquila. Esta melhoria visa agilizar o processo de atendimento de pedidos, tornando-o mais rápido e eficiente. Continue compartilhando seu feedback conosco. Estamos atentos.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
17.3:
Мы усовершенствовали процесс создания транспортных этикеток, чтобы сделать его понятнее и эффективнее. Цель этого улучшения — оптимизировать и ускорить процесс выполнения заказа. Мы по-прежнему ждём ваших отзывов и прислушиваемся к ним!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
17.3:
Vi har förbättrat flödet vid skapande av fraktsedlar för att säkerställa en smidigare och mer intuitiv upplevelse. Förbättringen är tänkt att effektivisera din orderhanteringsprocess och göra den snabbare och mer effektiv. Fortsätt att skicka feedback till oss – vi lyssnar.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
17.3:
Daha sorunsuz ve sezgisel bir deneyim sağlamak için gönderim etiketi oluşturma akışını geliştirdik. Bu geliştirme, sipariş tamamlama sürecinizi kolaylaştırmayı hedefleyerek bu süreci daha hızlı ve verimli hale getirir. Lütfen bize geri bildirim göndermeye devam edin, sizi dinliyoruz!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
17.3：
我们增强了货运标签创建流程，以确保更流畅、更直观的体验。 这项改进旨在简化订单履行流程，使之更快速、更高效。 请继续向我们发送反馈，我们时刻倾听您的意见！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
17.3：
提升了運送標籤的製作流程，以確保更順暢直觀的使用體驗。 這項改善旨在簡化訂單履行流程，使其更快速有效率。 歡迎繼續給予我們意見回饋，我們很樂意虛心傾聽！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
17.3:
We've enhanced the shipping label creation flow to ensure a smoother and more intuitive experience. This improvement aims to streamline your order fulfillment process, making it faster and more efficient. Please continue sending us feedback – we are listening!
</en-US>
