<ar>
5.7:
- إزالة الصور من أنواع المنتج!
- يمكن للتطبيق فتح برنامج البريد الإلكتروني على نظام تشغيل Android 11 في أثناء عملية تسجيل دخول الرابط السحري.
- إصلاحات الأخطاء: يتم عرض المنتجات المتغيرة عند شراء ملصقات الشحن؛ يتم تكريم الاختيارات في مربع الحوار.
- يتم عرض الرسوم في تفاصيل دفع الطلب.
- تم دعم عمليات تسجيل الدخول من دون كلمة مرور.
- تحسينات طفيفة في النمط لشاشات تسجيل الدخول.
</ar>
<de-DE>
5.7:
- Bilder aus Produktvarianten entfernen!
- Die App kann den E-Mail-Client während des Anmeldevorgangs per magischem Link auf Android 11 öffnen.
- Fehlerkorrekturen: Beim Kauf von Versandetiketten werden Produktvarianten angezeigt. Im Dialogfeld vorgenommene Auswahlen werden berücksichtigt.
- Auf dem Bildschirm mit den Zahlungsdetails für die Bestellung werden Gebühren angezeigt.
- Passwortlose Anmeldungen werden unterstützt.
- Kleine Stilverbesserungen an den Anmeldebildschirmen
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
5.7:
- Eliminar imágenes de las variaciones de producto.
- La aplicación puede abrir el cliente de correo electrónico en Android 11 durante el proceso de acceso con enlace mágico.
- Reparación de errores: al adquirir etiquetas de envío se muestran los productos variables; las selecciones en los diálogos se respetan.
- Se muestran las tarifas en la información de pago del pedido.
- Compatibilidad con el inicio de sesión sin contraseña.
- Pequeñas mejoras de estilo en las pantallas de inicio de sesión.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
5.7 :
- Supprimez les images des variantes du produit !
- L’application peut ouvrir le client de messagerie sur Android 11 pendant le processus de connexion au lien magique de connexion.
- Résolutions de bugs : divers produits s’affichent lors de l’achat d’étiquettes de livraison ; les sélections effectuées dans une boîte de dialogue sont respectées.
- Les frais apparaissent dans les détails de paiement de la commande.
- Connexions sans mot de passe prises en charge.
- Améliorations mineures du style des écrans de connexion.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
5.7: 
- להסיר תמונות בסוגי מוצרים!
- אפשר לפתוח את לקוח האימייל באפליקציה במערכת של Android 11 בתהליך ההתחברות דרך קישור ישיר.
- תיקוני באגים: מוצרים עם סוגים מוצגים כאשר נרכשו תוויות משלוח וניתן לבצע בחירה בתיבת דו-שיח.
- העמלות מוצגות בפרטי התשלום של ההזמנה.
- יש תמיכה בהתחברות ללא סיסמה.
- הוספנו שיפורים בסגנון של מסכי ההתחברות.
</iw-IL>
<id>
5.7:
- Gambar dihapus dari variasi produk!
- Di Android 11, aplikasi dapat membuka klien email saat proses login menggunakan magic link.
- Perbaikan bug: produk variabel muncul saat label pengiriman dibeli; opsi yang dipilih di dialog disimpan.
- Biaya ditampilkan di rincian pembayaran pesanan.
- Dapat login tanpa kata sandi.
- Perubahan kecil pada gaya di layar login.
</id>
<it-IT>
5.7:
- Rimuovi le immagini dalle varianti del prodotto.
- L'app può aprire il client di posta elettronica su Android 11 durante il processo di accesso tramite link.
- Correzioni di bug: visualizzazione dei prodotti variabili quando vengono acquistate le etichette di spedizione; rispetto delle selezioni effettuate in una finestra di dialogo.
- Visualizzazione delle tariffe nei dettagli di pagamento dell'ordine.
- Accessi senza password supportati.
- Miglioramenti minori alle schermate di accesso.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
5.7:
- 商品バリエーションから画像を削除しました。
- マジックリンクのログイン処理中に Android 11でメールクライアントを開けるようになりました。
- バグ修正 : 配送ラベルの購入時に可変製品が表示されるようになりました。ダイアログでの選択が有効になりました。
- 料金が、注文支払いの詳細に表示されるようになりました。
- パスワードレスログインに対応しました。
- ログイン画面のスタイルを微調整しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
5.7:
- 제품 변형에서 이미지를 제거하세요!
- 매직 링크 로그인 프로세스 동안 Android 11의 이메일 클라이언트를 앱에서 열 수 있습니다.
- 버그 수정: 배송 레이블을 구매할 때 변형 제품이 표시되며, 대화 상자에서 선택한 내용이 인식됩니다.
- 주문 결제 상세 정보에 수수료가 표시됩니다.
- 비밀번호 없는 로그인이 지원됩니다.
- 로그인 화면의 스타일이 약간 개선되었습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
5.7:
-Verwijder afbeeldingen van productvariaties!
- De app kan de e-mailclient openen op Android 11 tijdens het inloggen via de magische link.
- Bugfixes: variabele producten worden weergegeven bij het kopen van verzendlabels; producten die in een dialoogvenster worden geselecteerd, worden doorgevoerd.
- Toeslagen worden weergegeven bij betalingsgegevens van de bestelling.
- Log-ins zonder wachtwoord worden ondersteund.
- Kleine stijlverbeteringen voor de inlogschermen.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
5.7:
- Remoção das imagens das variações de produtos.
- O aplicativo pode abrir o cliente de e-mail no Android 11 durante o processo de login via link.
- Correções de bug: produtos variáveis são exibidos durante a compra de etiquetas de envio; as seleções feitas em uma caixa de diálogo são obedecidas.
- Visualização das taxas nos detalhes de pagamento do pedido.
- Suporte a login sem senha.
- Pequenas melhorias de estilo nas telas de login.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
5,7:
— Удалить изображения из вариантов продуктов!
— Приложение может открыть почтовый клиент в ОС Android 11 во время входа в систему по ссылке.
— Исправления ошибок: при покупке транспортных этикеток отображаются продукты с вариантами; учитывается выбор, сделанный в диалоговом окне.
— Сборы отображаются в сведениях об оплате заказа.
— Поддерживается вход в систему без ввода пароля.
— Небольшие усовершенствования стиля экранов входа в систему.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
5.7:
- Ta bort bilder från produktvariationer!
- Appen kan öppna e-postklienten i Android 11 under inloggningsprocessen med den magiska länken.
- Felkorrigeringar: variabla produkter visas när fraktetiketter köps. De val som görs i en dialogruta respekteras.
- Avgifter visas på beställningsbetalningsinformation.
- Lösenordsfria inloggningar stöds.
- Mindre stilförbättringar av inloggningsskärmarna.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
5.7:
- Ürün çeşitlerinden resimleri kaldırın.
- Uygulama, sihirli bağlantı giriş işlemi sırasında Android 11'de e-posta istemcisini açabilir.
- Hata düzeltmeleri: Gönderi etiketleri satın alındığında değişken ürünler görüntülenir; bir iletişim kutusunda yapılan seçimler kabul edilir.
- Ücretler, sipariş ödeme ayrıntılarında görüntülenir.
- Şifresiz girişler desteklenir. 
- Giriş ekranlarında küçük stil iyileştirmeleri.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
5.7：
- 删除了产品变体中的图像！
- 该应用程序可以在通过免密链接登录过程中在 Android 11 上打开电子邮件客户端。
- 错误修复：购买配送标签时会显示可变产品；将遵循在对话框中选定的产品。
- 订单付款详情中显示费用。
- 支持免密登录。
- 对登录屏幕的样式进行了一些细微改进。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
5.7：
- 從商品款式移除圖片！
- 應用程式可在神奇連結登入程序期間在 Android 11 上開啟電子郵件用戶端。
- 錯誤修正：購買運輸標籤時顯示子類商品；接受在對話方塊中所做的選擇。
- 費用顯示在訂單付款詳細資訊上。
- 支援無密碼登入。
- 對登入畫面的樣式稍做修改。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
5.7:
- Remove images from product variations!
- The app can open the email client on Android 11 during the magic link login process.
- Bug fixes: variable products display when shipping labels are purchased; selections made in a dialog are honored.
- Fees display on order payment details.
- Passwordless logins supported.
- Minor style improvements to the login screens.
</en-US>
