<ar>
13.0:
أخبار رائعة للجمهور الذي يستخدم امتداد WooCommerce Subscriptions. لقد أضفنا دعمًا للقراءة فقط لامتداد WooCommerce Subscriptions في تفاصيل الطلب وشاشات تفاصيل المنتجات. مزيد من الميزات قريبًا!
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.0:
Es gibt tolle Neuigkeiten für Benutzer der WooCommerce Subscriptions-Erweiterung. Wir haben auf den Bildschirmen mit den Bestell- und Produktdetails Support mit Lesezugriff für die WooCommerce Subsciptions-Erweiterung hinzugefügt. Weitere Funktionen sind demnächst verfügbar!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
13.0:
Buenas noticias para los usuarios de la extensión WooCommerce Subscriptions. Hemos añadido soporte de solo lectura para la extensión WooCommerce Subscriptions en las pantallas de detalles del pedido y detalles del producto. En breve incluiremos más funciones.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
13.0 : 
Bonne nouvelle pour les utilisateurs de l’extension WooCommerce Subscriptions. Nous avons ajouté un accès en lecture seule à l’extension WooCommerce Subscriptions sur les pages des détails de la commande et du produit. D’autres fonctionnalités sont à venir !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.0:
חדשות טובות למשתמשים בהרחבה של WooCommerce Subscriptions. הוספנו תמיכה לקריאה בלבד בהרחבה של WooCommerce Subsciptions במסכים של פרטי ההזמנה ופרטי המוצר. בקרוב נשיק אפשרויות נוספות!
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.0:
Kabar baik bagi pengguna ekstensi WooCommerce Subscriptions. Kami telah menambahkan dukungan hanya baca untuk ekstensi WooCommerce Subscriptions pada layar detail pemesanan dan detail produk. Segera hadir banyak fitur lainnya!
</id>
<it-IT>
13.0:
Ottime notizie per tutti coloro che utilizzano l'estensione Abbonamenti WooCommerce. Abbiamo aggiunto il supporto di sola lettura per l'estensione Abbonamenti WooCommerce nelle schermate dei dettagli dell'ordine e dei dettagli del prodotto. Maggiori funzionalità sono in arrivo!
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.0:
WooCommerce Subscriptions 拡張機能をお使いの皆さまに良いお知らせです。 注文詳細画面と商品情報画面に、WooCommerce Subsciptions 拡張機能の読み取り専用のサポートを追加しました。 その他の機能も近日中に公開予定です !
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.0:
우커머스 구독 확장 기능 사용자께 좋은 소식을 전해드립니다. 주문 상세 정보 화면과 상품 상세 정보 화면에 우커머스 구독 확장 기능 읽기 전용 지원을 추가했습니다. 더 많은 기능을 곧 공개할 예정입니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.0:
Geweldig nieuws voor de mensen die de WooCommerce Subscriptions-extensie gebruiken. We hebben read-only ondersteuning voor de WooCommerce Subscriptions-extensie toegevoegd aan de schermen bestellingsgegevens en de productgegevens. Binnenkort nog meer functies!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
13.0:
Ótimas notícias para quem está usando a extensão do WooCommerce Subscriptions: adicionamos compatibilidade com o modo somente leitura à extensão do WooCommerce Subscriptions nas telas de dados do pedido e de detalhes do produto. Mais funcionalidades em breve!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
13.0:
Превосходные новости для всех, кто использует расширение WooCommerce Subscriptions. Мы добавили поддержку режима «только для чтения» для расширения WooCommerce Subsciptions на экранах описаний заказов и продуктов. Еще больше функций выйдет уже скоро!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.0:
Goda nyheter för de som använder WooCommerce prenumerationstillägg. Vi har lagt till stöd för skrivskydd för WooCommerce prenumerationstillägget på skärmarna med orderinformation och produktinformation. Fler funktioner kommer snart!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.0:
WooCommerce Subscriptions uzantısını kullanan kişiler için harika bir haber. Sipariş detayı ve ürün detayı ekranlarına WooCommerce Subsciptions eklentisi için salt okunur destek ekledik. Yakında daha fazla özellik gelecek!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.0：
对于使用 WooCommerce Subscriptions 扩展程序的用户来说，这是个好消息。 我们在订单详细信息和产品详细信息屏幕中添加了对 WooCommerce Subscipations 扩展程序的只读支持。 更多功能即将推出！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.0：
使用 WooCommerce Subscriptions 擴充功能的使用者有福了。 我們已為 WooCommerce Subsciptions 擴充功能的訂單詳細資料和產品詳細資料頁面新增唯讀支援。 敬請期待更多功能！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
13.0:
Great news for folks that are using WooCommerce Subscriptions extension. We have added read only support for the WooCommerce Subsciptions extension in the order detail and product detail screens. More features coming soon!
</en-US>
