<ar>
9.6:
يتضمن هذا الإصدار خيار تحصيل المدفوعات لجميع الطلبات التي لم يتم دفعها عن طريق الدفع النقدي أو بطاقة أو روابط الدفع. يمكنك كذلك تحديد بوابة دفع مُفضَّلة عند تثبيت عدة إضافات على المتجر.

لقد أجرينا كذلك القليل من التحسينات الطفيفة الأخرى. شكرًا لكم جميعًا مرة أخرى على ملحوظاتكم الرائعة. استمروا!
</ar>
<de-DE>
9.6:
Diese Version enthält die Möglichkeit, für alle unbezahlten Bestellungen Zahlungen in bar, per Karte oder per Zahlungslink zu empfangen. Du kannst auch ein bevorzugtes Zahlungs-Gateway auswählen, wenn mehrere Erweiterungen im Shop installiert sind.

Wir haben außerdem noch ein paar andere Optimierungen vorgenommen. Danke an alle für euer hervorragendes Feedback. Weiter so!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
9.6:
Esta versión incluye la opción de recibir los pagos de los pedidos pendientes en efectivo, tarjeta o enlaces de pago. Además, si tienes varias extensiones instaladas en la tienda, puedes elegir la pasarela de pago que prefieras.

También hemos introducido otras mejoras más pequeñas. Gracias de nuevo por tus increíbles comentarios. ¡Sigue así!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
9.6 :
Cette version vous permet d’encaisser les paiements de toutes les commandes impayées en espèces, par carte ou via des liens de paiement. Vous pouvez également sélectionner votre passerelle de paiement préférée lorsque plusieurs extensions sont installées dans votre boutique. 

Nous avons également apporté quelques corrections mineures. Une fois encore, merci à tous pour vos précieux commentaires ! Continuez à nous les envoyer !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
9.6:
בגרסה הזאת הוספנו אפשרות לגביית תשלומים עבור כל ההזמנות שלא שולמו במזומן, באמצעות כרטיס או דרך קישורים לתשלום. אפשר גם לבחור שער תשלום מועדף אם מותקנות מספר הרחבות בחנות.

הוספנו גם כמה שיפורים קטנים אחרים. אנחנו שוב רוצים להודות לכולם על המשוב החשוב. תמיד נשמח לשמוע מה דעתכם!
</iw-IL>
<id>
9.6:
Rilis ini mencakup pilihan untuk menerima pembayaran untuk semua pesanan yang belum dibayar melalui tunai, kartu, atau tautan pembayaran. Jika beberapa ekstensi diinstal di toko, Anda juga dapat memilih gateway pembayaran yang diutamakan.

Kami juga telah membuat peningkatan minor lainnya. Sekali lagi, terima kasih atas feedback Anda. Terus kirimkan feedback Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
9.6:
Questo rilascio include l'opzione per ricevere pagamenti per tutti gli ordini non pagati tramite contanti, carta o link di pagamento. Puoi anche selezionare un gateway di pagamento preferito quando vengono installate più estensioni nel negozio.

Abbiamo anche apportato altri miglioramenti minori. Grazie a tutti ancora per il meraviglioso feedback. Continuate a inviarlo.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
9.6:
このリリースには、すべての未払い注文に対する支払いを現金、カード、支払いリンク経由で受け取るオプションが含まれています。 複数の拡張機能がストアにインストールされている場合は、希望の決済方法を選択することもできます。

いくつかの細かな改善も行っています。 皆さまからのフィードバックが改善の励みになります。 今後ともよろしくお願いいたします。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
9.6:
이 릴리스에는 현금, 카드 또는 결제 링크를 통한 모든 미결제 주문에 대한 결제를 수령하는 옵션이 있습니다. 스토어에 여러 확장 기능이 있으면 선호하는 결제 게이트웨이를 선택할 수도 있습니다.

다른 몇 가지도 소소하게 개선했습니다. 놀라운 피드백을 제공해 주셔서 정말로 감사합니다. 계속 보내주세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
9.6:
Met deze versie kun je betalingen met cash, betaalkaart of betaallinks innen voor alle onbetaalde bestellingen. Daarnaast kun je een favoriete betaalgateway selecteren als je meerdere extensies voor je winkel hebt geïnstalleerd.

We hebben tevens enkele kleine verbeteringen doorgevoerd. Wederom bedankt voor jullie geweldige feedback. Blijf zo doorgaan!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
9.6:
Esta versão inclui a opção de receber os pagamentos de todos os pedidos não pagos em dinheiro, cartão ou links de pagamento. Você também pode selecionar o gateway de pagamento que quiser quando várias extensões estão instaladas na loja.

Além disso, fizemos algumas outras pequenas melhorias. Obrigado a todos pelos incríveis feedbacks. Continuem mandando!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
9.6:
В этой версии добавлена возможность получения платежей за неоплаченные заказы наличными средствами, картой или посредством ссылок для оплаты. Кроме того, можно выбрать предпочтительный платёжный сервис, если для магазина установлено несколько расширений.

Мы также внесли некоторые незначительные усовершенствования. Благодарим вас за невероятные отзывы. Они очень важны для нас!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
9.6:
Den här versionen inkluderar möjligheten att ta betalt för alla obetalda beställningar via kontanter, kort eller betalningslänkar. Du kan även välja en föredragen betalnings-gateway när det finns flera utökningar installerade på butiken.

Vi har även utfört vissa mindre förbättringar. Tack ännu en gång för all fantastisk feedback. Fortsätt skicka in den!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
9.6:
Bu sürüm, ödenmemiş tüm siparişler için ödemeleri nakit, kart veya ödeme bağlantıları aracılığıyla tahsil etme seçeneğini içerir. Mağazada birden fazla uzantı yüklü olduğunda da tercih edilen bir ödeme ağ geçidini seçebilirsiniz.

Ayrıca birkaç küçük iyileştirme daha yaptık. Harika geri bildirimleriniz için herkese tekrar teşekkür ederim. Devam edin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
9.6：
此版本包括选择通过现金、银行卡或付款链接向所有未付款订单收款。 当商店安装了多个扩展时，您也可以选择推荐的付款网关。

我们还做了其他一些细微改进。 再次感谢您宝贵的反馈。 请继续提供反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
9.6：
此版本包含收款選項，可讓你透過現金、信用卡或付款連結收取所有未付款訂單的費用。 如果商店安裝多個擴充功能，你也可以選擇偏好的付款閘道。

我們也完成了幾項微幅改善作業。 再次感謝你提供寶貴的意見回饋， 未來請繼續多多指教！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
9.6:
This release includes the option to collect payments for all unpaid orders via cash, card or payment links. You can also select a preferred payment gateway when multiple extensions are installed on the store.

We’ve also made a few other minor improvements. Thank you all again for your amazing feedback. Keep it coming!
</en-US>
