<ar>
15.5:
إننا متحمسون لطرح ميزة جديدة في هذا التحديث الجديد! لمساعدتك على البقاء مطلعًا على تعليقات العملاء، أضفنا عامل تصفية جديدًا لمراجعات المنتجات غير المقروءة. سيسمح لك ذلك بفرز ردودك وتحديد أولويتها بسهولة، ما يضمن أن يشعر كل عملائك بأن ثمّة مَن يسمعهم ويقدِّرهم. استمتع بهذا المستوى الجديد أو الكفاءة في إدارة متجرك على الإنترنت.
</ar>
<de-DE>
15.5:
Wir freuen uns, in diesem Update eine neue Funktion vorstellen zu dürfen. Damit du über Kundenfeedback stets im Bilde bist, haben wir einen neuen Filter für ungelesene Produktbewertungen hinzugefügt. Du kannst deine Antworten damit einfach sortieren und priorisieren und deinen Kunden zeigen, dass sie gehört und wertgeschätzt werden. Genieße diese neu gewonnene Effizienz beim Verwalten deines Onlineshops.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
15,5:
Nos complace presentar una nueva función en esta nueva actualización. Para ayudarte a estar al tanto de las opiniones de los clientes, hemos añadido un nuevo filtro para las opiniones de productos no leídas. Esto te permitirá ordenar y priorizar fácilmente tus respuestas, así como asegurarte de que todos tus clientes se sientan escuchados y valorados. Disfruta de este nuevo nivel de eficiencia en la gestión de tu tienda online.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
15.5 :
Cette mise à jour comporte une nouvelle fonctionnalité ! Pour vous aider à rester au fait des commentaires des clients, nous avons ajouté un nouveau filtre permettant d’afficher les avis non lus sur les produits. Vous pourrez ainsi facilement trier et prioriser vos réponses afin que tous vos clients se sentent écoutés et valorisés. Profitez de ce nouveau niveau d’efficacité dans la gestion de votre boutique en ligne.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
15.5:
אנחנו שמחים להציג אפשרות חדשה בעדכון הזה! כדי לעזור לך להתעדכן בכל המשוב שמתקבל מלקוחות, הוספנו מסנן חדש כדי להציג רק ביקורות שלא נקראו למוצרים. המסנן יאפשר לך למיין בקלות את המשוב ולתעדף את התגובות כדי להראות ללקוחות שהתייחסת למשוב ושהוא חשוב לך. אנחנו מקווים שהתייעלות הביצועים בניהול החנות המקוונת שלך תמצא חן בעיניך.
</iw-IL>
<id>
15.5:
Dengan bangga kami persembahkan fitur baru di pembaruan kali ini! Agar Anda bisa memantau feedback pelanggan dengan mudah, kami hadirkan penyaring untuk ulasan produk yang belum terbaca. Dengan begitu, feedback bisa disortir dan diprioritaskan dengan praktis, sehingga tiap pelanggan akan merasa dihargai dan didengar. Efisiensi dalam mengelola toko online Anda kini naik kelas.
</id>
<it-IT>
15.5:
Siamo felici di introdurre una nuova funzionalità in questo nuovo aggiornamento. Per aiutarti a tenere sotto controllo il feedback dei clienti, abbiamo aggiunto un nuovo filtro per visualizzare le recensioni dei prodotti non lette. Questo ti consentirà di ordinare e dare priorità facilmente alle risposte, assicurandoti che tutti i clienti si sentano ascoltati e apprezzati. Goditi questo nuovo livello di efficienza nella gestione del tuo negozio online.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
15.5:
この新しいアップデートでは新機能を導入することをお知らせいたします。 お客様からのフィードバックを常に把握できるよう、未読の商品レビュー用に新しいフィルターを追加しました。 この機能により、回答を簡単に分類して優先順位を付けることができ、すべてのお客様が、自分の意見を聞いてくれる、大切にされていると感じられるようになります。 オンラインストアの管理では、この新境地の機能や効率性にぜひご注目ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
15.5:
이 새 업데이트에서 새로운 기능을 소개합니다! 고객 피드백을 파악하는 데 도움이 되도록 읽지 않은 상품 리뷰에 대한 새로운 필터를 추가했습니다. 이를 통해 응답을 쉽게 정렬하고 우선순위를 지정할 수 있으므로 모든 고객이 자신의 의견이 수용되고 존중받는다고 느끼게 됩니다. 온라인 스토어 관리에서 이 새로운 레벨, 즉 효율을 만끽하세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
15.5:
Met veel trots presenteren we in deze nieuwe update een nieuwe functie! Om ervoor te zorgen dat je altijd op de hoogte bent van feedback van klanten hebben we een filter toegevoegd voor ongelezen productbeoordelingen. Hierdoor kan je je reacties makkelijk sorteren en prioriteit geven waardoor al je klanten zich gehoord en gewaardeerd voelen. Geniet van een nieuw efficiëntieniveau op het gebied van het beheren van je online winkel.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
15.5:
Temos o prazer de apresentar uma nova funcionalidade nesta atualização! Para ajudar você a ficar por dentro dos feedbacks dos clientes, adicionamos um filtro de avaliações de produto não lidas. Assim, você poderá facilmente ordenar e priorizar suas respostas, garantindo que todos os clientes se sintam ouvidos e valorizados. Aproveite este novo nível de eficiência na gestão da sua loja online.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
15.5:
В новом обновлении мы рады представить вам новую функцию! Мы добавили новый фильтр — «Непрочитанные отзывы», чтобы вы могли всегда быть в курсе того, что думают клиенты. Этот фильтр поможет вам без труда сортировать и упорядочивать отзывы, а ваши клиенты будут знать, что их мнения услышаны и оценены по достоинству. Управлять онлайн-магазином становится ещё проще. Надеемся, что вам понравится!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
15.5:
Vi är glada att kunna presentera en ny funktion i den här uppdateringen. För att hjälpa dig att hålla koll på feedback från kunder har vi lagt till ett nytt filter för olästa produktrecensioner. Detta gör att du enkelt kan sortera och prioritera dina svar, vilket säkerställer att alla dina kunder känner sig hörda och värdesatta. Ta del av den här nya effektivitetsnivån för hantering av din onlinebutik.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
15.5:
Bu yeni güncellemede yeni bir özelliği tanıtmaktan heyecan duyuyoruz! Müşteri geri bildirimlerini takip etmenize yardımcı olmak için, okunmamış ürün incelemeleri için yeni bir filtre ekledik. Bu filtre, yanıtlarınızı kolayca sıralamanıza ve önceliklendirmenize imkan tanıyacak, dolayısıyla tüm müşterilerinizin dikkate alındığını ve değer verildiğini hissetmesini sağlayacaktır. Çevrimiçi mağazanızı yönetirken bu yeni seviyenin veya verimliliğin keyfini çıkarın.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
15.5：
我们很高兴在此次更新版本中推出一项新功能！ 为帮助您随时了解客户反馈，我们新增了未读产品评论过滤器。 这样，您就可以轻松地对回复进行整理和优先排序，确保所有客户都能感受到您的关注和重视。 这将进一步提高您的在线商店的管理水平和效率。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
15.5:
很高興為你介紹這次更新的新功能！ 為了方便掌握最新的客戶意見回饋，我們新增了未讀產品評論篩選條件； 這可以讓你輕鬆排序評論並依緊急程度安排回應的優先順序，確保所有客戶都感受到我們傾聽並重視他們的意見。 好好享受全新層次的線上商店管理效率。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
15.5:
We're excited to introduce a new feature in this new update! To help you stay on top of customer feedback, we've added a new filter for unread product reviews. This will allow you to easily sort and prioritize your responses, ensuring that all your customers feel heard and valued. Enjoy this new level or efficiency in managing your online store.
</en-US>
