<de-DE>
7.1:
Einige Verkäufer in den USA, die WooCommerce Shipping & Tax in ihrem Store verwenden, haben einen Fehler beim Erstellen von Etiketten für Bestellungen von Produktmengen mit Dezimalstellen entdeckt. Diesen haben wir behoben!

Möchtest du versuchen, ein Etikett zu erstellen? Installiere und aktiviere die Erweiterung „WooCommerce Shipping & Tax“ in deinem Store. Derzeit unterstützen wir den weltweiten Versand für Verkäufer in den USA. Wir wissen dein Feedback zu schätzen!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
7.1:
Algunos vendedores de Estados Unidos que usan la extensión WooCommerce Shipping & Tax descubrieron un error al crear etiquetas para pedidos con cantidades de producto con decimales. ¡Ya está arreglado!

¿Quieres probar a crear etiquetas? Instala y activa la extensión WooCommerce Shipping & Tax en tu tienda. Actualmente, está disponible para vendedores en Estados Unidos que hacen envíos internacionales. ¡Agradecemos tu opinión!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
7.1:
Certains commerçants aux États-Unis qui utilisent l’extension WooCommerce Shipping & Tax ont rencontré un bug lors de la création d’étiquettes pour les commandes dont les quantités de produits incluent des valeurs décimales. Ce problème est résolu !

Voulez-vous essayer de créer des étiquettes ? Installez et activez l’extension WooCommerce Shipping & Tax depuis votre boutique. Nous soutenons désormais les commerçants américains qui livrent le monde entier N’hésitez pas à donner votre avis !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
7.1:
חלק מהסוחרים בארה"ב שהשתמשו בהרחבת WooCommerce Shipping & Tax נתקלו בבאגים בזמן יצירת תוויות להזמנות עם כמויות מוצר דצימליות. תיקנו את השגיאה!

רוצה לנסות את אפשרות יצירת תווית? התקן והפעל את הרחבת WooCommerce Shipping & Tax בחנות שלך. בשלב זה אנחנו תומכים בסוחרים בארה"ב המבצעים משלוחים לכל העולם. נשמח לשמוע מה דעתך!
</iw-IL>
<id>
7.1:
Sebagian penjual di Amerika Serikat yang menggunakan ekstensi WooCommerce Shipping & Tax menemukan bug saat membuat label untuk pesanan dengan jumlah produk desimal. Ini sudah teratasi.

Ingin coba membuat label pesanan? Instal dan aktifkan ekstensi WooCommerce Shipping & Tax di toko Anda. Saat ini, kami mendukung penjual di Amerika Serikat yang ingin mengirim produk ke seluruh dunia. Kami pasti mendengar masukan Anda.
</id>
<it-IT>
7.1:
Alcuni venditori negli USA che utilizzano l'estensione WooCommerce Shipping & Tax hanno visualizzato un bug durante la creazione di etichette per ordini con quantità di prodotto decimali.  È stato risolto.

Vuoi provare la creazione di etichette? Installa e attiva l'estensione WooCommerce Shipping & Tax nel tuo negozio. In questo momento, supportiamo i commercianti negli USA che spediscono in tutto il mondo. Accogliamo volentieri il tuo feedback.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
7.1:
WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 拡張機能を使用している米国の一部のマーチャントで、小数点のある商品数量の注文にラベルを作成する際にバグが発生していました。 この問題を修正しました。

ラベルの作成を試す場合は、 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 拡張機能をストアにインストールして有効化します。 現在、世界中に配送する米国のマーチャントに対応しています。 フィードバックをお待ちしております。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
7.1:
WooCommerce 배송 및 세금 확장 기능을 사용하는 미국의 일부 판매자가 주문에 대한 레이블을 생성할 때 제품 수량에 소수점을 사용하면 버그가 발생했습니다. 해당 버그를 수정했습니다!

레이블을 생성해 보시겠어요? 스토어에 WooCommerce 배송 및 세금 확장 기능을 설치하고 활성화하세요. 미국 내 판매자의 전 세계 배송이 곧바로 지원됩니다. 피드백을 보내주세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
7.1:
Enkele verkopers in de VS die gebruikmaakten van de extensie WooCommerce Shipping en Tax liepen tegen een bug aan bij het aanmaken van labels voor bestellingen met productaantallen in decimalen. Dat is nu verholpen!

Wil je labels aanmaken? Installeer en activeer de extensie WooCommerce Shipping en Tax in je winkel. Op dit moment ondersteunen we verkopers in de VS die wereldwijd verzenden. We horen graag je feedback!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
7.1:
Alguns comerciantes nos EUA que usam a extensão WooCommerce Shipping & Tax perceberam um bug ao criar etiquetas para pedidos com quantidades decimais de produtos. Já foi corrigido!

Quer experimentar a criação de etiquetas? Instale e ative a extensão WooCommerce Shipping & Tax na sua loja. No momento, oferecemos suporte a comerciantes nos EUA que enviam produtos para todo o mundo. Adoraríamos receber seu feedback!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
7.1:
Некоторые продавцы в США, пользующиеся расширением WooCommerce Shipping & Tax, сталкивались с ошибкой при создании этикеток для заказов, количество товара в которых было выражено дробным числом. Эта ошибка исправлена.

Хотите попробовать создать этикетку? Установите и активируйте расширение WooCommerce Shipping & Tax в своём магазине. В настоящее время мы поддерживаем продавцов из США, осуществляющих доставку по всему миру. Ждем ваших отзывов!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
7.1:
Vissa handlare i USA som använde WooCommerce Shipping & Tax-utökningen noterade ett fel när de skapade etiketter för beställningar med produktkvantiteter innehållande decimaler. Detta har åtgärdats!

Vill du prova att skapa etiketter? Installera och aktivera WooCommerce Shipping & Tax-utökningen i din butik. För tillfället stöder vi handlare i USA med frakt över hela världen. Vi välkomnar din feedback!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
7,1:
WooCommerce Shipping & Tax uzantısını kullanan ABD'deki bazı satıcılar, ürün sayıları ondalık işaretli olan siparişler için etiket oluştururken bir hata ile karşılaşıyordu. Ve bu hata giderildi!

Etiket oluşturmayı denemek ister misiniz? Dükkanınızda WooCommerce Shipping & Tax uzantısını indirerek etkinleştirin.  Şu anda, ABD'den tüm dünyaya satış yapan satıcıları destekliyoruz. Geri bildirimleriniz bizim için değerli!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
7.1:
一些美国商家发现，在使用 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 扩展程序创建订单时，如果商品数量带有小数，会遇到错误。 我们修复了这个问题！

想试试标签创建功能吗？ 只要在您的商店中下载并激活 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 扩展程序就可以了。 目前，我们支持美国商家发货到全球地址。 欢迎大家积极提供反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
7.1:
部分美國商家在使用 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 擴充功能為產品數量有小數點的訂單建立標籤時發現了一個錯誤。 問題現在已經解決！

想要試用標籤建立功能嗎？ 請在你的商店安裝並啟用 WooCommerce Shipping & Tax 擴充功能。 我們現在支援美國商家出貨到世界各地。 歡迎你提供寶貴意見！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
7.1:
Some merchants in the USA using the WooCommerce Shipping & Tax extension saw a bug when creating labels for orders with decimal product quantities. It’s fixed!

Want to give label creation a try? Install and activate the WooCommerce Shipping & Tax extension in your store. Right now, we support merchants in the USA shipping worldwide. We welcome your feedback!
</en-US>
