<ar>
16.2:
مرحبًا بك في آخر تحديث من تطبيق WooCommerce الخاص بنا للهاتف المحمول! إننا متحمسون للكشف عن قسم المدفوعات والعملاء المُعاد تصميمه، ما يعزز سير عمل إنشاء الطلب الخاص بك. يتماشى هذا التحديث مع مواصفات التصميم الخاصة بنا، ما يسهّل إدخال المبالغ المخصصة. استمتع بتجربة أكثر سهولة وملائمة للمستخدم. تحديث الآن!
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.2:
Es gibt ein neues Update an unserer WooCommerce-Mobil-App! Wir freuen uns, dich über die Umgestaltung des Zahlungs- und Kundenabschnitts zu informieren, wodurch der Workflow bei der Bestellerstellung optimiert wird. Dieses Update wurde im Einklang mit unseren Designspezifikationen vorgenommen und erleichtert die Eingabe individueller Beträge. Profitiere von einem intuitiveren, benutzerfreundlichen Erlebnis. Führe jetzt ein Update durch!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
16,2:
Te damos la bienvenida a la última actualización de nuestra aplicación móvil de WooCommerce. Nos complace presentar una sección de pagos y clientes rediseñada, que mejora el flujo de trabajo de creación de pedidos. Esta actualización se ajusta a nuestras especificaciones de diseño, lo que facilita la introducción de importes personalizados. Disfruta de una experiencia más intuitiva y fácil de usar. ¡Mejora tu plan ahora!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
16.2 :
Bienvenue dans la dernière mise à jour de notre application mobile WooCommerce ! Nous sommes ravis de vous dévoiler la nouvelle section Paiements et Clients qui a subi une refonte, votre flux de création de commande s’en trouve amélioré. Cette mise à jour correspond à nos spécifications en matière de design, il est donc plus facile de saisir des montants personnalisés. Profitez d’une expérience plus intuitive et plus conviviale. Mettez à jour dès maintenant !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.2:
ברוך בואך לגרסה העדכנית ביותר של WooCommerce! We're excited to unveil a redesigned Payments and Customers section, enhancing your order creation workflow. This update aligns with our design specifications, making it easier to input custom amounts. Enjoy a more intuitive, user-friendly experience. Update now!
</iw-IL>
<id>
16.2:
Selamat datang di pembaruan terkini aplikasi seluler WooCommerce! Kami meluncurkan desain baru di bagian Pembayaran dan Pelanggan untuk menyempurnakan alur kerja pembuatan pesanan. Pembaruan ini sesuai dengan spesifikasi desain kami sehingga mempermudah Anda memasukkan jumlah kustom. Nikmati pengalaman yang lebih intuitif dan ramah pengguna. Perbarui sekarang!
</id>
<it-IT>
16.2:
Ti diamo il benvenuto all'ultimo aggiornamento dell'app WooCommerce per dispositivi mobili. Siamo felici di presentare una sezione Pagamenti e Clienti riprogettata, che migliora il flusso di lavoro per la creazione degli ordini. Questo aggiornamento è in linea con le nostre specifiche di progettazione, che semplificano l'inserimento di importi personalizzati. Goditi un'esperienza più intuitiva e facile da usare. Aggiorna ora.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.2:
WooCommerce モバイルアプリの最新アップデートへようこそ ! 注文作成のワークフローを強化する、再設計された「支払いと顧客」セクションを発表いたします。 このアップデートは当社の設計仕様に準拠しており、カスタム金額の入力が容易になります。 より直感的で使いやすい操作環境でぜひご利用ください。 今すぐアップデートしましょう !
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.2:
우커머스 모바일 앱 최신 업데이트에 오신 것을 환영합니다! 주문 생성 워크플로우 개선을 위해 다시 디자인된 결제 및 고객 섹션을 공개합니다. 이 업데이트는 저희의 디자인 사양과 연계되어 사용자 정의 금액을 입력하기 더욱 쉽습니다. 더욱 직관적이고 사용자 친화적인 환경을 이용하세요. 지금 업데이트하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.2:
Welkom bij de nieuwste update van WooCommerce! We're excited to unveil a redesigned Payments and Customers section, enhancing your order creation workflow. This update aligns with our design specifications, making it easier to input custom amounts. Enjoy a more intuitive, user-friendly experience. Update now!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.2:
Esta é a atualização mais recente do aplicativo móvel do WooCommerce! Temos o prazer de revelar a repaginação das seções Pagamentos e Clientes, aprimorando seu fluxo de criação do pedido. Esta atualização está alinhada às nossas especificações de design, o que facilita inserir valores personalizados. Desfrute de uma experiência mais intuitiva e fácil de usar. Atualize agora mesmo!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.2:
Представляем очередное обновление мобильного приложения WooCommerce! Мы рады представить вам обновлённые разделы «Платежи» и «Клиенты». Они позволят вам оптимизировать процесс создания заказов. Это обновление соответствует нашим требованиям к дизайну и упрощает введение индивидуальных сумм. Приложение стало ещё понятнее, а работа с ним — ещё приятнее. Надеемся, что обновления вам понравятся!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.2:
Välkommen till den senaste uppdateringen av vår WooCommerce-mobilapp. Vi är glada över att kunna presentera omdesignade versioner av sektionerna Betalningar och Kunder, vilka kommer att förbättra ditt arbetsflöde vid beställningsskapande. Den här uppdateringen är i linje med våra designspecifikationer, vilket gör det lättare att mata in anpassade belopp. Ta del av en mer intuitiv, användarvänlig upplevelse. Uppdatera nu.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.2:
WooCommerce mobil uygulamamızın en yeni güncellemesine hoş geldiniz! Sipariş oluşturma iş akışınızı geliştiren, yeniden tasarlanmış bir Ödemeler ve Müşteriler bölümünü tanıtmaktan heyecan duyuyoruz. Bu güncelleme tasarım özelliklerimizle uyumlu olduğundan özel tutarlar girmenizi kolaylaştırır. Daha sezgisel ve kullanıcı dostu bir deneyimin keyfini çıkarın. Hemen güncelleyin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.2：
欢迎使用我们的最新版 WooCommerce 移动应用程序！ 我们很高兴推出经过重新设计的“付款和客户”部分，以改进您的订单创建工作流。 本次更新符合我们的设计规范，能够帮助用户更简便地输入自定义金额。 享受更加直观、人性化的用户体验。 立即更新！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.2:
歡迎來到 WooCommerce 行動應用程式的最新更新！ 我們很高興推出重新設計的「付款」和「顧客」區段，協助你改善建立訂單的工作流程。 這項更新符合我們的設計規格，讓輸入自訂金額更加方便。 希望你能享受更直覺易懂、簡單好用的體驗。 立即更新！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
16.2:
Welcome to the latest update of our WooCommerce mobile app! We're excited to unveil a redesigned Payments and Customers section, enhancing your order creation workflow. This update aligns with our design specifications, making it easier to input custom amounts. Enjoy a more intuitive, user-friendly experience. Update now!
</en-US>
