<ar>
6.3:
يوفِّر تطبيق WooCommerce المتوافق مع نظام تشغيل Android 6.3 تحديثين مهمين للمستخدمين:

- يمكنك الآن تضمين عبارة "قابل للتنزيل" في تفاصيل نوع المنتج إن أمكن.
- أصلحنا خطأ بحيث تظهر حالة طلب العميل بشكل صحيح الآن في تفاصيل الطلب.

</ar>
<de-DE>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3 hält zwei wichtige Updates bereit:

- Falls zutreffend kannst du jetzt in den Produktdetails „Zum Herunterladen“ angeben.
- Wir haben einen Fehler behoben, sodass der Status einzelner Bestellungen jetzt korrekt unter den Bestelldetails angezeigt wird.

</de-DE>
<es-ES>
6.3:
WooCommerce para Android 6.3 ofrece a los usuarios dos mejoras importantes:

- Cuando proceda, ya puedes incluir "descargable" en los detalles del tipo de producto.
- Hemos solucionado un error para que el estado de los pedidos personalizados aparezca correctamente en los detalles del pedido.

</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
6.3 :
WooCommerce Android 6.3 propose aux utilisateurs deux mises à jour importantes :

- Le cas échéant, vous pouvez désormais inclure « téléchargeable » dans les détails de type d’un produit.
- Nous avons résolu un bug afin que l’état d’une commande personnalisée s’affiche désormais correctement dans les détails de la commande.

</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
6.3:
גרסת 6.3 של WooCommerce ל-Android כוללת שני עדכונים חשובים למשתמשים:

- אם רלוונטי, אפשר להוסיף אפשרות 'להורדה' בפרטי הסוג של המוצר.
- תיקנו באג כדי לוודא שסטטוס ההזמנה המותאם מופיע כעת בצורה תקינה בפרטי ההזמנה.

</iw-IL>
<id>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3 memberikan dua pembaruan penting untuk pengguna:

- Jika dibutuhkan, sekarang Anda dapat menyertakan “bahan unduhan” pada detail tipe produk.
- Kami telah memperbaiki bug sehingga status pesanan khusus ditampilkan dengan benar pada detail pesanan.

</id>
<it-IT>
6.3:
WooCommerce per Android 6.3 offre agli utenti due importanti aggiornamenti:

- Se applicabile, puoi ora includere "scaricabile" nei dettagli del tipo di prodotto.
- Abbiamo risolto un bug in modo che lo stato di un ordine personalizzato ora venga visualizzato correttamente nei dettagli dell'ordine.

</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3に2つの重要なアップデートがあります : 

- 該当する場合は、商品のタイプの詳細に「ダウンロード可能」を含めることが可能になりました。
- カスタム注文のステータスが注文の詳細に正確に表示されるようバグを修正しました。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3에서 다음 두 가지 중요한 업데이트를 사용자에게 제공합니다.

- 업데이트를 적용하면 상품 유형 상세 정보에 "다운로드 가능"이라는 표시를 포함할 수 있습니다.
- 이제 주문 상세 정보에 사용자 정의 주문의 상태가 올바르게 표시되도록 버그를 수정했습니다.

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3 bevat twee belangrijke updates:

- Indien van toepassing, kan je nu 'downloadbaar’ toevoegen aan de informatie van het producttype.
- We hebben een bug verholpen zodat de status van een aangepaste bestelling nu correct wordt weergegeven in de bestellingsgegevens.

</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
6.3:
O WooCommerce para Android 6.3 conta com duas atualizações importantes:

- Se aplicável, agora é possível incluir "pode ser baixado" nos detalhes de tipo de um produto.
- Corrigimos um bug e agora o status de pedidos personalizados é exibido corretamente nos detalhes do pedido.

</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
6.3:
Доступно два важных обновления WooCommerce 6.3 для Android:

— Теперь в сведениях о типе можно указать, что товар является загружаемым (если применимо).
— Исправлена ошибка, благодаря чему статус заказа клиента отображается корректно в сведениях о заказе.

</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
6.3:
Med WooCommerce Android 6.3 får användare två viktiga uppdateringar:

– Vid behov kan du nu inkludera "nedladdningsbar" i typinformationen för en produkt.
– Vi åtgärdade en bugg så att en status för en anpassad order nu visas korrekt i orderinformationen.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3 kullanıcılara iki önemli güncelleme sunuyor:

- Mümkünse, artık bir ürünün tür ayrıntılarına "indirilebilir" ifadesini ekleyebilirsiniz.
- Özel bir siparişin durumunun sipariş ayrıntılarında doğru şekilde görüntülenmesini önleyen bir hatayı düzelttik.

</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
6.3：
WooCommerce Android 6.3 为用户提供了两个重要更新：

- 如果适用，您现在可以在产品的类型详情中包括“可下载”。
- 我们修复了一个错误，以便现在可以在订单详情中正确显示自定义订单的状态。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
6.3：
WooCommerce Android 6.3 版為使用者提供兩項重要更新：

- 在適用情況下，你現在可以在產品類型詳細資料中提供「可下載」內容。
- 修正錯誤，現在自訂訂單詳細資料中會正確顯示訂單狀態。

</zh-TW>
<en-US>
6.3:
WooCommerce Android 6.3 offers users two important updates: 

 - If applicable, you can now include “downloadable” in the type details of a product.
 - We fixed a bug so that a custom order’s status now displays correctly in order details.
 
</en-US>
