<ar>
16.1:
اكتشف تجربة WooCommerce أكثر سلاسة مع آخر تحديث لدينا! طرحنا ميزة جديدة تسمح لك بإدخال مبالغ مخصصة في أثناء إنشاء الطلب، ما يوفر لك مرونة أكبر. أيضًا، عززنا معالجة الأخطاء لدينا لتسهيل ميزة Jetpack Connection، لا سيما عند استخدام عنوان URL للمسؤول مخصص. استمتع بتطبيق أكثر انسيابية وكفاءة، ومصصم من أجل راحتك.
</ar>
<de-DE>
16.1:
Mit unserem neuesten Update profitierst du von einem nahtloseren WooCommerce-Erlebnis! Wir haben eine neue Funktion eingeführt, durch die du während der Bestellerstellung individuelle Beträge eingeben kannst. Damit bist du flexibler. Außerdem haben wir die Fehlerbehandlung verbessert, um dir eine reibungslosere Jetpack-Verbindung bereitzustellen, besonders bei der Verwendung einer individuellen Admin-URL. Profitiere von einer optimierten und effizienteren App, die dir das Leben leichter machen wird.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
16.1:
Descubre una experiencia de WooCommerce más fluida con nuestra última actualización. Hemos añadido una nueva función que te permite introducir cantidades personalizadas durante la creación del pedido, lo que te proporciona una mayor flexibilidad. También hemos mejorado nuestra gestión de errores para una conexión de Jetpack más fluida, especialmente cuando se utiliza una URL de administración personalizada. Disfruta de una aplicación más ágil y eficaz, diseñada para tu comodidad.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
16.1 :
Découvrez et profitez d’une expérience WooCommerce encore plus fluide avec notre dernière mise à jour ! Nous avons introduit une nouvelle fonctionnalité qui vous permet de saisir des montants personnalisés lors de la création de commande, pour une plus grande flexibilité. Par ailleurs, nous avons amélioré la gestion des erreurs pour une connexion à Jetpack plus fluide, en particulier lorsque vous utilisez une URL administrateur personnalisée. Profitez d’une application plus rationalisée et efficace, conçue pour votre confort.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
16.1:
ליהנות מחוויית שימוש חלקה יותר ב-WooCommerce בעקבות העדכון האחרון! הוספנו כלי חדש, שיאפשר לך להזין סכומים בהתאמה אישית בתהליך יצירת הזמנה, כך שתהיה לך יותר גמישות. בנוסף, שיפרנו את הטיפול בשגיאות ועכשיו חיבור Jetpack חלק יותר, בייחוד דרך כתובת URL מותאמת אישית למנהל/ת המערכת. נהנים מאפליקציה משוכללת ויעילה יותר, שתוכננה לנוחותך.
</iw-IL>
<id>
16.1:
Nikmati kemudahan pengalaman WooCommerce dengan pembaruan terkini kami! Kami memperkenalkan fitur baru yang membuat Anda makin bebas memasukkan jumlah khusus saat membuat pesanan. Penanganan error kami juga makin sempurna agar Jetpack Connection makin lancar, terutama saat URL admin khusus digunakan. Nikmati aplikasi yang makin praktis dan efisien yang didesain untuk kenyamanan Anda.
</id>
<it-IT>
16.1:
Scopri un'esperienza WooCommerce più fluida con il nostro ultimo aggiornamento. Abbiamo introdotto una nuova funzionalità che consente di inserire importi personalizzati durante la creazione dell'ordine, offrendoti maggiore flessibilità. Inoltre, abbiamo migliorato la gestione degli errori per una connessione a Jetpack più fluida, soprattutto quando si utilizza un URL di amministrazione personalizzato. Goditi un'app più semplice ed efficiente, progettata per la tua comodità.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
16.1:
最新のアップデートで、よりシームレスになった WooCommerce の操作環境をご確認ください。 注文作成時にカスタム金額を入力できる新機能を導入し、柔軟性が大幅に向上しました。 また、特にカスタム管理 URL を使用する場合に、Jetpack 連携がよりスムーズになるようにエラー処理を強化しました。 利便性を考慮して設計され、よりスムーズに効率的になったアプリをご利用ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
16.1:
최신 업데이트와 함께 더욱 원활해진 우커머스 환경을 만나 보세요! 주문 생성 중에 사용자 정의 금액을 입력할 수 있는 새로운 기능을 도입하여 유연성을 높였습니다. 또한, 특히 사용자 정의 관리 URL을 사용할 때 젯팩 연결을 더 원활하게 사용할 수 있도록 오류 처리를 강화했습니다. 편의를 위해 설계되어 더 간소화되고 효율적인 앱을 즐겨보세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
16.1:
Ontdek een meer vloeiende WooCommerce-ervaring met onze laatste update! We hebben een nieuwe functie geïntroduceerd waarmee je aangepaste bedragen kunt invoeren tijdens het aanmaken van bestellingen, wat zorgt voor meer flexibiliteit. We hebben ook onze foutverwerking verbeterd voor een vloeiendere Jetpack-verbinding, met name wanneer er een aangepaste beheerders-URL wordt gebruikt. Geniet van een meer gestroomlijnde en efficiënte app, ontworpen voor jouw gemak.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
16.1:
Descubra uma experiência WooCommerce mais uniforme com nossa atualização mais recente. Introduzimos um nova funcionalidade, que permite inserir valores personalizados durante a criação do pedido, proporcionando maior flexibilidade. Além disso, aprimoramos nosso tratamento de erros para permitir uma conexão mais suave com o Jetpack, especialmente ao usar uma URL de administrador personalizada. Desfrute de um aplicativo mais simples e eficiente, projetado para sua conveniência.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
16.1:
Наше очередное обновление поможет сделать работу с WooCommerce ещё удобнее! Мы внедрили новую функцию, которая позволит вводить индивидуальные суммы в процессе создания заказа, что существенно расширит ваши возможности. Кроме того, мы усовершенствовали обработку ошибок, чтобы обеспечить более плавное подключение Jetpack, особенно при использовании индивидуального URL-адреса администратора. Надеемся, что вам понравится оптимизированное, эффективное приложение, созданное специально для того, чтобы вам было удобно работать.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
16.1:
Upptäck en smidigare WooCommerce-upplevelse med vår senaste uppdatering! Vi har infört en ny funktion som gör det möjligt för dig att ange anpassade belopp när du skapar en order, vilket ger dig större flexibilitet. Vi har också förbättrat vår felhantering för en smidigare Jetpack-anslutning, särskilt när du använder en anpassad admin-URL. Upplev en mer strömlinjeformad och effektiv app, utformad för att underlätta för dig.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
16.1:
En yeni güncellememizle daha sorunsuz bir WooCommerce deneyimini keşfedin! Sipariş oluşturma sırasında özel tutar girebileceğiniz, böylece size daha fazla esneklik sağlayan yeni bir özelliği kullanıma sunduk. Ayrıca, özellikle özel yönetici URL'si kullanırken daha kolay Jetpack Bağlantısı için hata işlememizi geliştirdik. Size kolaylık olması için tasarlanan daha kolaylaştırılmış ve verimli bir uygulamanın keyfini çıkarın.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
16.1：
了解最新更新带来的更无缝的 WooCommerce 体验！ 我们引入了一项新功能，使您可以在订单创建期间输入自定义金额，为您提供了更大的灵活性。 此外，我们还增强了错误处理能力，使 Jetpack 连接更加顺畅，尤其是在使用自定义管理员 URL 的情况下。 请尽情体验更简洁高效的 WooCommerce 应用程序，感受为您提供的专属便利。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
16.1:
透過我們的最新更新探索更流暢的 WooCommerce 體驗！ 我們已推出一項新功能，可讓您在建立訂單時輸入自訂金額，讓你操作更加靈活。 此外，我們還改良了錯誤處理功能，使得 Jetpack 連線更順暢 (尤其是在使用自訂管理 URL 時)。 享受更簡潔有效率的應用程式，專為了讓你使用方便而打造。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
16.1:
Discover a more seamless WooCommerce experience with our latest update! We've introduced a new feature allowing you to input custom amounts during order creation, providing you with greater flexibility. Also, we've enhanced our error handling for a smoother Jetpack Connection, especially when using a custom admin URL. Enjoy a more streamlined and efficient app, designed for your convenience.
</en-US>
