<ar>
8.1:
لقد حصلت علامة تبويب الطلبات على تحديث يتضمن هذا الإصدار. اختفت علامات التبويب الآن، ولقد منحناك عامل تصفية حسب خيار الحالة أو نطاق التاريخ. يعتمد هذا على ملاحظاتك المباشرة على مدار السنين، ونعلم أنك ستحب التغيير!
</ar>
<de-DE>
8.1:
Der Tab „Bestellungen“ wurde in dieser Version aktualisiert. Wir haben die Tabs entfernt und stattdessen eine Option zum Filtern nach Status oder Zeitraum hinzugefügt. Diese Änderung basiert auf jahrelangem Feedback der Benutzer. Deshalb wissen wir, dass sie dir gefallen wird!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
8.1:
Con esta versión, se ha actualizado la pestaña de pedidos. Las pestañas ya no están, y te ofrecemos la opción de filtrar por estado o por rango de fechas. Este cambio se lleva a cabo a raíz de los comentarios directos que hemos recibido a lo largo de los años, así que estamos seguros de que te gustará.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
8.1 :
L’onglet Commandes a fait peau neuve ! À la place des onglets, vous pouvez désormais filtrer les commandes par état ou plage de dates. Cette mise à jour tient compte des commentaires que vous avez formulés au fil des ans. Elle va vous plaire.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
8.1:
עדכנו את לשונית ההזמנות בגרסה החדשה. הלשוניות לא קיימות עוד והוספנו אפשרות לסנן לפי סטטוס או טווח תאריכים. השינוי בוצע בהתאם למשוב שקיבלנו ממשתמשים במהלך השנים ואנחנו בטוחים שהעדכון ימצא חן בעיניך!
</iw-IL>
<id>
8.1:
Melalui rilis ini, tab pesanan akan diperbarui. Sekarang tab sudah dihilangkan, dan kami memberi Anda penyaring berdasarkan status atau pilihan rentang tanggal. Pembaruan ini didasarkan pada feedback langsung Anda, dan kami tahu Anda akan menyukai perubahan ini! 
</id>
<it-IT>
8.1:
È stato effettuato un aggiornamento della scheda degli ordini a questa versione. Le schede ora sono sparite e ti abbiamo fornito un filtro per stato oppure l'opzione per intervallo di date. Alla base di ciò c'è il feedback diretto che ci hai inviato nel corso degli anni e sappiamo che ti piacerà la modifica.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
8.1:
このリリースでは注文タブが更新されました。  タブがなくなり、ステータスや日付範囲のオプションでフィルタリングできるようになりました。 これは長年にわたるお客様からの直接のフィードバックに基づくもので、皆さまにはこの変更を気に入っていただけると思います。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
8.1:
이 릴리스를 통해 주문 탭이 업데이트되었습니다. 이제는 탭이 사라지고 상태 또는 날짜 범위별 필터링 옵션이 제공됩니다. 수년간의 직접적인 피드백을 반영했으며, 마음에 드실 것으로 생각합니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
8.1:
Het bestellingentabblad is in deze versie bijgewerkt. De tabbladen zijn nu weggehaald. We hebben de optie gegeven om te filteren op status of binnen een datumbereik. We hebben dit op basis van jullie feedback van de afgelopen jaren gedaan, dus we verwachten dat deze update met open armen wordt onthaald!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
8.1:
A guia de pedidos recebeu uma atualização nesta versão. Agora, as guias não existem mais, e você tem a opção de filtrar por status ou intervalo de datas. Essa decisão foi baseada no seu feedback direto, ao longo dos anos. Temos certeza de que você vai adorar a mudança!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
8.1:
В этом выпуске обновлена вкладка заказов. Теперь вкладки исчезли и мы предоставили вам возможность фильтровать заказы по статусу или диапазону дат. Пользователи долгое время сами просили об этом, поэтому мы уверены, что вы оцените это изменение!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
8.1:
Beställningsfliken har fått en uppdatering i den här version. Flikarna är nu borta och vi har skapat ett alternativ för att filtrera efter status eller datumintervall. Denna ändring är baserad på direkt feedback från er genom åren och vi vet att du kommer att gilla den!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
8.1:
Siparişler sekmesi bu sürümde güncellendi. Sekmeleri kaldırdık ve duruma veya tarih aralığına göre filtreleme seçeneğini sunduk. Bu değişikliği yıllardır sizden aldığımız geri bildirimlere göre yaptık. Beğeneceğinizi biliyoruz!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
8.1：
本版本中更新了“订单”选项卡。 选项卡现已被删除，但我们为您提供了按状态或日期范围选项进行筛选的过滤器。 此项更改基于多年来的用户直接反馈，因此我们知道您会喜欢的！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
8.1：
此版本更新了訂單分頁。 我們現已移除這些分頁，並提供篩選功能，讓你根據狀態或日期範圍選項進行篩選。 我們參考了各位在這些年來直接提供的意見回饋，相信你會喜歡這項變更！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
8.1:
The orders tab has gotten an update with this release. The tabs are now gone, and we’ve given you a filter by status or date range option. This is based upon your direct feedback over the years, and we know you’ll like the change!
</en-US>
