<ar>
13.9:
لقد طرحنا ميزة جديدة تسمح لك بالبحث عن المنتجات بواسطة وحدة SKU في شاشة محدّد المنتجات، ما يسهّل العثور على العناصر التي تبحث عنها. ترجى تجربته ومشاركة ملاحظاتك!
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.9:
Wir haben eine neue Funktion eingeführt, mit der du im Produktauswahlbildschirm Produkte nach ihrer SKU suchen kannst. So ist es noch einfacher, das zu finden, was du suchst. Probiere es aus und teile uns dein Feedback mit!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
13.9:
Hemos introducido una nueva función que te permite buscar productos por SKU en la pantalla del selector de productos, lo cual hace que sea más fácil que encuentres los elementos que buscas. Pruébala y déjanos tus comentarios.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
13.9 :
Pour simplifier davantage la recherche des articles qui vous intéressent, nous avons introduit une nouvelle fonctionnalité de recherche des produits par UGS dans l'écran du sélecteur de produits. Faites le test et dites-nous ce que vous en pensez !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.9:
השקנו אפשרות חדשה שבעזרתה ניתן לחפש מוצרים לפי SKU במסך של בוחר המוצרים, כדי לעזור לך למצוא את הפריטים שברצונך לחפש. נשמח לקבל משוב אחרי שניסית אותה!
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.9:
Kami memperkenalkan sebuah fitur baru untuk mencari produk berdasarkan SKU di layar pemilihan produk, sehingga Anda lebih mudah menemukan item yang dicari. Cobalah dan berikan feedback Anda!
</id>
<it-IT>
13.9:
Abbiamo introdotto una nuova funzionalità che consente di cercare i prodotti per SKU nella schermata di selezione dei prodotti, rendendo ancora più facile trovare gli articoli che stai cercando. Prova l'opzione e condividi il tuo feedback.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.9:
商品選択画面に SKU 別に商品を検索できる新機能を導入し、お探しの商品がさらに見つけやすくなりました。 ぜひお試しいただき、フィードバックをお寄せください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.9:
원하는 아이템을 더 쉽게 찾을 수 있도록 상품 선택 도구 화면에서 SKU로 상품을 검색할 수 있는 새 기능을 도입했습니다. 사용해 보고 피드백을 공유해 주세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.9:
We hebben een nieuwe functie ontwikkeld waarmee je in het scherm voor productselectie door middel van SKU naar producten kan zoeken. Hierdoor is het nog makkelijker om de items te vinden die je zoekt. Probeer het uit en laat weten wat je ervan denkt!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
13.9:
Incluímos uma nova funcionalidade, que permite pesquisar produtos por SKU na tela de seleção de produto. Isso torna ainda mais fácil encontrar os itens que você procura. Experimente e compartilhe seu feedback.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
13.9:
Мы добавили новую функцию, которая позволяет искать товары по артикулам на экране выбора товаров: так находить нужное стало ещё проще. Попробуйте и оставьте отзыв!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.9:
We've introduced a new feature that allows you to search for products by SKU in the product selector screen, making it even easier to find the items you're looking for. Prova och dela din feedback.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.9:
Ürün seçici ekranında ürünleri SKU'ya göre aramayabilmenizi sağlayan ve böylece aradığınız ürünleri bulmanızı daha da kolaylaştıran yeni bir özelliği kullanıma sunduk. Lütfen deneyin ve geri bildiriminizi paylaşın!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.9：
我们推出了一项新功能，借助该功能，您可以在产品选择器屏幕上按 SKU 搜索产品，这样可以更容易地找到您要查找的产品。 欢迎试用并分享您的反馈！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.9：
我們推出了全新功能，讓你在商品選擇器畫面中按貨號搜尋商品，更輕鬆找到要尋找的商品。 請務必試用此功能並分享你的意見！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
13.9:
We've introduced a new feature that allows you to search for products by SKU in the product selector screen, making it even easier to find the items you're looking for. Please try it out and share your feedback!
</en-US>
