<ar>
4.9:
- انقر على زر "إرسال الملاحظات" الجديد لإرسال أفكارك واقتراحاتك إلينا في استطلاع رأي CrowdSignal.
- حرِّر تباينات المنتجات كالسعر والوصف والمخزون والرؤية والشحن.
- جرِّب الميزات الجديدة في قسم المنتجات! انتقل إلى الإعدادات لتمكينها.

</ar>
<de-DE>
4.9:
- Tippe in einer CrowdSignal-Umfrage auf den neuen Button „Feedback senden“, um deine Ideen und Vorschläge an uns zu senden.
- Bearbeite Produktvarianten wie Preis, Beschreibung, Bestand, Sichtbarkeit und Versand.
- Experimentiere mit neuen Funktionen im Abschnitt „Produkte“! Navigiere zu „Einstellungen“, um sie zu aktivieren.

</de-DE>
<fr-FR>
4.9 :
- Appuyez sur le nouveau bouton Envoyer un commentaire pour nous envoyer vos idées et suggestions dans une étude CrowdSignal.
- Modifiez les variantes du produit, comme le prix, la description, le stock, la visibilité et la livraison.
- Testez les nouvelles fonctionnalités dans la section Produits ! Allez dans Réglages pour les activer.

</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
4.9:
 - ניתן להקיש על הכפתור החדש 'לשלוח משוב' כדי לשלוח לנו רעיונות והצעות באמצעות סקר של CrowdSignal.
- ניתן לערוך פרטים של סוגי מוצר, כגון מחיר, תיאור, מלאי, נראות ומשלוח.
- אפשר להתנסות בתכונות חדשות במקטע המוצרים! יש לעבור ל'הגדרות' כדי להפעיל אותן.

</iw-IL>
<id>
4.9:
- Ketuk tombol Kirim Masukan untuk mengirim ide dan saran Anda kepada kami di survei CrowdSignal.
- Sunting variasi produk seperti harga, deskripsi, persediaan, visibilitas, dan pengiriman.
- Bereksperimen dengan fitur baru di bagian Produk! Buka Pengaturan untuk mengaktifkannya.

</id>
<it-IT>
4.9:
- Tocca il nuovo pulsante Invia feedback per inviarci le tue idee e i tuoi suggerimenti mediante un'indagine CrowdSignal.
- Modifica le varianti di prodotto come prezzo, descrizione, inventario, visibilità e spedizione.
- Prova le nuove funzionalità nella sezione Prodotti. Vai alle Impostazioni per abilitarle.

</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
4.9:
- 新しい「意見を送る」ボタンをタップし、CrowdSignal のアンケートでご意見やご提案をお寄せください。
- 価格、説明、在庫、公開状態、配送などの商品のバリエーションを編集します。
-「商品」セクションの新しい機能をお試しください ! 有効にするには「設定」に移動します。

</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
4.9:
- CrowdSignal 설문 조사에서 새롭게 추가된 '피드백 보내기' 버튼을 탭하여 저희에게 아이디어와 의견을 제출해주세요.
- 가격, 설명, 재고, 가시성, 배송과 같은 제품 선택사항을 편집하세요.
- '제품' 섹션에서 기능을 사용해보세요! 기능을 활성화하려면 '설정'으로 이동하세요.

</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
4.9:
- Tik op de nieuwe knop Feedback verzenden om je ideeën en suggesties met ons te delen via een CrowdSignal-enquête.
- Bewerk productvariaties zoals prijs, beschrijving, voorraad, zichtbaarheid en verzending.
- Experimenteer met nieuwe functies in het gedeelte Producten! Ga naar Instellingen om ze in te schakelen.

</nl-NL>
<ru-RU>
4,9:
- Нажмите кнопку «Отправить отзыв», чтобы поделиться идеями и предложениями в опросе CrowdSignal.
- Вы можете редактировать такие параметры товара, как цена, описание, наличие на складе, видимость и доставка.
- Испытайте новые возможности в разделе «Товары»! Чтобы включить их, перейдите в раздел «Настройки».

</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
4.9:
- Tryck på den nya knappen Skicka feedback för att skicka dina idéer och förslag till oss i en CrowdSignal-undersökning.
- Redigera produktvariationer som pris, beskrivning, lager, synlighet och frakt.
- Experimentera med nya funktioner i avsnittet Produkter! Gå till Inställningar för att aktivera dem.

</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
4.9:
- Bir CrowdSignal anketiyle fikirlerinizi ve önerilerinizi bize göndermek için yeni Geri Bildirim Gönder düğmesine dokunun.
- Fiyat, açıklama, stok, görünürlük ve gönderim gibi ürün varyasyonlarını düzenleyin.
- Ürünler bölümünde yeni özelliklerle denemeler yapın. Bunları etkinleştirmek için Ayarlar'a gidin.

</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
4.9：
- 轻点新的“发送反馈”按钮，以在 CrowdSignal 调查中向我们提交您的想法和建议。
- 编辑产品变体，如价格、描述、库存、可见性和配送。
- 尝试“产品”部分中的新功能！ 转到“设置”以启用这些功能。

</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
4.9：
- 點選新的「傳送意見回饋」按鈕，即可透過 CrowdSignal 調查傳送想法與建議給我們。
- 編輯商品變化項目資訊，例如價格、說明、庫存、可見度和貨運資訊。
- 體驗「商品」區段的新功能！ 前往「設定」即可啟用這些功能。

</zh-TW>
<en-US>
4.9:
- Tap the new Send Feedback button to submit your ideas and suggestions to us in a CrowdSignal survey.
- Edit product variations like price, description, inventory, visibility, and shipping.
- Experiment with new features in the Products section! Go to Settings to enable them.
 
</en-US>
