<ar>
14.8:
أخبار مثيرة! يمكنك الآن إنشاء قسائم مباشرة داخل التطبيق وتقديم خصومات استثنائية وعروض خاصة إلى عملائك! قمنا بتحسين عملية ربط العملاء بطلباتهم، ما يجعلها أسرع وأكثر فاعلية. قم بتحديث تطبيقك لتجربة هذه التحسينات الجديدة!
</ar>
<de-DE>
14.8:
Tolle Neuigkeiten! Du kannst Gutscheine jetzt direkt in der App erstellen und deinen Kunden exklusive Rabatte und Sonderangebote bieten! Außerdem haben wir das Verknüpfen von Kunden mit ihren Bestellungen einfacher und effizienter gemacht. Aktualisiere deine App, um diese neuen Verbesserungen zu erleben!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
14.8:
¡Buenas noticias! Ahora puedes crear cupones directamente desde la aplicación. Ofrece descuentos exclusivos y ofertas especiales a tus clientes. Hemos mejorado el proceso de vincular a los clientes con sus pedidos, y ahora es más rápido y eficiente. Actualiza la aplicación para probar estas nuevas mejoras.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
14.8:
Grande nouvelle ! Vous pouvez désormais créer des codes promo directement depuis l’application - faites bénéficier à vos clients de remises exclusives ! Nous avons amélioré le processus de liaison entre les clients et leurs commandes, le rendant plus rapide et plus efficace. Mettez à jour votre application pour une expérience améliorée !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
14.8:
יש לנו חדשות מרגשות! כעת אפשר ליצור קופונים ישירות בתוך האפליקציה – ולהציע הנחות בלעדיות והצעות מיוחדות ללקוחות שלך! שיפרנו את התהליך של קישור הלקוחות להזמנות שלהם, כדי ליצור תהליך מהיר ויעיל יותר. כדאי לעדכן את האפליקציה כעת כדי לנסות את השיפורים החדשים!
</iw-IL>
<id>
14.8:
Kabar gembira! Anda kini bisa membuat kupon langsung di aplikasi - berikan diskon dan penawaran eksklusif untuk pelanggan Anda! Kami telah menyempurnakan proses menautkan pelanggan dengan pesanan mereka sehingga kini makin cepat dan efisien.  Perbarui aplikasi untuk mencoba fitur baru ini!
</id>
<it-IT>
14.8:
Notizie straordinarie: ora puoi creare i codici promozionali direttamente all'interno dell'app: sconti esclusivi e offerte speciali per i tuoi clienti! Abbiamo migliorato il processo di collegamento dei clienti ai loro ordini, rendendolo più rapido ed efficiente. Aggiorna l'app per provare questi nuovi miglioramenti.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
14.8:
嬉しいお知らせです ! アプリ内で直接クーポンを作成できるようになり、顧客に限定の割引や特別オファーを提供します。 顧客と注文を結び付けるプロセスを強化し、より迅速かつ効率的にしました。 アプリを更新して、以上の新しい機能強化を体験してください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
14.8:
신나는 소식입니다! 이제는 앱 내에서 바로 쿠폰을 생성할 수 있습니다. 고객에게 특별 할인과 특별 행사를 제공하세요. 고객을 자신의 주문과 연결하는 프로세스를 더 빠르고 더 효율적으로 개선했습니다. 앱을 업데이트하여 이러한 새로운 향상된 기능을 경험하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
14.8:
Spannend nieuws! Je kan nu coupons direct in de app aanmaken. Geef je klanten exclusieve kortingen en speciale aanbiedingen! We hebben het proces voor het koppelen van klanten aan hun bestellingen verbeterd, waardoor het sneller en efficiënter is. Update je app om deze nieuwe verbeteringen te ervaren!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
14.8:
Boas notícias! Agora você pode criar cupons diretamente do app para oferecer descontos exclusivos e ofertas especiais para seus clientes. Aprimoramos o processo de associar clientes aos pedidos, tornando-o mais eficiente e rápido. Atualize o app para experimentar todas essas melhorias!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
14.8:
Отличные новости! Теперь можно создавать купоны непосредственно в приложении и предоставлять клиентам эксклюзивные скидки и специальные предложения. Процесс привязки клиентов к заказам стал быстрее и эффективнее. Обновите приложение, чтобы воспользоваться новыми усовершенствованиями.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
14.8:
Spännande nyheter! Nu kan du skapa kuponger direkt i appen. Erbjud exklusiva rabatter och specialerbjudanden till dina kunder! Vi har förbättrat processen med att länka kunder till sina beställningar så att den är snabbare och mer effektiv. Uppdatera appen och upplev de här nya förbättringarna!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
14.8:
Heyecan verici haberlerimiz var! Artık kuponlarınızı doğrudan uygulama üzerinden oluşturabilirsiniz ve müşterilerinize ayrıcalıklı indirim ve özel teklifler sunabilirsiniz! Müşterileri siparişlerine bağlama sürecini daha hızlı ve etkili olacak şekilde geliştirdik. Bu yeni geliştirmeleri deneyimlemek için uygulamanızı güncelleştirin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
14.8：
激动人心的消息！ 您现在可以直接在应用程序内创建优惠券，为您的客户提供专属折扣和特别优惠！ 我们优化了连接客户与其订单的流程，使之更快速、更高效。 更新您的应用程序，体验新的增强功能吧！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
14.8:
好消息！ 現在你能直接在應用程式內建立優惠券，為顧客提供獨家折扣和特別優惠！ 我們強化了顧客的訂單連結流程，提升流程的速度和效率。 快更新應用程式，體驗這些全新的增強項目！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
14.8:
Exciting news! You can now create coupons directly within the app - provide exclusive discounts and special offers to your customers! We've enhanced the process of linking customers to their orders, making it quicker and more efficient. Update your app to experience these new enhancements!
</en-US>
