<ar>
17.4:
إننا متحمسون لتقديم الدعم إلى مزوّدي خدمة مفاتيح المرور التابعة لأطراف ثالثة. صمِّم هذا التحديث لتزويد مستخدمي ووردبريس.كوم بمزيد من المرونة والراحة في ما يتعلق بكيفية إدارة الأمان في حسابهم. استعد للتخلص من التعب الناتج عن إدخال كلمات المرور والترحيب بتجربة أكثر سلاسة وأمان عند تسجيل الدخول!
</ar>
<de-DE>
17.4:
Wir freuen uns, Anbieter von Drittanbieter-Passkeys zu unterstützen. Dieses Update wurde entwickelt, um WordPress.com-Benutzern mehr Flexibilität und Komfort beim Verwalten ihrer Kontosicherheit zu bieten. Mach dich bereit – verabschiede dich von ermüdenden Passwörtern und entdecke ein reibungsloseres, sichereres Anmeldeerlebnis!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
17.4:
Nos alegra contarte que ya ofrecemos compatibilidad para otros proveedores de Passkey. Esta actualización está diseñada para que los usuarios de WordPress.com gestionen la seguridad de sus cuentas de forma más versátil y fácil. Despídete del tedio de las contraseñas y prepárate para una experiencia de acceso segura más amena.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
17.4 :
Nous sommes ravis de proposer la prise en charge des fournisseurs tiers de clés d’accès. Grâce à cette mise à jour, les utilisateurs de WordPress.com peuvent gérer la sécurité de leur compte plus commodément et avec une plus grande fluidité. Préparez-vous à dire adieu aux fastidieux mots de passe et à découvrir une connexion fluide et sécurisée !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
17.4:
אנחנו שמחים להציע תמיכה לספקי מפתחות גישה של צד שלישי. העדכון הזה נועד לספק למשתמשי WordPress.com גמישות ונוחות רבות יותר בניהול האבטחה של חשבונם. תכף אפשר יהיה לנטוש את התהליך המייגע של הזנת סיסמה ולעבור לחוויית התחברות חלקה ומאובטחת יותר!
</iw-IL>
<id>
17.4:
Kami senang dapat menyediakan dukungan untuk penyedia Passkey pihak ketiga. Dengan pembaruan ini, pengguna WordPress.com dapat mengelola keamanan akun secara lebih fleksibel dan mudah. Tak perlu menghafal kata sandi. Login lebih lancar dan aman.
</id>
<it-IT>
17.4:
Siamo lieti di offrire il supporto ai fornitori di Passkey di terze parti. Questo aggiornamento è stato progettato per offrire agli utenti di WordPress.com maggiori flessibilità e comodità nella gestione della sicurezza del proprio account. Preparati a dire addio allo stress delle password e a dare il benvenuto a un'esperienza di login più fluida e sicura!
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
17.4:
サードパーティのパスキープロバイダーのサポートをご提供します。 このアップデートは、WordPress.com ユーザーがアカウントのセキュリティをより柔軟かつ便利に管理できるようにするものです。 パスワードに関するストレスに別れを告げ、よりスムーズかつ安全にログインしましょう !
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
17.4:
서드파티 패스키 제공업체 지원을 제공하게 되어 기쁩니다. 이번 업데이트는 워드프레스닷컴 사용자의 계정 보안 관리 방식에 있어 유연성과 편의성을 더할 수 있도록 설계되었습니다. 외우기 힘든 비밀번호에서 벗어나 더욱 원활하고 안전한 로그인 환경을 이용하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
17.4:
We zijn heel enthousiast over onze ondersteuning voor externe passkeyproviders. Deze update biedt gebruikers van WordPress.com meer flexibiliteit en gemak bij het beheren van de beveiliging van hun accounts. Zeg vaarwel tegen wachtwoordmoeheid en bereid je voor op een soepelere, veilige inlogervaring!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
17.4:
Temos o prazer de anunciar a compatibilidade com provedores terceiros de chave de acesso. Esta atualização visa dar mais flexibilidade e praticidade aos usuários do WordPress.com no gerenciamento da segurança de suas contas. Aposente o uso de senhas e desfrute de uma experiência de login segura e mais tranquila.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
17.4:
Мы рады предоставить поддержку сторонних ключей доступа. Это обновление призвано сделать управление безопасностью учётной записи более гибким и удобным для пользователей WordPress.com. Вскоре вы сможете забыть об утомительных паролях и входить в систему без лишних проблем в условиях полной безопасности!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
17.4:
Vi är glada över att kunna erbjuda stöd för tredjepartsleverantörer av säkerhetsnycklar. Den här uppdateringen är utformad för att ge WordPress.com-användare mer flexibilitet och bekvämlighet när de hanterar säkerheten för sina konton. Säg adjö till lösenordströttheten och hej till en smidigare och säkrare inloggningsupplevelse!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
17.4:
Üçüncü taraf Güvenlik Anahtarı sağlayıcıları için destek sunmaktan heyecan duyuyoruz. Bu güncelleme, WordPress.com kullanıcılarının hesaplarının güvenliğini yönetme şekline daha fazla esneklik ve rahatlık sağlamak için tasarlanmıştır. Parolalardan kaynaklanan yorgunluğa elveda demeye ve daha sorunsuz, güvenli bir oturum açma deneyimine merhaba demeye hazırlanın!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
17.4：
我们很高兴能为第三方通行密钥提供商提供支持。 此更新旨在让 WordPress.com 用户能够更灵活、便捷地管理其账户的安全。 准备好告别繁琐的密码输入操作，享受更流畅、安全的登录体验吧！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
17.4:
我們熱切期待提供第三方密碼金鑰供應商支援。 此更新可讓 WordPress.com 使用者在管理帳號安全性時更加靈活便利。 準備好揮別密碼疲勞，迎接更順暢、安全的登入體驗！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
17.4:
We're excited to offer support for third-party Passkey providers. This update is designed to provide WordPress.com users with more flexibility and convenience in how they manage their account's security. Get ready to say goodbye to password fatigue and hello to a smoother, secure login experience!
</en-US>
