<ar>
13.8:
أخبار مثيرة! يمكنك الآن مسح الرمز الشريطي ضوئيًا لمنتج ما عند إنشاء طلب من التطبيق! لا يلزم التمرير يدويًا للبحث عن منتج بعد الآن! لقد أصلحنا أيضًا اثنين من مشكلات التعطل في قائمة الطلبات وشاشات تفاصيل المنتجات. ترجى مواصلة إرسال الملاحظات إلينا – فكلنا آذان صاغية!
</ar>
<de-DE>
13.8:
Tolle Neuigkeiten! Du kannst jetzt den Barcode auf Produkten scannen, wenn du in der App eine Bestellung erstellst. Kein manuelles Scrollen auf der Suche nach Produkten mehr! Außerdem haben wir einige Abstürze in der Bestellliste und im Bildschirm mit den Produktdetails behoben. Sende uns bitte weiter Feedback – wir freuen uns darauf!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
13.8:
¡Buenas noticias! Ahora puedes escanear el código de barras de un producto al crear un pedido desde la aplicación. Ya no tendrás que desplazarte para buscar a mano tus productos. También hemos solucionado un par de problemas de bloqueo en las pantallas de la lista de pedidos y detalles del producto. Sigue enviando tus comentarios: ¡te escuchamos!
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
13.8 :
Grande nouvelle ! Vous pouvez désormais scanner le code-barres d’un produit lorsque vous créez une commande depuis l’application ! Fini les défilements infinis à la recherche d’un produit ! Nous avons également résolu plusieurs incidents dans les écrans de la liste de commandes et des détails sur les produits. Continuez à nous envoyer vos commentaires. Votre avis nous intéresse !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
13.8:
יש לנו חדשות מרגשות! כעת אפשר לסרוק ברקוד של מוצר כאשר יוצרים הזמנה בתוך האפליקציה! כבר אין צורך לגלול כדי לחפש את המוצר! בנוסף, תיקנו כמה בעיות שגרמו לקריסה במסכים של רשימת ההזמנות ופרטי המוצר. נשמח לקבל עוד משוב – אנחנו תמיד כאן כדי להקשיב!
</iw-IL>
<id>
13.8:
Kabar gembira! Sekarang Anda dapat memindai barcode produk sewaktu membuat pesanan dari aplikasi. Tidak perlu lagi repot-repot menggulir layar untuk mencari produk. Kami juga telah memperbaiki beberapa masalah crash di layar daftar pesanan dan detail produk. Mohon terus berikan feedback – kami siap mendengarkan!
</id>
<it-IT>
13.8:
Notizie straordinarie: ora puoi scansionare il codice a barre di un prodotto quando crei un ordine dall'app. Non è più necessario scorrere manualmente per ricercare un prodotto. Abbiamo anche risolto alcuni problemi di arresto anomalo nell'elenco degli ordini e nelle schermate dei dettagli del prodotto. Continua a inviarci feedback: siamo lieti di ascoltarli.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
13.8:
嬉しいお知らせです ! アプリから注文を作成する際に商品のバーコードをスキャンできるようになりました。 今後商品を探す際に手動でスクロールする必要はありません。 さらに注文リスト画面と商品詳細画面のクラッシュの問題もいくつか修正しました。 引き続き、フィードバックをお寄せください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
13.8:
신나는 소식입니다! 이제는 앱에서 주문을 생성할 때 상품 바코드를 스캔할 수 있습니다. 더는 상품 검색에서 수동으로 스크롤할 필요가 없습니다. 주문 목록과 상품 상세 정보 화면의 두세 가지 충돌 문제도 해결했습니다. 계속 피드백을 보내주세요. 경청하겠습니다!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
13.8:
Spannend nieuws! Je kan nu de streepjescode van een product scannen wanneer je in de app een bestelling doet! Je hoeft niet meer handmatig naar het product te scrollen! We hebben ook een aantal problemen met het vastlopen van de schermen bestellijst en productgegevens opgelost. Blijf ons feedback sturen – wij luisteren!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
13.8:
Boa notícia. Agora é possível escanear o código de barras de um produto ao criar um pedido no aplicativo. Você não precisa mais rolar manualmente para buscar um produto. Também corrigimos alguns problemas de travamento na lista de pedidos e nas telas de detalhes do produto. Continue compartilhando seu feedback conosco. Estamos atentos.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
13.8:
Отличные новости! Теперь при создании заказа из приложения можно сканировать штрихкод товара! Больше не нужно прокручивать список товаров вручную! Кроме того, мы исправили некоторые ошибки на экранах списка заказов и сведений о товаре, которые приводили к сбою. Мы по-прежнему ждём ваших отзывов и прислушиваемся к ним!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
13.8:
Spännande nyheter! You can now scan the barcode of a product when creating an order from the app! No need to manually scroll in search of a product anymore! We also fixed a couple of crash issues in the order list and product detail screens. Fortsätt att skicka feedback till oss – vi lyssnar!
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
13.8:
Heyecan verici haberlerimiz var! Artık uygulamadan sipariş oluştururken ürünün barkodunu okutabilirsiniz! Bir ürün ararken artık manuel olarak kaydırmanıza gerek olmaz! Ayrıca sipariş listesindeki ve ürün detayı ekranlarındaki birkaç kilitlenme sorununu da giderdik. Lütfen bize geri bildirim göndermeye devam edin, sizi dinliyoruz.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
13.8：
激动人心的消息！ 在应用程序中创建订单时，您现在可以扫描产品的条形码！ 不再需要手动滚动搜索产品！ 我们还修复了订单列表和产品详情屏幕中的几个崩溃问题。 请继续向我们发送反馈，我们时刻倾听您的意见！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
13.8：
好消息！ 現在透過應用程式建立訂單時，可以直接掃描商品條碼！ 不再需要手動捲動，費力地搜尋商品了！ 我們也已修正訂單清單和商品詳細資料畫面的幾個當機問題。 歡迎繼續給予我們意見回饋，我們很樂意虛心傾聽！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
13.8:
Exciting news! You can now scan the barcode of a product when creating an order from the app! No need to manually scroll in search of a product anymore! We also fixed a couple of crash issues in the order list and product detail screens. Please continue to send us feedback – we are listening!
</en-US>
