<ar>
2.5:
* لقد تعقبنا وأصلحنا: عطلاً نادرًا حدث بعد إنجاز أحد الطلبات وتصغير حجم التطبيق، إلى جانب خطأ تسبب في تبديل الموقع المُحدَّد في منتقي المواقع إلى التحديد السابق مرة أخرى، فضلاً عن بعض المشكلات في واجهة المستخدم التي تحتوي على علامة تبويب "المراجعات" الجديدة.
* يمكنك الآن تضمين أسماء المنتجات في سطرين في شاشة تفاصيل الطلب.
</ar>
<de-DE>
2.5:
* Wir haben folgende Probleme gefunden und behoben: einen seltenen Absturz, der nach dem Erfüllen eines Auftrags und Minimieren der App auftrat, einen Fehler, bei dem die ausgewählte Website in der Websiteauswahl zur vorherigen Auswahl zurückwechselte, und einige Probleme mit der Benutzeroberfläche auf dem neuen Tab „Rezensionen“.
* Produktnamen können jetzt auf dem Bildschirm mit den Bestelldetails in zwei Zeilen geschrieben werden.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
2.5:
* Hemos supervisado y corregido lo siguiente: un error extraño que se producía después de hacer un pedido y minimizar la aplicación, un error que hacía que el sitio seleccionado en el selector de sitios volviera a la selección anterior y algunos problemas de la interfaz de usuario que ocurrían en la nueva pestaña "Revisiones".
* Los nombres de los productos ahora pueden agruparse en dos líneas, en la pantalla Información del pedido.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
2.5 :
* Nous avons détecté et résolu : une défaillance rare qui survenait après l'exécution d'une commande et la réduction de l'application, un bug remplaçant le site sélectionné dans le sélecteur de site par la sélection précédente, ainsi que quelques problèmes d'interface utilisateur avec le nouvel onglet « Avis ».
* Les noms de produit peuvent désormais occuper deux lignes dans l'écran des détails de la commande.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
2.5:
* איתרנו ותיקנו את הבעיות הבאות: קריסה נדירה שהתרחשה לאחר השלמה של הזמנה וצמצום האפליקציה,באג שגרם לאתר שנבחר בבורר האתרים להתחלף לבחירה הקודמת ועוד כמה בעיות בממשק המשתמש בלשונית 'ביקורות' החדשה.
* כעת ניתן לפרסום את שמות המוצרים על שתי שורות במסך של פרטי ההזמנה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
2.5:
* Kami telah menemukan dan memperbaiki: sebuah crash langka yang terjadi setelah memenuhi pesanan dan mengecilkan aplikasi, satu bug yang menyebabkan situs terpilih di pemilih situs beralih kembali ke pilihan sebelumnya, dan beberapa masalah UI di tab “Ulasan” yang baru.
* Nama produk kini dapat dijadikan dua baris dalam layar detail pesanan.
</id>
<it-IT>
2.5:
* Siamo risaliti alle cause e abbiamo risolto: un raro arresto anomalo che si verificava dopo aver evaso un ordine e ridotto a icona l'app, un bug che portava il sito selezionato in Scelta siti a tornare alla selezione precedente e alcuni problemi di interfaccia utente con la nuova scheda "Recensioni".
* I nomi dei prodotti ora possono essere inseriti in due righe nella schermata dei dettagli dell'ordine.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
2.5:
* 追跡して次の修正を実行しました :注文を完了してアプリを最小化した後に発生した稀なクラッシュ、サイトピッカーで選択したサイトが以前の選択内容にスイッチバックするバグ、新しい「レビュー」タブに関する UI の問題の一部。
* 注文詳細の画面で製品名を折り返して2行で表示できるようになりました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
2.5:
* 추적 및 수정 내용: 주문을 이행하고 앱을 최소화한 후 발생하는 드문 충돌, 사이트 선택 도구에서 선택한 사이트가 이전 선택으로 다시 전환되는 버그, 새로운 "검토"탭의 UI 문제.
* 이제 주문 세부정보 화면에서 제품 이름을 2줄로 줄바꿈할 수 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
2.5:
* We hebben het volgende gevonden en gerepareerd: een zeldzame crash die plaatsvond na het voltooien van een bestelling en het minimaliseren van de app, een bug die ervoor zorgde dat de geselecteerde sitekiezer terugkeerde naar de vorige selectie en een paar UI-problemen met het nieuwe tabblad 'Beoordelingen'.
* Productnamen kunnen nu op twee regels worden weergegeven op het scherm met bestelgegevens.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
2.5:
* Rastreamos e corrigimos: um travamento raro que ocorria após a conclusão de um pedido e ao minimizar o aplicativo, um bug que fazia com que o site selecionado no seletor de sites retornasse à seleção anterior e alguns problemas de interface na nova guia "Comentários".
* Os nomes dos produtos agora podem ser agrupados em duas linhas na tela de detalhes do pedido.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
2.5:
* Мы нашли и исправили следующее: редкую ошибку, которая возникала, если заполнить заказ и свернуть приложение; ошибку, из-за которой при выборе сайта выделение откатывалось на шаг назад; несколько проблем с интерфейсом новой вкладки "Обзоры".
* Названия товаров в окне информации о заказе теперь помещаются в две строки.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
2.5:
* Vi har hittat och åtgärdat: en sällsynt krasch som inträffade efter att en beställning hade lagts och appen minimerats, ett fel som gjorde att den valda webbplatsen i webbplatsväljaren växlade tillbaka till det föregående valet och några gränssnittsproblem med den nya fliken "Recensioner".
* Produktnamn kan nu sträcka sig över två rader på skärmen för beställningsinformation.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
2.5:
* Takip ettik ve aşağıdakileri düzelttik: bir sipariş verilip uygulama simge durumuna küçültüldükten sonra oluşan nadir bir hata, site seçiciden site seçildikten sonra önceki seçime geri dönülmesine neden olan bir hata ve yeni “Yorumlar” sekmesiyle ilgili bir kaç kullanıcı arayüzü sorunu.
* Ürün adları artık sipariş ayrıntıları ekranında iki satıra sarılabiliyor.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
2.5：
* 我们跟踪并修复了以下内容：完成订单并将应用程序最小化后偶尔出现的崩溃、导致站点选择器中所选站点切换回之前选择的站点的错误，以及新“评论”选项卡中存在的一些 UI 问题。
* 产品名称现在可以在“订单详细信息”屏幕中分两行显示。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
2.5：
* 我們已追蹤及修正以下問題：履行訂單並最小化應用程式後所發生不常見的當機情形；導致所選網站在網站挑選器中切換回上一個選項的錯誤；以及「評論」分頁的一些 UI 問題。
* 產品名稱現在可於訂單詳細資料畫面中以兩行顯示。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
2.5:
* We tracked down and fixed: a rare crash that happened after fulfilling an order and minimizing the app, a bug causing the selected site in the site picker to switch back to the previous selection, and a few UI issues with the new “Reviews” tab.
* Product names can now wrap onto two lines in the order detail screen.
/<en-US>
