<ar>
15.2:
يسرنا الإعلان عن تحديث جديد لتطبيق Android لدينا! في هذا الإصدار، قمنا بنقل خيار "إغلاق الحساب" إلى قسم جديد يُسمى "إعدادات الحساب" لتسهيل التنقل. لقد أصلحنا بعض المشكلات المتعلقة بعدد شارات الطلبات لضمان التتبُّع الدقيق. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أجرينا تحسينات إلى مهمة إعداد WooPayments من أجل عملية إعداد أكثر سلاسة. التحديث الآن للحصول على تجربة مستخدم أفضل!
</ar>
<de-DE>
15.2:
Großartige Neuigkeiten: Unsere Android-App bekommt ein neues Update! In dieser Version wurde die Option „Konto schließen“ für eine einfachere Navigation in den neuen Bereich „Kontoeinstellungen“ verschoben. Außerdem wurden Probleme beim Badge-Zähler für Bestellungen behoben, um eine genaue Sendungsverfolgung zu ermöglichen. Für einen reibungsloseren Einrichtungsprozess haben wir zudem die Onboarding-Aufgabe für WooPayments verbessert. Führe jetzt ein Update durch, um von einem verbesserten Benutzererlebnis zu profitieren!
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
15.2:
Estamos encantados de anunciar una nueva actualización para nuestra aplicación de Android. En esta versión, hemos movido la opción «Cerrar cuenta» a una nueva sección llamada «Ajustes de la cuenta» para facilitar la navegación. También hemos solucionado algunos problemas con el contador de insignias del pedido para garantizar un seguimiento preciso. Además, hemos realizado mejoras en la tarea de incorporación de WooPayments para que el proceso de configuración sea más fluido. Actualiza ahora para una mejor experiencia de usuario.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
15.2 :
Nous sommes ravis d’annoncer une nouvelle mise à jour de notre application Android ! Dans cette version, nous avons déplacé l’option « Fermer le compte » dans une nouvelle section appelée « Réglages du compte » afin de faciliter la navigation. Nous avons également corrigé certains problèmes liés au compteur de badges des commandes afin d’assurer un suivi précis. De plus, nous avons apporté des améliorations à la tâche d’accueil de WooPayments pour un processus d’installation plus fluide. Effectuez la mise à jour dès maintenant afin de profiter d’une meilleure expérience utilisateur !
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
15.2:
אנחנו שמחים להכריז על העדכון החדש של האפליקציה! בגרסה הזאת העברנו את האפשרות 'לסגור את החשבון' למקטע חדש בשם 'הגדרות חשבון' כדי לשפר את הניווט. תיקנו גם כמה בעיות במונה הסמלים של ההזמנה כדי להבטיח מעקב מדויק. בנוסף, הוספנו שיפורים למשימת ההצטרפות ל-WooPayments כדי לאפשר תהליך התקנה חלק יותר. כדאי לעדכן עכשיו לחוויית שימוש טובה יותר!
</iw-IL>
<id>
15.2:
Dengan gembira kami umumkan pembaruan untuk aplikasi Android kami! Di versi ini, kami memindahkan opsi 'Tutup Akun' ke bagian baru dengan nama 'Pengaturan Akun' agar navigasi lebih mudah. Kami juga memperbaiki beberapa isu terkait penghitung lencana pesanan untuk memastikan pelacakan yang akurat. Dan, kami juga menyempurnakan langkah penyiapan WooPayments agar proses penyiapan berjalan lebih lancar. Perbarui sekarang untuk pengalaman lebih baik!
</id>
<it-IT>
15.2:
Siamo felici di annunciare un nuovo aggiornamento per l'app per Android. In questa versione, l'opzione "Chiudi l'account" è spostata in una nuova sezione, "Impostazioni dell'account", per una navigazione più semplice. Abbiamo anche risolto alcuni problemi al contatore dei badge dell'ordine per un monitoraggio accurato. Inoltre, abbiamo migliorato l'attività di avviamento di WooPayments per un processo di configurazione più fluido. Aggiorna ora per una migliore esperienza utente.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
15.2:
Android アプリの新しいアップデートを発表できることを大変嬉しく思います。 このバージョンでは、「アカウントを閉じる」オプションを「アカウント設定」という新しいセクションに移動し、操作しやすくなりました。 正確に追跡できるよう、注文のバッジカウンターに関する問題もいくつか修正しました。 さらに、WooPayments のオンボーディングタスクを改善し、セットアッププロセスがよりスムーズになりました。 今すぐ更新してさらに便利にご利用ください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
15.2:
Android 앱의 새로운 업데이트를 발표합니다! 이 버전에서는 더 쉽게 탐색할 수 있도록 '계정 종료' 옵션을 '계정 설정'이라는 새로운 섹션으로 이동했습니다. 정확하게 추적할 수 있도록 주문의 몇 가지 배치 카운터 문제도 해결했습니다. 또한 설정 프로세스를 더 원활하게 진행할 수 있도록 WooPayments 온보딩 작업을 개선했습니다. 사용자 환경이 나아지도록 지금 업데이트하세요!
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
15.2:
We kondigen vol blijdschap de nieuwe update aan voor onze Android-app! In deze versie hebben we optie Account sluiten verplaatst naar een nieuw gedeelte genaamd Accountinstelling voor eenvoudiger navigeren. We hebben ook een aantal problemen opgelost met de badgeteller van bestellingen om voor nauwkeurigere tracking te zorgen. Daarnaast hebben we ook verbeteringen aangebracht aan de WooPayments-onboardingstaken voor een soepeler instellingsproces. Update nu voor een betere gebruikerservaring!
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
15.2:
Apresentamos uma nova atualização para nosso aplicativo no Android! Nesta versão, transferimos a opção “Encerrar conta” para uma nova seção chamada “Configurações da conta“ para facilitar a navegação. Também corrigimos alguns problemas com o contador de selo do pedido para garantir a precisão no rastreamento. Além disso, aprimoramos a tarefa de integração do WooPayments para uma configuração mais tranquila. Atualize agora mesmo para uma experiência do usuário ainda melhor!
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
15.2.
Рады сообщить вам об обновлении приложения для устройств на базе Android! В этой версии мы переместили опцию «Закрыть учётную запись» в новый раздел «Настройки учётной записи», чтобы упростить навигацию. Мы также исправили ряд проблем со счётчиком значка заказа, чтобы обеспечить точный подсчёт. Кроме того, мы усовершенствовали задачу адаптации WooPayments, чтобы сделать процесс настройки более плавным. Обновите приложение прямо сейчас!
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
15.2:
Vi är glada att kunna presentera en ny uppdatering av vår Android-app! In this version, we've moved the 'Close Account' option to a new section called 'Account Settings' for easier navigation. We've also fixed some issues with the order's badge counter to ensure accurate tracking. Plus, we've made improvements to the WooPayments onboarding task for a smoother setup process. Uppdatera nu för en bättre upplevelse.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
15.2:
Android uygulamamız için yeni bir güncellemeyi duyurmaktan büyük heyecan duyuyoruz! Bu sürümde, daha kolay gezinme deneyimi için 'Hesabı Kapat' seçeneğini 'Hesap Ayarları' adlı yeni bir bölüme taşıdık. Ayrıca, doğru takibi sağlamak için siparişin rozet sayacındaki bazı sorunları giderdik. Ayrıca, daha sorunsuz bir kurulum süreci için WooPayments yeni müşteri görevinde iyileştirmeler yaptık. Daha iyi bir kullanıcı deneyimi için şimdi güncelleyin!
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
15.2：
我们很高兴地宣布，Android 版应用程序已更新！ 在此版本中，我们将“关闭账户”选项移动到了名为“账户设置”的新部分，以方便导航。 我们还修复了订单徽章计数器的一些问题，以确保跟踪的准确性。 此外，我们还对 WooPayments 的登录任务进行了改进，使设置过程更加顺畅。 立即更新，获得更优用户体验！
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
15.2：
很高興在此宣布 Android 應用程式推出全新更新！ 此版本將「關閉帳號」選項移到稱為「帳號設定」的新區塊，瀏覽起來更加輕鬆。 這次也修正了一些訂單徽章計數器問題，確保能準確追蹤。 此外也改善了 WooPayments 入門任務，設定過程更順暢。 立即更新就能享受更優秀的使用者體驗！
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
15.2:
We're thrilled to announce a new update for our Android app! In this version, we've moved the 'Close Account' option to a new section called 'Account Settings' for easier navigation. We've also fixed some issues with the order's badge counter to ensure accurate tracking. Plus, we've made improvements to the WooPayments onboarding task for a smoother setup process. Update now for a better user experience!
</en-US>
