<ar>
17.2:
يتضمن الإصدار تحسينات تتعلق بالسرعة والموثوقية. إننا ملتزمون بمواصلة تحسين التطبيق، ما يجعل إدارة متجرك على الإنترنت أكثر كفاءة وخالية من العقبات.
</ar>
<de-DE>
17.2:
Diese Version enthält Optimierungen im Hinblick auf Geschwindigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit. Unser Ziel ist es, die App kontinuierlich zu verbessern, damit du deinen Onlineshop effizient und stressfrei verwalten kannst.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
17.2:
Esta versión incluye optimizaciones de velocidad y fiabilidad. Nuestro compromiso es que mejoraremos continuamente la aplicación, para que puedas gestionar tu tienda en Internet de forma eficaz y sin ningún problema.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
17.2 :
Dans cette version, la vitesse et la fiabilité ont été optimisées. Nous nous engageons à améliorer sans cesse notre application pour vous permettre de gérer plus efficacement et sans le moindre souci votre boutique en ligne.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
17.2:
הגרסה הזאת כוללת מיטוב למהירות וליציבות. אנחנו מחויבים להמשיך לשפר את האפליקציה כדי לאפשר לך לנהל את החנות המקוונת בצורה יעילה וללא בעיות.
</iw-IL>
<id>
17.2:
Versi ini mencakup optimasi kecepatan dan keandalan. Kami berkomitmen untuk terus meningkatkan aplikasi, sehingga toko online Anda dapat dikelola secara lebih efisien dan bebas repot.
</id>
<it-IT>
17.2:
Questa versione include ottimizzazioni per velocità e affidabilità. Ci impegniamo a migliorare continuamente l'app, rendendo la gestione del tuo negozio online più efficiente e meno problematica.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
17.2:
このバージョンには速度と信頼性の最適化が含まれています。 私たちはアプリを継続的に改善し、オンラインストアの管理がより効率的かつ手間のかからないものになるよう取り組んでいます。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
17.2:
이 버전에는 속도 및 안정성 최적화가 포함됩니다. 더 효율적이면서 간편하게 온라인 스토어를 관리하실 수 있도록 지속적으로 앱을 개선하기 위해 최선을 다하고 있습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
17.2:
Deze versie omvat optimalisaties voor snelheid en betrouwbaarheid. We zijn eraan toegewijd om de app steeds te blijven verbeteren, waardoor we het beheer van je online winkel efficiënter en handiger maken.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
17.2:
This version includes optimizations for speed and reliability. Temos o compromisso de melhorar cada vez mais o aplicativo para deixar o gerenciamento da sua loja online mais eficiente e simples.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
17.2:
В эту версию вошли усовершенствования в сферах быстродействия и надёжности. Мы стремимся постоянно совершенствовать приложение, чтобы вы могли управлять своим онлайн-магазином ещё более эффективно и без всяких проблем.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
17.2:
Den här versionen inkluderar optimeringar för snabbhet och tillförlitlighet. Vi arbetar kontinuerligt med förbättringar av appen, så att du ska kunna hantera din onlinebutik på ett effektivt sätt utan krångel.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
17.2:
Bu sürümde hız ve güvenilirlik için optimizasyonlar yapıldı. Uygulamayı sürekli iyileştirmeye ve çevrimiçi mağazanızı daha verimli ve sorunsuz hale getirmeye kararlıyız.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
17.2：
此版本在速度和可靠性方面进行了优化。 我们致力于持续改进该应用程序，助您更轻松高效地管理您的在线商店。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
17.2:
此版本包含了可提升速度和可靠性的最佳化功能。 我們會致力改善應用程式，持續讓管理線上商店更有效率且更輕鬆。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
17.2:
This version includes optimizations for speed and reliability. We are committed to continuously improving the app, making managing your online store more efficient and hassle-free.
</en-US>
